Chapter 171: The Day Before 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Grandmaster, my martial arts takes priority over my family household." The youngster replied with respect.

"Di Youwen Household?" Garen was slightly stunned as household was very well known. It had the potential to be in the top ten households in the whole Federation. They often appeared in the news as well. The household was one of the founders of this country and had great authority. They were considered the big guns in the southern region, and Garen didn’t expect that a member from this household would want to join his sects.

"When did you enter White Cloud Gate?" Garen frowned.

Simon was stunned and quickly explained as he knew there must be some misunderstanding.

"Master, Yuan Reese joined when Corinne and I were taking care of the sects. He enrolled as a normal student after the battle between you and Andrela. I recommended him after I realized that he was qualified to grow even more."

"Oh?" Garen didn’t expect him to join in that early on. He looked at Yuan Reese. A youngster with deep eyes and a sharp gaze. He seemed to have very high perseverance, and obviously had a strong motive.

"There are so many sects out there. Is there any reason you chose White Cloud Gate?" He asked him directly without trying to hide his suspicion.

Yuan Reese was stunned for a bit but naturally recovered from it.

"Yes. Sister Felicity and I were best of friends. She was the one who introduced me to learn martial arts."

"Ah, Felicity." Garen understood and recalled that noble and naughty woman. "If it’s her then it’d be expected. How is she now?"

"She’s well, except that she is currently grounded and isn’t allowed out of the house." Yuan Reese softly replied. This youngster seemed to be very soft and weak when he spoke. He looked so elegant that he didn’t look like a male at all. People might have sized him up as a female if not for his adam’s apple.

After looking at Yuan Reese and Karina again, the female was cold looking whereas the male was gentle and beautiful. Although they looked different physically, both of them had the same, firm gaze. He wasn’t sure if they had joined the sects because of the benefits it would bring to their household, or if they were here on their own accord.

"Both of you have spirit. If you work hard enough you’ll definitely succeed before you reach twenty years old. It all depends on whether you guys can hold up to it." Garen nodded his head in satisfaction. No matter how you looked at it, Both of them represented the power of complete surrender on this land and a powerful household in this country. The White Cloud Gate would be fine with these two around. This was especially true for Yuan Reese as he, a household member of the top ten households in the Federation,and even enrolled into the White Cloud Gate, meaning that he acknowledged Garen and the entire White Cloud Gate.

"Since Grandmaster is here, I have a question to ask, but I’m unsure if you would want to answer it." Yuan Reese lowered his head and asked.

"What’s your question?" Garen agreed as he was in a good mood.

"It’s regarding the key elements to martial art. What is the most important factor for a martial artist? What makes the martial artist able to keep moving forward?" Yuan Reese directly questioned the core of the subject.

Simon, Corinne and even Garen was slightly stunned. If he asked this question, it meant that Yuan Reese was not mentally ready yet.

Garen looked at the beautiful boy again. Through his gaze, he saw a firm and strong will.

Only a faint breath and heartbeat could be heard in the performance hall, as no one spoke for a short while.

Yuan Reese continued staring at Garen. Although he looked relaxed, he was actually under a tremendous amount of pressure. He felt like something was pressing onto him whenever he tried to inhale. Sweat started to break out from his temple and flowed down along his face.

He had the same feeling when he met his uncle who was a lieutenant general. However it was not as intense as this. Even meeting the patriarch of the parliaments wasn’t this terrifying.

It was totally different from them. When he faced the Grandmaster Garen, he felt a sense of horror.

Yuan Reese’s was so horrified that his hair all over his body were frozen. It was as if there was an abyss in front of him and the moment he leaned forward he would fall into it.

"Your household didn’t agree to let you join the sects, right?" Garen suddenly questioned him.

Yuan Reese was stunned and bit his lips.

"Yes. They strongly opposed me from joining. I came here without their knowledge."

"This!!..." Simon and Corinne were both stunned.

Being a member of the top ten households in the Federation meant he had a huge authority.

"Didn’t you say they agreed to let you join?" Simon panicked.

"Sorry master." Yuan Reese lowered his head and apologized. "I was being capricious." He hadn’t really wanted to join the White Cloud Gate. At first, he just wanted to have fun and take it as a leisurely hobby. He didn’t expect to be targeted by Simon when they were having a conversation.

Even Simon agreed to let him become his disciple without a second doubt.

He wasn’t even sure how important was the relationship between a master and a disciple in the martial art world. Yuan Reese didn’t hold this relationship in high regard as well, and both of them confusingly went through the process of learning the Mammoth Secret Technique.

It was too late when Yuan Reese realized that something was not right. He wasn’t able to break off this relationship since he had learnt and experienced the secret techniques of the White Cloud Gate. Not to mention, he even consumed the body quenching pill.

Garen had already made a name for himself here when he decided to break off the relationship with Simon.

The relationship between a master and disciple had become a complicated situation.

As Yuan Reese thought of this, he raised his head and looked at Simon. Both of them were speechless.

It would be considered a rebellion if Yuan Reese leave the sects now. Simon, who knew of Rosetta’s outcome started to fear for Yuan Reese, who also knew Rosetta’s situation as well. This was one of the reason why he wanted to meet Garen through Simon.

Garen smiled as if he was not concerned with the situation.

"Regarding your question, I can tell you the answer. However, every martial artist has their own answer to this question."

"Please enlighten me, Grandmaster." Yuan Reese collected himself and replied.

"In my opinion, there are two key elements to a martial artist." Garen slowly said.

"Number one: Talent. To be more precise, physical talent. You’ll learn faster and save more time if you’re physically stronger. This allows you to go to the higher level."

Everyone nodded as they agreed with the explanation.

"Second: Spirit." Garen raised one of his fingers to emphasize on this point.

"No matter if you’re a hobbyist, martial artist, or even Grandmaster of Combat. Spirit is very important." Garen was slightly emotional, "Take those who fights on the street for example. If one were spiritually threatened before the fight, will it determine the outcome of the battle?"

Garen continued his explanation as they seemed to be confused.

"If two commoners with the same physical attribute, strength and speed fight, the one with weaker spirit would have less confidence in himself and try to defend and avoid more. The one with a stronger spirit would continuously attack. If there are no major unexpectations, the winner will always be the one with stronger spirit."

"I’m starting to understand." Yuan Reese frowned.

d

Garen looked at Karina, who seemed to understand the idea as well. Both children had a strong sense of understanding. Corinne obviously understood the answer. However, Simon was the only one who didn’t get it.

"What about the tier of the martial artist?" Yuan Reese followed up with another question.

"Martial artists want to be stronger so that they can showcase their courage and challenge the limits of the human body. so that they could become the Grandmaster of Combat." Garen calmly explained. "The spirit of martial art is formed from the courage and spirit of the user, which will show the personality of the martial artist. The effects differ from everyone. Some use courage to oppress the enemy, some use it to disrupt the enemy’s spirit. Since I have not met many Grandmasters of Combat, my knowledge here is limited."

"What’s the importance of spirit to a Grandmaster of Combat then?" Yuan Reese asked another question again.

"It’s too early for you to ask such a question." Garen sat down firmly as he looked at Yuan Reese, who was a youngster not older than fifteen years old. He was indeed a good seedling as he was able to converse with him without feeling pressured.

"However, I can tell you a little bit."

Garen answered him with some admiration.

"If you have a weak spirit, you will not be able to react fast enough to the enemy’s attack and the sudden change in the situation. If you have a weak spirit, you’ll hesitate, and slow down when it comes to making a decision. One mistake leads to another, and this causes the fighter to lose confidence in his decision, which then delays his actions even further. The chances of winning will definitely lessen, no matter how strong you are."

He added on: "If your spirit isn’t strong enough, you’ll not be able to react in time due to your hesitation. Most of the time it will be that crucial moment that decides the outcome of the battle. This is the importance of spirit and courage."

"This is why a lot professionals would try to break the opponent before battle. If they succeed, the opponent’s chances of winning will greatly diminish." Garen looked at Yuan Reese and continued, "Professionals who do not have a strong spirit will use other methods to attack their opponent. For example, they would use words to agitate, or hidden schemes to fight their opponent,"

"I understand." Yuan Reese nodded his head. "In short, one has a higher chance of losing a battle of equals, if one’s spirit is disturbed. This is because one is unable to bring out his true strength as the spirit, hence the chances of winning will decrease."

"How do we increase our spirit then?"

"This depends on the individual itself. There are a lot of methods in strengthening one’s spirit. All you need to do is find a method that suits you best." Garen didn’t give him any indication. He couldn’t help but to smile as he looked at the four of them who was pondering on what he just said.

"You can ask me any questions now since both of you, namely Simon and Corinne, will be managing the White Cloud Gate in the future."

Simon and Corinne looked at each other and stood up.

"Please teach us more master."

Both of them started to put out the White Cloud Gate’s pose as they were ready to fight.

Seeing the situation, both Yuan Reese and Karina got up and moved back.

"Come at me both at once. Let me see how much you have improved." Garen sat firmly and didn’t move at all.

Chapter 172: The Day Before 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After correcting Corinne’s and Simon’s mistakes as well as answering their questions, Garen started cleaning up the mess that was White Cloud Gate after his departure.

His sister’s exams were already over. Garen visited his family for a bit, asked a little about his sister’s result. Ying Er scored normally, one subject wasn’t that great, another she did wonderfully, cancelling each other out.

Ying Er planned to apply to Shengying University, which is the direct pathway from Shengying Academy.

Under the influence of Golden Hoop, Huaishan and other surrounding districts were like metal buckets, safe and secure. The only thing Golden Hoop lacks was the presence of a high-powered individual, otherwise they were equally matched to other influences in the world. They can even take care of his sister slightly under the name of Shengying University.

Garen also arranged for Second Senior Brother Joshua to take care of most of the properties of White Cloud Gate.

Garen also modified some misconceptions in the Mammoth Secret Technique, choosing nuggets of better fleshed out methods in other secret martial arts and modifying it. Even though, at the highest level, other people will still not be able to use the secret technique like he does, it was much better than the regular third-rate secret technique, approaching a second-rate secret technique like the Red Jade Palm.

He also asked Corinne to talk to Ying Er as a fellow woman to gauge if she’s willing to join White Cloud Gate to learn secret martial arts.

Ying Er’s talent in learning secret martial arts was average, however, she does have a great understanding of bowmanship, so she’s not willing to waste time on secret martial arts.

She had enough training to protect herself without a weapon. To raise her level, she’ll need to spend her time mainly on martial arts, which she’s not willing to do. After all, no one can be like Garen with his abnormal special abilities.

Any discipline will need focus to allow oneself to achieve better results. Stronger secret martial arts would mean one would need to spend more time in maintaining their training, otherwise it would be like rowing a boat against the current, the boat would reverse even if one doesn’t move.

The adaptability of human body would make any fighter forget their training.

Garen, however, is different. His special ability has completely eliminated his body’s ability to forget, solidifying his physical attributes. In other words, he would not have bad days, but he would also not be able to perform beyond his standard. That’s because his progression and regression of power all depend on his physical attributes.

With sloth and self-indulgence, the body will naturally think it doesn’t need to maintain the physical conditions anymore, and will slowly decrease nutritional supply and finally degenerate,

With high pressure, the body will keep requiring more power to adapt to the situation and solve the threat from the outside world.

This is Darwin’s Theory of Evolution*, it is a natural instinct of every living being.

　　

Garen have always known that. Hence, his special ability is his biggest secret, no one else other than him knew about it. Ever since his attributes grew stronger, he can no longer improve his physique with just training, it’s as if he was in a perfectly stable condition.

For every gain, there will be a loss. He knew that. His special ability disabled his ability to forget, making him stronger, but at the same time losing his adapting mechanism.

He finally realized, this special ability takes root in the world view and the limitless knowledge he had access to from Earth. His subconscious used these knowledge to create a reflection of his special ability in a way that’s most suitable for him, by becoming a game-esque status bar.

After tying up loose ends, he left Huaishan City with going to University as an excuse, and took the train straight to Harmony City, planning to go to Skylark Mountain Waterfall from there.

　　

The Confederation and Weisman’s conflict has already started, as reflected by the small clashes at the border. The newspaper from both ends had already evolved into a medium for the war of words.

Even on the train he would see Confederate soldiers being mobilized to conduct training exercises.

The normal train service in Confederate was not luxurious, there were no beds in those. Only special trains will have this service. Garen was on normal trains the last few times he took them, but as of now, he managed to get on a special train, utilizing Golden Hoop’s special power. The train had only five compartments for a dozen people to rest in.

There were food, drinks, magazines, and newspapers, all available for free. As a special train, it takes priority over other trains, hence it was fast traveling in it. The whole trip to Harmony City spent only about a day.

By now, his fame has already spread past the whole of the South, even Northerners have heard about him.

During the battle at Crimson Sand Sword Gate main branch, he single-handedly defended a joint attack from Behemoth Gate and Black Mark Association, which included the hunting team from Weisman. Compared to the battle with Andrela, this battle is far more dangerous.

Alighting the train, Garen led Cynthia and Jack into a special passage, and exited the train station under the protection of marshals.

The sky was still dim.

The street was littered with a few cars and carriages. There was a silver car in the midst of it, doors wide open, a young girl holding the door with a smile.

The girl was dressed in a purple gown and wore a black crystal earring, looking graceful and delicate.

　　

"Hi master, it’s been a while."

Garen walked onto the street and saw this girl waving at him, smiling.

"Aris, how are you here?"

Su Lin’s sister Aris approached him with a cheeky smile, her arms wrapping around Garen naturally.

"Why can’t I be here? Let’s go, rest for a bit at my place. When you’re in Harmony City, you’ve got to let me be a good host! I have already booked a large room at Rose’s Whisper, a lot of my girlfriends couldn’t wait to meet you!"

"Stop that, I have business to attend to, I won’t be here for long." Garen felt a slight helplessness.

"But all my friends really wanted to meet you, master, come with Rissy~~~" Aris immediately pressed her bust against Garen’s arm in a coquettish way, her aristocratic elegance completely missing from her behavior.

"I really do have things to do. Maybe next time. Tell your dad I said hello." Garen declined decisively.

The battle with White Bird Holy Fist Palosa is what he have been looking forward to. Even now, he’s slightly excited just thinking about it, not wanting to do anything else.

Aris’ intention of introducing him to her friends may not be that simple. Her resorting to acting coquettishly, it must be some other reasons.

Garen gave it a thought, "Let’s do it this way. Vanhatten."

A man in black stepped forward.

"Yes sir, is there anything I can do?"

"Help Aris with whatever she needs help with." Garen didn’t hesitate utilizing this subordinate Golden Hoop has assigned him.

"Consider it done." Vanhatten smiled gently, "Miss Aris, you need not trouble Master Garen with the issue with Felicia Sisterhood, your brother could’ve solved it himself."

"You knew?" Aris was slightly taken aback, and looked at the black haired youth.

Aris herself banded together with a few friends to found a sisterhood and gained some influence in the Eliza Province. Recently, they got into a row with some other groups with some other princelings and princesslings*. She wanted to get Garen to show up at her party so she could take advantage of his fame to suppress their arrogance.

From her father, she found out about the extent of Garen’s influence. The authorities were also shocked at Garen’s battle record. He was almost like a humanoid beast. Even the Weisman Hunting Team barely scratched him, as if he’s more durable than the armor of a tank.

Anyone who offended Garen would be hard-pressed to fight back without a cannon. Only by fleeing early on can they be safe.

"Hm, that’s also fine. I only needed master’s fame on my side." Aris grinned this time.

"What’s the matter?" Garen was slightly curious.

The black haired youth Vanhatten started explaining.

The Felicia Sisterhood hosted an underground fighting tournament in Harmony City. It was pretty prominent, and had recruited a batch of underground boxers to fight in a death match, at the same time, they opened bets to earn a huge profit. Recently however, an outsider organization from another area brought their boxers to fight in the tournament. The boxers were so strong, Felicia Sisterhood’s boxers kept losing, almost to the point of them losing all their money. It is then that Aris wanted to borrow Garen’s fame to warn the other party.

"Underground boxers? Are they strong?" Garen’s interest was piqued.

"It’s hard to say, some of them have some martial arts experience, some are descendents of fallen martial arts family. Some of them were even martial artists who led a poor life, you can find any kind of people in there. Some fighters also did that before their breakthrough." Vanhatten explained.

The three people stood in front of the car but didn’t get in. Garen shifted, holding the car door for support.

"Leo should be nearby, isn’t he? How is he?" He looked at Cynthia behind him.

Cynthia was attempting to blow bubble with her bubblegum. Hearing the question, she sucked the bubblegum back in.

"He’s alright. He injured his opponent quite badly. His opponent struggled a little, so he got slightly injured as well."

Garen nodded satisfactorily. To shrug off his past, King of Fist Leo attacked another King of Fist from Black Mark Association, heavily injuring him from the back. The only other King of Fist was not hurt, so he drove off Leo as he tended to the injured one and damaged Leo a little.

"You got their location?"

"Yeah, we’re following them, but there were people obstructing."

Kings of Fist from Black Mark Association were also Grandmasters of Combat. They were also looking forward to Garen’s challenge against White Bird Holy Fist Palosa before they were surprised by Leo.

It was also a pledge of Leo’s loyalty toward Garen. That man is a fanatic who would disregard everything for his ideals.

"Let’s check him out. We can let Leo do something about Aris’ problems."

Garen also wanted to whittle down the power of Black Mark Association. Their interference with White Cloud Gate was still fresh in his mind.

"What are you talking about?" Aris was confused, "Is this Leo strong?"

There are so many Leos on this world, it isn’t strange that she doesn’t know.

"Stop worrying, someone will take care of your problems really soon." Garen smiled, "Let’s go. I need to borrow your car. Jack, you’ll drive."

"Of course!" Jack opened the door from the driver seat like a pro.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. It’s actually Classical Conditioning by Pavlov. Author has not done his research.

2. 太子党 lit. Party's Crown Princes, are the descendants of prominent and influential senior officials in the country. It is not a political party, but an informal, and often derogatory, categorization to signify those benefiting from nepotism and cronyism, by analogy with crown princes in hereditary monarchies. “Princesslings” is the female variant.

Chapter 173: Disappointment 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In a forest between Harmony City and Vilmahn City.

The evening sun showered its golden rays ornamented with vermilion ribbons, painting the trees and hills with a reddish-orange.

At the peak of a hillock surrounded by pine trees, white buildings stood.

The buildings looked like individual cubes and rectangular prisms huddling up together under a blanket of artichoke green roofs.

From its side, at the exit of the buildings, two people in black supported each other by the arm and walked out, drenched in sweat. They walked warily, as if trying to avoid something.

They were a man and a woman, both of them had blonde hair.

The man was ugly. He had a crooked mouth pointing upward to the right, he looked as strange as strange can be.

The woman was pleasant looking, but pale. Her blonde hair was damp with sweat and sticking to her forehead.

Both of them descended the stone stairs leading away from the monastery in quick steps.

"Be strong! He couldn’t find us, by now he should have left!" The man helped the woman descend in quick but cautious steps.

"Leo, that traitor! I’m sorry, Manila, if it wasn’t for me, you wouldn’t be hurt." Blonde woman said in sorrow.

"That’s okay, I’m willing to do that for you." The ugly man Manila didn’t hesitate to answer her.

The woman eyes glimmered, moved by his words.

"Tsk tsk… how touching."

At the stone stairs behind them, a fit man wearing black followed them. The handsome man had a hooked nose with bluish-black eyes. He's wearing a smirk on his face.

"Leo!" Manila glared at the man behind, as if he wanted to kill him right there and then. He turned around, shielding the woman behind him. "As Kings of Fist of Black Mark Association, how could you betray us? Why!"

"Why?" Leo scoffed.

"There's a saying in the far East, ‘you can't explain snow to a worm in the summer.’ Do you know what that means?" His face contorted to show a sense of fanatic enthusiasm. "I'm chasing after my dream. My justice, my determination, these are what I base my actions on. As a fellow King of Fist, as a fellow Grandmaster of Combat, I can't stand how you two are always so naive."

He lowered his right fist which was covered with a black leather glove. His knuckles were layered with scale-like silvery white metal plates.

He waved his arm, producing a sound similar to an eagle's scream.

"Manila, Ankh, for the sake of my dreams," Leo held his arms up in preparation to attack, "Please die."

"You think you can take on the both of us at the same time?" The blonde woman Ankh stepped up, "Leo, you know that if we fight back with all our might, you would get badly injured or even die," She paused, "I don’t know what your goal is, but you have already forced us into a corner, you’ve pretty much succeeded in your goal, didn’t you? There is no need to have a lose-lose situation."

"Lose-lose situation?" Leo’s sneered at them even more. "No, no, that won’t happen. You see, no amount of struggle could mean anything in front of Lord Garen."

Stunned, Manila and Ankh slowly turned to look behind. On the stone step below them, a huge figure stood, observing them. They didn’t know when he arrived.

"Garen!"

Shivers creeped up on their skins.

The strongest elite from the Southern Martial Arts community! An undefeatable man seconded only to Palosa!

They stared at Garen’s still silhouette, feeling a strong pressure encasing them like an enormous shadow.

Garen stared back at both of the Kings of Fist of Black Mark Association, completely blocking the road downhill.

As one of the strongest fighters in the Martial Arts community, Garen’s presence itself was a serious impact toward the both of them.

He stood there, allowing his massive Bravery fill the air around him. The Bravery was thick, as though it’s going to solidify at any time. It was like a mountain, even though it’s lower than the both of them, it felt as if they can only look up to it.

"Black Mark Association… is finished…" Manila paled completely. As soon as Garen appeared, he knew this whole saga was going to arrive at its final act. They should have thought about the retribution when Black Mark Association sprang that attack on White Cloud Gate.

Ankh’s smile was one of sadness. "Let Manila go, I will ensure mother give everything to White Cloud Gate!"

Garen shook his head slowly. "You don’t have the authority to discuss conditions with me. Don’t you realize? The Confederation had been chaotic recently. A new age will come. Between Weisman and the Confederation, Confederation had been weak."

He looked at them in a composed manner.

"A war will break out. The stronger your individual power is, the safer you are on the battlefield. King of Fist Ankh, you father realized that. That was why he founded Black Mark Association. That was also why Celestial Circle Gate and Crimson Sand Sword Gate want a unified power."

Silence fell upon everyone like a blanket. The surrounded two were almost desperate enough to try and charge past their enemies.

The golden afternoon rays poured past the leaves and the branches, and finally found their spot on Garen’s figure.

His squinted slightly, his gaze still fixed on the Kings of Fist who huddled together.

"Killing you does not benefit me in any way."

The two finally loosened up, understanding the undertones of his speech.

"We will tell you about the Grandmaster of Combat who hurt Master Fei! Black Mark Association will also be appertained to Lord Garen." A voice belonging to an old lady beseeched from behind Garen.

The old lady approached with several masked men with cold eyes.

"We will surrender all the people who joined the operation." She said, in her low voice.

Garen was waiting for her, the proprietor of Black Mark Association, the mother of King of Fist Ankh, Vivian-Rita.

"Go arrange the necessary. That will be all today." Garen said, aloof. He turned around to look at the old lady. Black Mark Association no longer has any threat after the battle at Crimson Sand Sword Gate.

On the other hand, there was still no news about Behemoth Gate. Their power were too individualized, difficult to track through the grapevines.

Garen didn’t say anything more. He strolled down the stone stairs with Leo following behind, eventually disappearing from the long winding staircase.

Vivian-Rita and the two Kings of Fist stared at their leaving silhouettes. They understood Garen will definitely attack Black Mark Association if they decided to go back on their words. From the moment Garen appeared, it wouldn’t have mattered if the Kings of Fist were healthy anyway,

　　********************

It was already 9 p.m. when they returned to Vilmahn City.

After witnessing the power Garen amassed through his strength alone, Black Mark Association announced their intention to be appertained under White Cloud Gate.

A negotiation like this can’t be settled within a day, of course. Black Mark Association was delaying it until the battle between Garen and White Bird Holy Fist is over.

All of Garen’s influence is based on the absoluteness of his strength. If the battle between him and White Bird Holy Fist went awry, the deal would be called off immediately.

Not only them, every organization with influences were focusing on that battle that signifies the replacement of the strongest force between two generations of fighters.

Fighters from every sect swarmed into the city in which Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate was stationed, even some unpopular fighters gathered in the dark.

Celestial Circle Gate, Crimson Sand Sword Gate, The Northern Martial Arts Union, as well as sects Garen haven’t even heard of all flocked into the city, some of them wanting to witness the higher realms of Martial Arts, some others with their own ulterior motives.

The government mobilized the army to take care of the orderliness, but there were still fights happening all over the city, dragging the whole of Vilmahn City into chaos.

During the time which people gathered in Vilmahn City, several people dressed in white led Garen, Leo and others toward the depth of Skylark Mountain.

　　*********************

The sky was dimly lit.

At the edge of a large still lake, the three people in white hastily led Garen and the other three, looking like a line of black and white ants beside a moss green mirror.

Greenish-yellow trees and bushes littered around the lakeside. Some of them were bent toward the water, some even had their leaves and branches dipped into it.

Garen stepped on the damp muddy road, following the people in white, as he looked toward the right at the lake.

Somewhere in front was a pier covered with undergrowths and trees. It looked just like a roll of green threads floating on the water from afar.

Garen turned his attention back onto himself and moved his neck a little. A thumb-sized red-and-black mosquito wobbled out of his collar and fell to the ground before squashed by Garen with a stomp.

Aside from him and Leo, the people in white as well as Cynthia and Jack were fully wrapped up, reproducing the effect of a hazmat suit.

A man in white saw the scene and a trace of worry flashed through his eyes.

Gwarr!

A sudden roar came from the bank of a river in front.

A black bear stood beside the bank, watching over two little ones which are playing in the water, learning to catch a fish.

The black bear glared at the group and slowly moved its strong paws to face them. It growled in warning to the intruders. The two little bears stopped as well, staring at the group in curiosity.

A taller man in white stepped forward. He took out a small vial and gently opened the stopper.

Smelling something, the black bear shrank and growled. It took its cubs and left the vicinity of the lake, disappearing into the woods.

"Let’s go." One of the people in white murmured.

Garen and the others followed. "We’re almost there, please cover your nose and mouth with that thing and be patient just a little more." He added.

Garen and the team didn’t reply, instead they took out a small wooden white bottle and placed it under their noses.

A faint smell of green grass permeated the air around the group.

Chapter 174: Disappointment 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"This area here is restricted to people with Sir Palosa’s secret medicine. Without it, it’s impossible to go deep into the mountains." The leader of the people in white explained, "There’s poisonous gas all over the deeper parts of this forest. People who wandered in without the medicine died after having ulcerated." He took a glance at Garen, "Unless they have Mr. Garen’s physical constitution."

Garen didn’t make much of it, being a sky warrior of Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate, he was considered part of the sect. This battle can more or less be considered as an intersectional exchange.

The only thing is, at their level of fame and fighting ability, the aftermath of the battle will be colossal no matter who won. To minimize the influence this event will cause, the Gate Master of Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate sent Garen and his team in earlier than was expected.

Going to the mountains earlier doesn’t necessarily mean no one would ever find out, but at least it would be concealed from a huge number of people. Through the poisonous gas, even less people would get to know about this fight.

Garen and White Bird Holy Fist’s fight has already been listed as the highest priority classified information. Nobody aside from the Gate Master and Elders who are leading were allowed to watch.

Garen only brought Leo, Cynthia, and Jack. Cynthia and Jack were total outsiders, they wouldn’t be able to comprehend a fight between Grandmasters of Combat like this anyway, so they’re fine. With Leo, Garen brought him because he wanted to cultivate an efficient right hand man.

After warning them about things to look out for, the three in white continued marching toward the deep end of Skylark Mountain. They have been in motion since 3 a.m. of the previous night*, and even then, they were only entering the depth of Skylark Mountain, it’s still a long way before arriving at the Skylark Mountain Waterfall.

On their way there, some faint green mist slowly appeared in the air in front of them. Most of it hovered just above the water surface, some escaped into the woods, as if they were semitransparent threads floating in the air.

All of them clutched their vials tightly below their noses, allowing the mild scent of freshly mown grass take over their olfactory sense, separating the misty gas.

Even so, Cynthia and Jack were having itchiness all over their bodies, making them paranoid and nervous.

　

Garen suddenly frowned and raised his right arm. With the speed of a snap, he pinched a jade colored string.

It came from the woods on their left, shooting at the neck of the woman in white.

Hissss…

The string struggled in Garen’s hand, hissing like a snake does.

It was only then the other people noticed the furtive creature.

It looked just like a green wire without a head or a tail, squirming in Garen’s hand. No one can be sure from where they produced the sound.

If it hadn’t moved, no one would probably guessed it was a living thing.

"Viridian Nematode!" The leading man in white’s face changed, "Karen, did you bring anything made of iron in here!" He shot an accusing look at the woman.

"I… I brought a blue iron ring… It’s my birthday present from my son." Karen stuttered.

"Blue iron ring? Did you want to die?" The leader of the people in white yelled in exasperation, "Throw it away now! If it weren’t for Mr. Garen, you’re already dead! Viridian Nematodes love iron products, wearing it without the power to repel it, I’d have thought you have a death wish!"

"I’m sorry…" Karen fumbled to take it off, and threw it far into the bushes.

In an instant, a horde of green strings lynched at the ring, rolling it into a ball as big as a fist, and at the same time writhing around it.

Everyone felt goosebumps crawling underneath their skins seeing that.

Garen gave the one on his finger a dirty look, it’s like a wire, but much stronger.

His other hand reached up to pull it apart lightly. It’s unexpectedly unyielding.

Both sides of the worm kept trying to break his skin, as if they are attracted to the bloodstream. It kept drilling into the skin near his veins.

Ding! Ding!

The sound of microscopic needles hitting the surface of a metal kept ringing, spooking everyone around.

Especially the people in white, they weren’t looking at the Viridian Nematode, but Garen.

They are very clear about how deadly those worms can be with its durable body and powerful piercing abilities, they can even punch a hole in a steel board as think as a nail.

However, when dealing with Garen’s skin, it only managed to produce sounds like this.

Seeing how the worm just continued attacking Garen’s skin, but never succeeding, the people in white felt weak in their teeth.

"This thing…" Garen frowned, "Leo, Cynthia, Jack. Be mindful of their attacks. Have you cleared out your iron products?"

"Yes."

"None on me."

Leo nodded as well.

"I will destroy them when they strike." He wore a thick black leather gloves with a matte finish.

"Just be careful. It’s a little tricky." His frown became more intense.

He pinched both ends of the Viridian Nematode and pulled.

Crack!

The Viridian Nematode were spliced into two.

The weird thing is, even though it’s in two pieces, it still wiggled about as if it didn’t matter. As two individuals, they attacked both of Garen’s arms respectively.

"These are really tenacious." Garen clapped his hands together and started grinding. Within seconds, the Viridian Nematose was ground into green powder, and sprinkled from Garen’s palms.

"Mr. Garen, there were some other troubles in front, please be careful." The leading man in white reminded them.

The woman in white, Karen, was ordered to return.

The rest continued their hike.

Soon, the group met some other rather bothersome creatures.

Black spiders as big as a washbasin. White carps with sharp teeth hanging about at the edge of the lake. Giant black ants the size of a chicken egg.

All sorts of horrific animals and bugs appeared in their path.

Cynthia and Jack were already stiff with anxiety, having their guards up constantly.

Even the King of Fist Leo had his scalp tingling and unleashed some Bravery to surround him, in attempt to turn some creatures away. If those things came near him, even if he’s a Grandmaster of Combat, he would probably have problems fighting them.

Garen was amazed, but he didn’t show it on his face, following the men in white closely.

The uniforms the men in white received was specially made and can prevent most of the deadly attacks from the creatures, but Garen didn’t cover up fully, so there’s still some bugs attacking him.

Without exceptions, the bugs would touch his skin and immediately be paralyzed and bounced away. By the time they hit the ground, they are already dead.

At Garen’s level, the Counter Shockwave* as a result of the Body Hardening Technique can directly kill the bugs.

To him, as long as nothing broke his defense, nothing can threaten him.

Currently, his Spirit is always nurturing his body, even his weakest, the visceral organs, are strengthening by the minute.

The group had some jerky-filled breads for lunch, and continued hiking until late afternoon. A crescendo of the sound of flowing water came from the front.

With every step, the sound grew stronger and clearer.

After a few turns, the group finally arrived at the breakage of the lake.

The lake water flowed toward the cliff on their right, tempestuously free-falling for thirty-odd meters before crashing into the pool below, forming a huge white waterfall.

The group walked through the path on the left of the waterfall, arriving at an enormous white boulder.

The waterfall is like a white cloth tens of meters in length, hanging on a black cliff. In front of the oval greenish pool, a petite old man in white robes was fishing on the rock with a fishing pole.

The old man sat there, unmoving. Only the fishing pole swayed occasionally with the rapid water.

Garen followed the men in white behind the old man, and stood. With his eyesight, he could see there were worms so green they might as well be black swimming in the pool.

These worms are like enlarged loquat worms*. They have eight short legs and hard shells, as well as round bodies as large as a washbasin.

The old man heard the approaching guests and gently set down the fishing pole. He fixed the pole under a large rock before turning around.

"It’s been a long time since you visited, little Bondi. You’re such a big man now." The old man turned toward the leading man in white.

"It’s all thanks to grandpa." He bowed and answered.

　　

"You brought outsiders here?" The old man suddenly turned to Garen and his team before focusing on Garen and Leo. "Are they from our sect?"

Garen frowned slightly. The old man may have been living in seclusion for a while, he didn’t care and didn’t know anything from the outside world. He didn’t even know what they are here for.

"White Bird Holy Fist Sir Palosa?" He asked. "My name is Garen."

The old man took a double take. "It’s been so long before anyone called me by my title," He smiled, "Is there anything I can help you with? Looking at your age and your Bravery, you must have some kind of a story."

"I’m here to seek consultation about Martial Arts." Garen took a step forward in front of everybody.

The man in white retreated while giving signals to others to follow suit, giving the two space.

Garen placed his hands behind him.

"I have fought Duskdune Shura twice. He had nothing but good things to say about you, sir. He reckoned you were the strongest fighter of the contemporary, the peak of Martial Arts! As the strongest in my generation, I wish to seek advice from you."

"Duskdune Shura?" Palosa’s wrinkly face was covered with nostalgia for a second. "He’s a genius, even when I was younger. Our relationship was never good, I didn’t think he would give me such a high praise."

He woke from his nostalgia, and his gaze fell upon Garen’s hands, shaking his head.

"Too bad I already sealed my fist* a year ago. Please leave, I will not have this fight with you."

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. “昨晚三点”. That’s what the author wrote. The 3 a.m. of previous night.

2. Changed from counter-Vibration to Counter Shockwave because of the nature of the skill. Will henceforth be known as such.

3. A kind of harmful worms found commonly on loquat fruits.

4. 封拳”, lit. “Sealed fist”, meaning to stop hurting people with fist. May extend to other forms of fighting skills.

Chapter 175: Age of the Pinnacle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s face sank. The Palosa in front of him looked like any old man on the street, kind, lovely, not a strand of the aura of a Grandmaster of Combat, and no sign of Bravery. Then again, Garen understood the ability to survive in such a grisly environment is no easy feat, not to mention he seemed to be doing quite well.

"Sealed fist a year ago? Sir Palosa, I am also a Sky Warrior of Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate. Don’t you think that shouldn’t apply to a friendly exchange with a fellow member of the sect?"

Palosa smiled.

"Listen, kid. My fist technique is completely different from yours. Your Secret Fist Technique is almost at the highest mastery. I can tell, your Body Hardening Technique is almost as good as Duskdune Shura’s. At your age, you already achieved what Duskdune Shura can only achieve at his mid-life. With only that, you are at the top of the whole Confederation. At this stage, whatever you’re trying to prove, I understand. However, I’m not the direction you’re after. What you wanted to see, I want to see too."

Garen silenced, he heard the underlying meaning behind Palosa’s words. He hadn’t been able to step further into the Martial Arts Realm as well.

"I would still like to witness the legendary, unbeatable White Bird Holy Fist."

"White Bird Holy Fist, it’s only a name my colleagues gave me. I only knew one fist technique, and that was White Bird Fist." Palosa answered with a smile. "I’m not like the prodigy Duskdune Shura or the terrifyingly talented Watson Langley. What I am good with is White Bird Fist. I spent my whole life, all my energy into this fist technique. I have sealed my fists, I will not fight you, but I can show you once."

"Show me?" Garen squinted.

"The Martial Arts community has been weaker and weaker for past generations. Garen, is it? I will show you with a tenth of my power. Don’t blink an eye." Palosa smiled warmly while he slowly walked to a mossy boulder on the left.

"Watch carefully, this is where I am with fist techniques!" Palosa lifted his right arm with his index finger pointing forward.

Punch!

Everything around seemed to have stopped in time.

The air, the water, the worms, the grass, as well as all sorts of voices that came from afar.

Even the massive waterfall halted for an instant.

Everyone stopped in that very moment. No thoughts, no actions, as if they were covered with solidified amber. There weren’t able to move or think, time may as well have been frozen.

Boom!

A black Bravery burst out of Palosa’s body like a shapeless smoke. Black smoke congregated behind Palosa, forming a giant silhouette about ten meters tall with a formless lower body.

Garen was able to see, the upper half of that silhouette was definitely Palosa with the same features and the same age.

However, it looks different. The Palosa formed with Bravery held a twisted grin, distinguishing itself from the kind man Palosa had appeared to be.

"This is… Bravery solidified!"

Garen’s mouth dropped and haven’t been able to move it since. Of all the people, only he had been trembling violently, trying to break free of this frozen state.

"This is my White Bird Fist." Palosa murmured softly.

His finger pressed against the mossy boulder standing two meters tall in front of him.

With that, the alarming pressure disappeared. Everyone had recovered their ability to move.

Cracks appeared on the mossy boulder. There was no explosions, no bursting into powder, nothing superfluous.

However, as soon as cracks formed, it still gave everyone a shock seeing the crack.

Centering on where Palosa touched, cracked flared out all over the mossy boulder, forming a complex network of sort.

Cracks crossed each other and made their way to the other side of the boulder, meeting at one point on the left side of it.

All the cracks converged into a single spot, with a deep hole appearing on that spot on the boulder.

Garen looked at the spot Palosa tapped, there was only a small thumbprint on it.

He went quiet.

"Silent Redirection Punch?"

"Oh, you knew that?" Palosa turned to him, "I’m already too old, or I could have given it a hundred cracks, instead of ninety-nine."

He caressed the surface of the boulder.

"This is my White Bird Fist. I need not break people’s defense to be able to redirect the strength, in order to attack the heart of my enemy from all sides."

"This is the most heinous assassination punch. Before me, all the heir for this technique were natural butchers who had felled people like woodcutters do trees. With every punch they make, another person dies. Even I couldn’t contain my Bravery when I use this fist technique to fight. Do you still want to fight me?"

The solidified Bravery disappeared from Garen’s senses abruptly.

When normal Grandmasters of Combat show their Bravery, it’s gaseous. Stronger ones have their Bravery concentrated to a liquid state, like Duskdune Shura and his current state. This is the first time ever has he seen one with solid state, one so powerful it could almost stop time.

"Confinement Bravery, Bravery is the Spirit of a Grandmaster of Combat, compressed. To be able to achieve the solid state, the strength of your will and Spirit are hard for people to comprehend." Garen was not able to break out of the solid Bravery, but he as a Grandmaster of Combat cannot be scared away with just a few words.

Palosa represented the ultimate fighting ability of the human community, no matter what, Garen would want to try and fight him. That was his initial goal after all.

"Really?" Palosa furrowed his brows and stared at Garen.

"This is what I came for." Garen returned the stare with his own.

"Once I start, I can’t guarantee I have control over myself. If I accidentally killed you…"

"Kill me?" Garen interrupted, smirking. "If you are able to do that, try." Garen was fuming by now.

"I really don’t want to touch another fellow sect member’s blood any more." Palosa winced in pain, "Leave. If I couldn’t control myself and crippled you… I have made too many mistakes in my life."

Garen was seething in fury.

"If you crippled me, that’s my fault, I’m not strong enough, I have a death wish, nothing to do with you! Stop the dilly-dally and fight me!"

The old man was still acting nice and kind, but he kept provoking Garen with his tone of voice.

"Kid, you’re still young. If you are handicapped by this, it’ll be a burden to your family and friends. If anything happened to you, I will not be able to face your parents." Palosa said, placing his arms behind his back.

"I will be responsible to myself! This is my choice. As a Grandmaster of Combat, I will take on all my responsibilities!" Garen’s voice gets stronger and louder as he went on. "Weren’t you only waiting for this?" He smirked. "If anything happens, I will take full responsibility for my actions, not you!"

"You’re sure about this?" Palosa finally took him seriously.

"Of course." Garen started with White Cloud Gate’s default stance, condensing a large amount of Bravery around him, preparing to fight at anytime.

Seeing they finally wanted to start the fight, everyone else stepped out of range to make space for them.

Garena and Palosa stood facing each other on the white boulder. In black and white respectively, it was almost too easy to tell them apart.

"Lemme see what sort of fist technique the legendary White Bird Holy Fist is!" Garen changed his stance, opening his arm on different height, as if ready to grapple, and sank lower from his waist, changing into the default stance of another fist technique.

After maximizing his intelligence, Garen was able to analyze the different techniques of different schools, and developed this unique improved fighting technique, he took the three forms of Mammoth Secret Technique, as well as other techniques like Red Jade Palm, Fiery Claws, Golden Statue Technique, and combined them into his own unique battle skill.

This particular default stance referenced the Golden Statue Technique, it is, after all, the strongest technique within those he learned. The battle skills in it were very suitable for fighters focusing on physical enhancements like Garen.

"Golden Statue Technique?" Palosa recognized it. "If that really is the Golden Statue Technique, then I will find out how much of a golden statue you are!"

Before he finished his sentence, a massive amount of Bravery rushed at Garen, attempting to slam him down.

The solid Bravery became a gruesome psychological stress, stunning Garen in his tracks.

Thud!

He felt a dull pain shot through his chest. When he had come to, he was already halfway falling backwards.

Between Palosa’s speech and his falling backward, the period when he was stunned was at most one second.

Palosa approached him with a charge, his palm softly pressed upon Garen’s chest.

From the viewpoint of the audience, Palosa only hopped forward and lightly pressed his palm onto an unmoving Garen. They immediately separated after that, and Garen was suddenly flying backward.

"This again!" Mid-air, Garen hit the air twice with his palm in the opposite direction of his momentum.

Generating a strong counter force, Garen’s body stopped falling backward and started landing immediately.

As soon as he balanced himself on a boulder, he saw Palosa leaped at him with his right palm flexed, ready to strike as if he’s a lamb waiting to be butchered*.

"Double Shot Form!" Garen countered with both his arms, as if using two hammers to take on Palosa’s palm strike.

"Don’t blame me." Palosa looked at Garen with pity before utilizing his Bravery again.

Thud! Thud! Thud!

On the boulder, Palosa hit Garen once more, and immediately jumped behind him to hit him from the back.

He kept doing the same thing, like he’s just hitting a baseball.

Garen’s whole body was aching from the strikes, his body doesn’t even need to be stunned by Palosa’s Bravery anymore, even the strikes could disable him from counterattacking. Every single hit from Palosa landed exactly where he wanted to block.

Luckily, after the Body Hardening Technique fused with his Spirit, it had evolved further. When hit by Palosa’s palm strikes, his body will naturally filter out most of the Hidden Power, allowing only a tiny part of it to enter the body wreaking havoc.

However, Garen’s body and visceral organs were far too strong from normal humans, the Hidden Power didn’t hurt him much at all.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

Chinese idiom, meaning being helpless to the situation.

Chapter 176: Age of the Pinnacle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was still in his normal state. When Palosa’s initial attack hit him, he already understood the destructibility of it. It was strong, but Garen would still be fine without transforming.

Using his minimum power to fight the Holy Fist was one of his wishes before he departed to hone his skills.

Strike by strike, Palosa’s palm pressed on his torso. As Garen observed his fighting style, he noticed something.

Every time Palosa did a straight palm strike, he would push it upward slightly, his fist would be slightly crooked, that was so it would fit the way he uses his power. However, this would leave him with a slight opening beneath his palm.

Garen squinted, using conserving his full power waiting for the moment to counter his attack.

"Give up!" Palosa charged to the side and raised his arm, before striking the incoming Garen.

"There’s my chance!" Garen flipped aside mid-air and whipped his right arm toward Palosa’s underarm.

This strike is definitely Palosa’s weak spot. With Garen’s strength and Palosa’s age, if this strike connected, it would’ve been a decisive point for the battle!

At the same time, Palosa’s palm was quickly approaching Garen’s forehead.

Both of them were attacking each other’s underarm and head, respectively. Garen’s attack was clearly faster.

Right at that moment.

Fwoosh!

A solid state Bravery washed over Garen’s body, stunning him.

Thud!

A palm struck Garen’s forehead.

Garen’s legs stomped on the boulder and was shot backward. His feet slid over it, leaving two black lines on the boulder.

Everyone from afar was shocked.

"Gate Master is fine, right?" Jack swallowed out of concern. He saw Garen being hit on his head. That’s his head! Not any other body part!* Combined with Palosa’s incredible control over his Hidden Power…

"I’m not sure, but Gate Master is really strong too, how would he be hurt with only one strike?" Cynthia wasn’t even chewing her bubble gum anymore. She said that, but her face showed a hint of worry. "Lord Leo, you’re a high ranking Grandmaster of Combat, what do you think?"

Leo brows were also knitted tightly together.

"Hard to say, but since Gate Master has reached an exceptional height in his Body Hardening Technique, he might be okay."

"Might be?" Cynthia and Jack both understood, Leo was also not sure.

The Gate Master of the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate was also closely following the happenings on the field below him. Not only him, the other man in white, the elder of his sect was stunned, like him.

From when they knew Palosa, anyone, any elites or Grandmasters of Combat, Palosa had never used a second round of attack before they were all heavily injured.

But now, Garen has already took countless hits, and they could tell Palosa was not holding back, he never would, but Garen didn’t even have a scratch on him.

"This White Cloud Gate Master is terrifyingly resilient! His Body Hardening Technique is beyond belief!" Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate Master looked at Garen on the boulder, his eyes sympathetic. "Grandpa Palosa’s fist technique deals damage to the inside with every attack, not even the giant alligators and giant rhinoceroses could withstand a second attack."

"Lord Palosa had apparently focused his Bravery onto Garen though," The elder said, "The situation’s a little complicated now."

Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate Master nodded without a sound.

When everyone was staring at the battlefield, Garen was standing still, indicating this battle was not over.

"White Bird Holy Fist! I don’t see any white birds in your fist technique." Garen waited until his breath returned to normal, and provoked. "Looks like I need to use my true power…"

Crack!

He left a crater where he stood with a stomp, charging toward Palosa as if becoming a black arrow.

"First stage!"

In mid-air, he swelled up with a fierce roar, his shirt ripped into pieces and flew away, freeing him from the hold of the solid Bravery.

A hideous dark green hand as big as a basin clawed at Palosa’s face.

Palosa didn’t expect his strike to not be effective toward Garen. Having the ability to take his strike at a weak point with no injury, this opponent is more accomplished in Body Hardening Technique than he thought.

Seeing Garen charging toward him like a lightning, his strength, speed, and momentum all rolled into one giant, unavoidable wave, he could only take the hit.

Thud!

Garen was hit by a whip kick on his side, his blackened torso shot into a pile of rocks.

As he was using his power, the solid Bravery appeared out of thin air, suppressing his follow-up moves. He couldn’t even finish his moves before being blasted into the rock pile, crushing an uncountable number of rocks.

"Damn it, again!" Furious, Garen flipped himself back up and prepared to unleash his attacks before seeing a blur.

Thud thud thud!

A continuous string of strikes hit at the exact same spot on his chest.

Even with his first stage transformation, Garen felt his body hurt from the inside. He was being drilled further into the rock pile.

Palosa’s face glowed with a slight blush, his face contorting weirdly, slowly turning into the face on his Bravery.

"So disappointing! White Cloud Gate Master Garen, how dare you speak with such extravagance with that puny strength of yours! I am so sad on behalf of your parents and siblings. No one forced you to come, yet you seek death by yourself!"

He kept on striking Garen casually, but with every strike, they had brought Garen numbness. Including the suppression from his Bravery, he was not able to move at all.

Even with the first stage transformation and its heightened defense and power surge, Garen still wasn’t able to curb the incoming attacks. He could only take the hits.

As if a different person, Palosa was harsh and mean, nothing like the kind old man that he was.

Garen felt unusually smothered. Every time when he tried to attack, the Bravery would interrupt him, causing him to be hit. And the cycle repeats.

However, with every attack, Palosa would need to endure Garen’s incredible Counter Shockwave, stunning him just by a little. He wasn’t hurt, but the recoil was still annoying, to say the least.

Powerful strikes keep shaking up Garen’s insides. Even though Body Hardening Technique has absorbed most of the blows, he was still nauseated with the constant vibration quivering throughout his body, slowing his attacks further.

"Hit me back!" Palosa’s face darkened.

Both of them were still in the rock pile, their movements and strikes sputtering gravels at every direction. Their Bravery clashed with each other, causing the living beings nearby to stay away, even the worms in the pool congregated at the far end of the pool.

"You’re as weak as a baby, are you sure you didn’t come all the way here to be beaten up? I don’t get how you managed to defeat Duskdune Shura, did you spring a surprise attack on him while he’s not ready? Or did you challenge him when he’s hurt? Weaklings will always be weaklings, they would never be ready for anything." Palosa sneered.

"You…" Thud!

Garen had barely replied before he was rudely interrupted, his words buried with the palm strike he got hit with. Crushed sand were blown into his eyes, forcing him to close them.

"Too weak!" Palosa struck him with his right palm.

Garen flew sideways yet again with the hit, falling into the woods nearby.

"Why are you even alive, being such a weakling!" Palosa’s moved his arms in a circular motion, the darkening of his face getting more obvious as time goes by.

A sharp bird sound appeared out of nowhere. It’s like a hawk’s call, but at the same time similar to the cry of a crane.

Palosa blitzed forward, charging into the woods where Garen fell.

One following the other, the sound of their fist fight echoed through the woods like muted thunder.

Their audience chased after them into the woods, and saw Garen being pressed to defend against the attacks while retreating deeper into the forest.

"Skylark Finger Pierce!"

Palosa’s palms glowed white, he charged toward Garen, aiming at his throat, leaving two white flashes in his trail.

"Final attack, you deserved to die if you can’t block it!" Palosa’s face had already warped into cruelty, his index fingers jabbing forward.

Before anything else could happen, Garen’s eyes opened suddenly.

"Red Jade · Ten Thousand Mammoth Retrograde!"

His hands flared a bright scarlet to face the incoming piercing finger attack.

The fists and fingers connected.

Boom!

A liquid state Bravery broke through the suppression, forming a humongous white elephant at least a dozen meters tall behind Garen.

The elephant raised its front hooves and trumpeted. Its raised hooves correlated with Garen’s arm, projecting a giant stone pillar and falling toward Palosa.

The ground rumbled with a boom.

Palosa grunted, and flew backward, crushing two trees as thick as a treehugger’s arm length.

Leaves rained down by the pile.

Garen’s shirt has disappeared, leaving him bare-chested in the woods. His body had grown even more, making him as tall as two meters and a half, not even the fiercest hunters in the jungle would dare to come near.

"This is my final form." Garen’s calmed down, looking between the trees not far away. "Unfortunately, this world is no longer yours to dominate…"

Boom!

His figure disappeared in an instant and reappeared in front of Palosa almost immediately.

"Explosion of Heavenly Spirits*!" Garen roared and flexed, pumping his bulging arms even more, before he clawed at Palosa with an unmatched ferocity.

Slam!

Phwoosh!

A shockwave pulsed outward centering the two, fallen leaves showered them, surrounding them. It was nearly impossible to get a clear glimpse of the situation aside from gauging from the tremor.

Several trees nearby fell with crackles. These were the trees that were hit in the shockwave, countless branches poured down, causing the poisonous insects to flee their falling homes.

A dozen seconds later, only after the leaves had stopped falling that the others who were spectating the fight were able to see what happened clearly.

Garen’s hands clawed at Palosa’s face, but was stopped and constricted by Palosa’s arms.

Both the fighters froze in place. A black human-like Bravery and a white mammoth Bravery tugged at each other, trying to gain an upper hand against the other.

A drop of blood trailed down Palosa’s brow bone.

"Palosa… is hurt!"

Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate Master and the others felt a chill run up their spines.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. That’s his heeeeaaaaddd!

2. 天罡 can refer to heavenly spirits or any specific stars in Taoist astrology, 霸烈 lit. domineering / tyrannous / brutal split.

Chapter 177: Age of the Pinnacle 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Chi!!!!

Garen’s arm took a quick turn, and his elbow went straight for Palosa’s temples. His elbows were like sharp tips, stabbing Palosa’s temples from both left and right.

Boom!

Palosa’s upper body blocked the attacks, but his lower body was still kicked, and his body flew backwards from the impact. Before he could react, he saw a black shadow zoom past him and his lower abdomen was hit by invisible punches. These were the signs of high speed punching.

Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!

The both of them continued to exchange blows in the woods, every time their arms met, Palosa’s body would shake, the explosive strength of his opponent continuously hit him on the body, and he could feel his arms going numb. Blow after blow of terrifying attacks and explosive shock was like a massive hammer, hammering down on him.

For a moment, Palosa’s attention faltered, and his waist was hit by a silent but deadly palm technique.

With a loud bang, his whole body flew towards the left side.

Garen caught up in a few quick steps, swung his hand downwards to hit Palosa, but was blocked by Palosa’s arms. At the same time, Palosa was hit by an unavoidable side whipping leg.

Pow!

The side whip leg slashed across Palosa’s right shoulder.

In the woods, the crowd could only see the duo fighting, like two shadows floating about, one black one white, crisscrossing.

Suddenly, the white shadow was hit and sent flying, taking down a few trees on its way, then the black shadow quickly caught up and continued to mess with it.

On the ground, and in the trees, there would occasionally be craters or holes leftover.

With a loud rumble, Palosa was again hit back over ten plus steps. He could no longer hold it in anymore, and started puking blood.

Garen was expressionless, he gestured his arms in a circular motion, and once more positioned himself into the stance for Explosion of Heavenly Spirit.

"Ten Thousand Mammoths Retrograde!!!"

Garen suddenly disappeared from where he stood, and appeared again right in front of Palosa, with both his palms aiming at his abdomen.

In this split second, all the muscles on his body started moving like little rats under his skin, forming a way towards his palms.

White Cloud Gate’s Four Major Forms’ combined explosive strengths were all focused in this one attack, paired with the second Dan’s powers, they all increased the effectiveness of the Explosion of Heavenly Spirit.

With this particular attack, Garen was reaching a whole new level in his abilities and strength.

This was the first time putting all of his strength into one single blow, before this he had never encountered an opponent worthy of such potency, today he finally had the chance to do so.

The force of his two palms were so great, that a strong wind formed as they got closer to Palosa’s abdomen. Before they even reached Palosa’s abdomen, Palosa’s skin was already slightly pressed down by the wind and force.

Palosa looked at Garen calmly, a stream of blood dripped off his chin along his face.

A black air seemed to slowly appear along with the stream of blood.

"You haven’t reached your limit yet," Palosa pushed both his arms forward.

Boom!!

A weird collision sound exploded from between their palms.

Palosa’s body first stumbled forward, then flew backwards into the direction of some green plants behind him, drawing a flat line of crushed greens as he fell onto them.

The forest was silent once more.

Palosa coughed furiously, the black air on his face disappeared completely, only his skin was showing some weird sickening purple red.

"Cough, cough, I never knew that you could beat me out of my demonic status," The air around him was no longer of a black humanoid, but white fog again.

"Back to normal now?" Garen’s arms returned to their normal shape, as he looked at the panting and obviously tired Palosa, he too took some deep breaths: this was the first time he had ever felt tired.

Ever since he started practicing secret martial arts, he had been continuously increasing his body’s strength and stamina, his recovery abilities have always been way beyond mortals. Yet this time, with the continuous use of all his energy blow after blow, he actually felt tired for once.

The both of them, one sat and the other stood facing each other, stopped fighting, giving each other and themselves time to regain their energies.

"What a pity," Palosa looked at Garen with sympathy,"a pity that you walked down this path, this is a path with no future."

Seeing how Garen didn’t seem to understand his statement, he smiled.

"Ever since I’ve started practicing White Bird Fist, I’ve fought thousands of battles, and not once have I lost. Yet since a year ago, I started noticing that the Fist was starting to act against me. Eventually, it sent me into a demonic state. Who knew that I would be struck awake by you."

"Acted against you?" Garen was dumbfounded.

"Many many years ago, I learned of the side effects of the Assassination Fist Techniques, so I chose to hide in the mountains in hopes of fighting and removing the side effect that gave me a constant intent to kill. However in the end the demons got better of me," Palosa’s face looked incredibly serious,"now I maybe injured, but thanks to you, I am fully awake."

He stood up from the ground and stretched his body, loud cracking sounds were made as he did so.

"Be careful now, this is my true form!" Palosa’s body shrank for a bit, then suddenly expanded. From a mere 160cm tall little old man, Palosa suddenly grew into a two meter tall buff fighter.

His muscles and bones made weird cracking noises, his wrinkled skin also tightened up, becoming smooth and young.

"Higher Form Hand!"

Palosa raised his right arm, and casually swung it along a nearby tree. His nails were like five sharp swords, easily etching deep marks into the tree bark.

"The pinnacle of Body Hardening Technique?" Garen squinted his eyes.

"No, this is a secret technique: 99 Acute Airholes," Palosa seemed to have completely recovered into his normal form, and smiled,"unlike Body Hardening Technique, this secret technique saves a copy of one’s pinnacle body form, and seals it away. When needed, it can project that form onto the user’s body, ensuring that the user would have access to his own pinnacle anytime he wants."

Palosa had suddenly became a long white haired young man, looking at Garen and talking smoothly without pause.

"I self made 178 different types of secret techniques, each one of them are individually unique and each took years of research and perfecting to complete. 99 Acute Airholes, ranks number 67 out of them all."

The air and aura around him turned completely white, but unlike other fighters, his white aura made people around him feel peaceful.

"I’m sorry to have disappointed you earlier," Palosa’s face turned serious,"your strength far exceeds the world of Fist Techniques, one could even regard you as the undisputed Ruler of All Fists! This path of pure strength and energy of yours is a first amongst the many fighters I’ve encountered in my life."

"Cut the crap, let’s do this," Garen placed himself into the stance of Explosion of Heavenly Spirit. This was a technique he had acquired from a trade with the Tenth Loop, its side effects were nothing to him, its powers however, were formidable.

Just that he had not expect to be forced to use it by Palosa’s demonic form.

"You’re right," Palosa smiled, and turned into a white shadow.

Garen turned into a black shadow at the same time.

The both of them dashed into each other with a loud blast.

This was unlike anything before!!

The both of them exchanged blows, neither was giving the other any openings, each hit was a solid and serious one. Muscle on muscle, fist on fist, sounded like metal hitting metal.

"Three Blows Arm Technique!" both of Palosa’s arms took a quick turn and suddenly became three times of their original size, their speeds increased rapidly too as they headed straight downwards for Garen’s shoulders.

A sharp shrill tore through the sky, a white air wave appeared behind Palosa’s arms, like two silk straps were flying towards Garen’s shoulders.

This is the effect of air being torn through by excessive amount of speed.

Palosa’s eyes glowed with anticipation, Three Blows Arm Technique was the last of his 178 Secret Techniques. With his current pinnacle status combined with this secret technique, he once sliced a master of Body Hardening Technique in half.

This was a multiplication of his current strength by the factor of 3, this level of terrifying speed far exceeded the limits of the human body, instead it reached an inhuman level. Yet amongst all of his secret techniques, this was considered one of the most mundane ones.

"Let me see, how will you defend against this?" Palosa glared at Garen.

The both of them were dangerously close to each other, the Three Blows Arms was about to hit Garen in a split second. The shrill in the air caused by the two white waves of air caused Garen’s ears to totally lose their hearing.

He squinted his eyes, to avoid the massive air pressure from causing a him to lose his sight too.

As a fellow human at the limit of human physique, Garen knew the threat of such an attack. In a split second, a dozen different techniques crossed his head, but his body instinctively positioned into a specific stance welcoming the attack.

Whoooosh

The powerful White Mammoth Aura gathered around his body, and bellowed with its trunk, then it charged towards Palosa’s Three Blows Arms.

"Ten Thousand Mammoth Trample!!" this was one of three major techniques that Garen invented out of mixing many others. Just like Ten Thousand Mammoth Retrograde, it was based off the Mammoth secret techniques combined with other techniques like the Golden Statue Technique, to become an incredibly powerful standalone still.

Clang!

Looking from far away, one would be able to see two white lines violently striking Garen’s shoulders.

The both of their faces glowed a slight red, the explosive energy brought with it a violent shock and vibration, these were vibrations that neither of them were able to control so both of them immediately sustained internal injuries at the same time.

Palosa’s joints made the weird cracking noise again, but this time it sounded like trouble.

Garen’s shoulders on the other hand were left with two visible wounds, except that there wasn’t any blood, and the wounds seemed to close up as soon as they opened up.

At the same time, the both of backed away from each other.

"Secret Technique, Sealing Sun Arm!" A small cube suddenly appeared under the skin of Palosa’s abdomen, like he had installed a wooden cube under his skin.

The cube moved from his abdomen upwards to his chest, then it disappeared.

What was weird, was that Palosa’s originally swollen shoulders and broken bones, they were instantaneously healed, and his skin returned to its original unscathed state.

Garen sucked up the pain from his shoulders, as he watched Palosa heal himself in front of him. At this moment he realized how truly terrifying Palosa’s self made 178 Secret Techniques were.

Palosa wasn’t even a pinnacle practitioner of the Body Hardening Technique, and yet he could achieve such frightening results with his own abilities.

"I haven’t felt this pumped in a long while! Come, let’s do it again!" Palosa laughed and dashed towards Garen again with another strike of Three Blows Arm Technique.

At this moment, the white shirt man and Cynthia arrived to witness this scene.

The effects of Palosa’s Secret Techniques left everyone speechless.

"Grandfather Palosa’s 99 Acute Airholes can save the body of his absolute pinnacle state, and the most terrifying ability isn’t even that," the white shirt man and the leader of the Southern Heavenly Fist Gate said softly.

"This is already insane!" King of Fist Leo felt his hair stand on their edges as he watched this inhuman fight. The two monsters kept clashing into each other like giant beasts wrestling.

What was different was that Garen had metal-like skin while Palosa had his 178 Secret Techniques!

Heavenly Fist Gate’s Gate Master said,"We never knew that this was Palosa Grandfather’s true state. Who knew that the legendary Assasination Fist Technique could affect the mentality of the user too. No wonder all these years our grandfather forbade us from seeing him."

"You haven’t said what the most terrifying ability he possesses?" Cynthia’s eyes were fixed on the battlefield, while she spoke.

This was also what Jack and King of Fist Leo wanted to know.

Chapter 178: Age of the Pinnacle 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"The most terrifying part of 99 Acute Airholes is when it is used alongside his 10th Secret Technique, and that is the most famous Secret Technique of them all: 99 Regressions!" The Heavenly Fist Gate Master said with a deep voice,"that technique is the reason why Grandfather Palosa is undefeated and unmatched across the board."

"99 Regressions?" King of Fist Leo’s face fell,"Do you mean the legendary esoteric?!"

The Gate Master nodded proudly.

"That is the legendary esoteric! 99 Lives!!"

Rumble!!

It was at this moment, the both of them collided against each other again.

Their hands were continuously striking and slashing each other. Garen made a low ‘hmph’ and took a few steps back, the wounds on his shoulders wouldn’t close up anymore now, and were bleeding profusely.

Palosa’s shoulders were cracked beyond recognition as well, his arms hung without life on his body.

"Secret Technique, Sealing Sun Arm!" the small cube appeared under his skin again.

"Still trying to cure yourself?!"

Garen made low grunt and dashed towards him, his arm formed into a claw ready to gnash.

At this point, despite the fact that his shoulders were injured, which would in turn affect his speed, but he still had a solid 80% of his usual speed. His claw glowed a slight red and released some heat around it.

Palosa smiled at sight of this, the cube under his skin sped up magically until it disappeared under his chest. When it did, his chest recovered to a state like it had never been injured before, with two loud sounds he grabbed Garen’s claw in two moves.

The two of them moved backwards rapidly.

A weird dark energy moved from Palosa’s body into Garen’s, compared to the demonic Palosa earlier, this was much stronger and was headed straight for Garen’s heart.

"I have met many pinnacle practitioners of Body Hardening Technique, but you are definitely the strongest I have ever met. You are able to not just face my three techniques built based on the White Bird Fist, but still stay standing, ready to fight. I take back my words earlier," Palosa’s calm voice seemed to drill into Garen’s ears,"it is actually possible now that you defeated Duskdune Shura."

Palosa lifted his knee and kneed Garen in the abdomen, evading his attack. The both of them backed away from each other.

"It ends here!" Palosa’s face was suddenly covered in pale white jade colour.

"White Bird, Unrivaled Skyfall!"

The white aura around him suddenly concentrated into a form and created a massive white crane, it’s beak sharper than the sharpest swords and its claws, stacked on top of each other, were lifted up and slashed downwards.

The sharp beak pecked on Garen like an awl.

The same threatening aura appeared again, crushing Garen under its intimidating weight, causing his bones to vibrate slightly.

"You think I wouldn’t be able to fight back like this? Garen’s face suddenly turned sly, his arms expanded in a wide motion.

"Ten Thousand Mammoth Sky Encirclement!!!!!"

He put both his palms together like he was about to clamp onto the beak of the crane. As his palms traveled rapidly through the air, the already filled with poison arms were now forming a lot of friction against the air and was suddenly on fire!

Garen’s palms drew a red line as they both met in a prayer-like gesture.

At this moment, both of their abilities met each other. The forest fell silent once more.

The two large auras collided with each other and blurred everything around them. No living organism could tell for sure what was going on in there.

After a few seconds, both auras retreated away from each other and stood facing each other with a few meters of distance in between.

Palosa’s palms were charred black like they had been burned and he was sweating profusely like he had just expended all of his energy in his last attack. Especially his chest, it seemed to sank in the middle, obviously his ribs were broken and he was heavily injured.

He stared at Garen who stood across him.

Garen didn’t move from his spot, just that there was now a small cut on the middle of his chest and a small stream of blood was pouring out of it. From where he stood, there was a half circle line burned into the ground, the frightening after effect of his Ten Thousand Mammoth Sky Encirclement.

"It is over," Garen looked at Palosa,"you’ve taken a direct hit from my Ten Thousand Mammoth Sky Encirclement, that paired with the hot poison….." This was nothing like the time Garen defeated Duskdune Shura, this particular strike was at least twice as powerful as that one. Even if Palosa was stronger than Duskdune Shura, he could not possibly survive a direct hit.

He squinted his eyes and looked at Palosa.

The small cube popped up underneath Palosa’s chest again!

"Secret Technique: 99 Regressions!"

Palosa’s face was calm, the cube dissolved into countless beams that shot across his nerves to every part of his body.

After a series of weird bone cracks and muscle cracks, Palosa recovered from all his injuries, like had never been hit at all!

"My 99 Regressions, paired with 99 Acute Airholes, is the ultimate ability invented from the White Bird Fist Technique. I can heal myself 99 times within a hundred days from any injury."

Palosa tore off whatever broken fabric was left on his top, leaving on only his bottom long pants.

"99 Regressions…." Garen’s face was expressionless, but his heart was stirring. This kind of insane secret technique can only be invented by someone as good as Palosa.

"I’ll see how many times you can recover then!" Garen’s heart was set on defeating Palosa, he pushed from his feet and dashed towards Palosa.

Boom, boom, boom!

The sounds of collision continued. White Bird Aura and the Giant Mammoth Aura twist and turned over each other. The White Bird flew up and crashed down on the Giant Mammoth over and over again, while the Giant Mammoth whipped the White Bird with its trunk.

The two frighteningly large auras continuously exchanged blows.

"Ten Thousand Mammoth Sky Encirclement!!!" Garen bellowed, his palms once against on fire, colliding again with Palosa’s Unrivaled Skyfall.

Palosa jumped away and when he landed, he had recovered from his injuries.

"Again!!" Garen jumped towards Palosa aggressively.

The onlookers watched as the both of them repeatedly fought each other with all their might. As they continued to fight, Palosa was actually able to continuously recover from all his injuries, everywhere he was hit, he would heal within ten seconds.

With the combined use of Sealing Sun Arm and 99 Regressions, Palosa looked like he was never injured from beginning to end. His aura was as fresh as it gets, unaffected at all by the constant attacks.

Whereas for Garen, he was getting bloodied from the continuous pecking by the White Bird Fist. His eyes were bloodshot, but he didn’t seem to know anything about feeling tired, and just kept throwing blow after blow of his most powerful attack: Ten Thousand Mammoth Sky Encirclement!

The Ten Thousand Mammoth Sky Encirclement was delivered with Fiery Claws and each time it hit Palosa, it would leave him heavily injured. Yet every single time Palosa would recover completely from it, like the attack meant nothing.

One, twice, four times….ten times….twenty times! Garen’s body started wearing out, but he still stood straight like a pencil, aggressively attacking his opponent.

Finally, not sure after how long, the forest was silent once more.

King of First Leo, Cynthia and Jack clenched their jaws, their faces a mixed expression as they stared at Garen. Like them, the Gate Master too was looking at Garen with respect.

"There’s no point to continue fighting," Palosa stood silently by the side of a few collapsed trees.

All the trees in a ten meter radius around them were either torn in half or completely collapsed, some were even on fire due to Garen’s Fiery Claws.

The forest seemed to have become a plateau.

Streams of blood flowed down Garen’s chin, arms, legs.

He panted and gasped for air, his eyes were still glowing red, staring at Palosa with resentment. Garen’s shoulders, waist, back and chest were filled with wounds, lines of lines of bright red cuts filled his entire upper body.

"99 Regressions!" Garen panted,"there really...isn’t any point on fighting anymore."

Surely by now, they were both violently aware of each other’s limits and abilities.

99 Regressions paired with Sealing Sun Arm sure is a terrifying combo, but that’s an ability made for the Palosa at his peak. The Palosa now, if he continued using the same techniques, would put such a strong burden on his body that he would not die from his injuries but instead from a total lack of energy. After all, he wasn’t the same Palosa as he was when he was younger.

As for Garen, using Ten Thousand Mammoth Sky Encirclement was also a great burden on his body. After using it so many times, he had exhausted all of his energy, and could faint anytime soon.

But he knew he cannot be defeated like this!

Too much depended on him, as he was the main foundation holding up White Cloud Gate. If he falls, not only will White Cloud Gate fall, so will his family and friends, everyone will disappear like a house of cards.

White Cloud Gate and his family have been able to stay safe all these years because of the intimidation of his strength. If he falls, not only will his enemies seize the opportunity to strike, but so will the people who surrendered to him purely because of his strength betray him and his family.

At this point, both them knew very well that if they continued, they would both end up dead. Perhaps Garen would die first, but Palosa would follow after very soon too.

"I lost," Palosa laughed, his body shrinking back to his real age, turning back into the small old man he was earlier. His face now was so pale it was terrifying,"I used 99 Acute Airholes to retain my prime till now, but I never expected you to be able to force me to use 99 Regressions more than ten times."

Realistically, the both of them were almost equal in strength, just that Garen was at a disadvantage due to Palosa’s Secret Techniques.

"You didn’t lose," Garen said coldly, and stood up, his body shook for a second, and all his wounds instantly opened and shut with a large spout of blood.

He reached out his hand towards Leo.

Leo threw over a black cloak to Garen, which he used to instantly cover up himself.

"Let’s go, we’ve achieved our objective for this time," Garen turned around and took big steps away, as if he was never injured before,"next time, next time I will defeat you!"

King of Fist Leo was the first to catch up to Garen, followed by Cynthia and Jack.

"A year ago, a man named Sylphalan showed up here once. We ended our battle with heavy injuries on both sides. If you meet this man, be careful," Palosa’s yelled from behind him.

"Sylphalan…." Garen stopped in his steps for a moment, then he continued walking.

Chapter 179: Closer 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A year ago, Sylphalan was here, and he fought with Palosa.

A year ago, Palosa sealed himself away as he fell into his demonic tendencies.

Garen suddenly understood the correlation.

The reason why Sylphalan showed up coincidentally in Galantia and Eliza Province, was because he was motivated by some other objective. Perhaps that objective was to seek Palosa out for battle.

Since the White Bird now said that the both of them sustained heavy injuries from the fight, that means Sylphalan should still be recovering from his injuries, unless he has some sort of special recovery method.

Whereas for Palosa, his injuries were mostly mental, especially since he would later fall into his demonic form. Sylphalan must have sustained some bad injuries as well.

On the way out from the big waterfall, Garen kept thinking of that possibility.

As the four of them walked back, nobody spoke.

Garen’s body was covered from head to toe in the black cloak, nobody, not even the other three could tell how injured he was.

"Gate Master Garen, are you alright?" King of Fist Leo frowned and aksed.

"Not too good not too bad either, I’ll be fine," Garen looked at him briefly, and answered.

"That’s good," Leo’s face relaxed,"Since we’ve achieved our objective in this journey, what shall we do next?"

Garen stopped in his steps,"We’ll talk about that once we get back to Galantia. This fight with Palosa made me realize some very important things, but first I need to recover. The rest of the things just play by ear, if you hear anything about Black Mark Association you are to inform me immediately."

"Yessir,"

Leo nodded.

As Cynthia and Jack heard Garen say that his injuries weren’t too serious, they were relieved. Now their fates were tied to Garen’s, if Garen fell, they wouldn’t be spared from the ensuing consequences either.

"I’ve arranged a carriage near the city, I’ll lead the way once we’re out of here," Cynthia said.

"Alright,"

Garen didn’t want to say anything else, so he just agreed.

While he might have told the others that he wasn’t badly injured, but he knew himself that his status right now was not your average injury.

When fighting with Palosa, the true killing force isn’t sheer strength or overwhelming force. Instead, it is the small but potent beak attacks. Where the beak bit Garen, he could not heal completely, the only reason why they stopped bleeding was because of his muscle expansions covering the wounds.

Aside from this, the beak attacks were unlike any other pierces. The moment the dark energy pierced his skin, a large part around it went numb, and he couldn’t even feel if he was bleeding.

"3 spots on my abdomen, 12 on my back, 8 on my limbs….out of those 5 are bleeding internally, 3 are just surface cuts, the rest are completely numb."

Garen checked his own body as he walked. Under his Attribute Pane, his vitality had dropped a staggering 5 points. Obviously due to the overwhelming injury, even his Body Hardening Technique’s efficiency was lowered.

"And then there’s my innards, all major organs seemed to have moved in different directions, my heart is slightly cracked, which means my recovery abilities are suppressed as well. I wonder what secret techniques Palosa used to do that."

Garen looked at his palm under the cloak, it was pale, terrifyingly pale.

"Let’s try and see if there’s any effect if I use the attribute points,"

He tried to expense his unused potential points into the vitality section.

Disappointingly to no effect. His vitality went blur for a second, then it returned to the original amount, his body didn’t change the slightest.

"Looks like this time I will have to slowly recover," he frowned,"an injury like this has surpressed my recovery abilities, even if it doesn’t get worst I will still need a whole month to fully recover."

His issue with Behemoth’s Gate wasn’t even settled yet, but for now he could only return home to recover.

Garen’s fought a lot of opponents before, and has always won right out with everyone. He thought that once he reached this level, he would never end up in a horrible condition like so anymore, but little did he expect himself to be reduced to this after a simple exchange with Palosa.

Sylphalan, Palosa, even though he was still slighter weaker than them, but on the bright side it meant that he had stepped into the highest level of fighters.

Now whenever someone were to bring him up in a conversation, they would compare him to the two of them as equals, sometimes even as superior.

As he recalled Palosa’s fighting style, Garen continued to shake slightly, as he tried to fix his internal injuries.

***************************

Ten days later…

The fight between White Cloud Gate’s Gate Master and White Bird Fist’s Palosa, ended without anyone knowing about it.

But after a few days, news of it had spread throughout the entire southern martial arts world.

The fact that the both of them ended it in a draw was beyond everyone’s wildest expectations. Garen, as a new age Master of Combat, was able to actually fight the great Fist Master to a draw, was unbelievable for most. Overnight, the news spread via telegram to every corner of the martial arts world.

Garen’s position as a regional leader was also cemented by this battle’s outcome. White Cloud Gate’s Territory of Galantia became a place of attention for every sect.

As for White Cloud Gate’s ranking, it rose up to stand equal with the Southern Holy Fist Gate and the Celestial Circle Gate.

As for the Black Mark Association and Crimson Sand Sword Gate:

Black Mark association was discussing surrender and possible merger of elements with White Cloud Gate, especially since amongst their three King of Fists, one betrayed the sect, one was heavily injured and the remaining one was no longer able to hold the entire organisation up by himself. Black Mark association was alive by name, but dead in reality.

Crimson Sand Sword Gate disappeared into the shadows since the day the Hunter Killer Squad fought Garen. In an instance they disappeared from public eye and sold most of their assets to nearby sects like White Cloud Gate or the Celestial Circle Gate.

The entire southside of the Confederation was now split between three major sects.

Namely they were: Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate, Celestial Circle Gate and White Cloud Gate. Amongst the three, White Cloud Gate was the weakest, they had zero plans to expand beyond Galantia. All they were interested in was to continue consolidating their power in Galantia and they even turned away ex-members of the Black Mark Association trying to join them.

Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate expanded aggressively, they absorbed many small sects and formed their own alliance.

Celestial Circle Gate also started to consolidate their power after Garen fought Palosa, rumors even tell of a possibility that Andrela had left self-confinement.

***************************

Galantia, Hubo City.

In a white manor surrounded by various maple trees.

Outside the manor, in the maplewood forest.

Two young men sat by a stone table playing Go.

Maple leaves would occasionally fall on the stone table, along with what looked like dandelion seeds, both of which would be expertly flung away by the duo each time they fell.

One of the men was buff and tall, his body wrapped all over with black bandage. The other one was handsome, with black hair that fell on his shoulders, and an eye patch that covered one of his eyes.

The setup on the table was filled with black pieces. Instead of white and black to distinguish the factions, they were differentiated by squared and circular ones. The stronger buffer man’s was playing the squared pieces while the one-eyed man was playing the circular pieces.

"I heard you challenged Palosa, I came as soon as I left my self-confinement. Who knew that even someone with your abilities would end up in a state like this," the one-eyed man was Andrela who had just rushed from Celestial Circle Gate. He donned a long sleeve and long pants with a black robe that had constellations etched in beautiful silver thread on the end of the sleeves.

"If you don’t believe it then you’re always welcomed to go try," Garen was covered in black bandage, wearing only black long pants and boots. He sat on the stool with his back straight and his eyes slightly squinting, still looking intimidating in this state. His hair was short now, and his right arm was still being supported by a wooden board.

"I can’t even defeat you, if I go wouldn’t I just be asking for death?" Andrela laughed,"But Palosa has always been someone I wish to overtake one day. Now there’s you too. What if I kill you now with my sword? Would that earn me the title of Number One Combat Master in the Southern World?"

"Looks like this self-confinement session of yours was really rewarding," Garen couldn’t help but laugh, as he lifted up his hand and placed a piece onto the playing field,"sadly, I’ve killed you already."

The game was set, Andrela’s circular pieces were all surrounded by Garen’s square pieces, he only had one piece left to place, and one spot for him to do so. Once he does, he would seal his own fate.

"The medicine you gave me was really good," Garen moved his body about,"I can already feel the effects, the spots where the pus infected have also stopped worsening. Thank you so much."

Ever since the day he got back, his body’s only been getting worst. Every spot that was hit by Palosa’s Unrivalled Skyfall ability was infected by pus. Had it not been for the rare medicine, he wouldn’t have been able to stop it at all.

But that’s as much progress as he was able to make, he simply couldn’t recover.

In over ten days, he only recovered some parts of his organs, but his energy and abilities were still deterred.

"Pair it up with edible medication, you should be able to completely rid yourself of the infections." Andrela unwillingly let go of the chesspiece on his hand,"consider that I’ve lost. Looks like other than being good at martial arts, you’re a monster even at Go."

He stood up and revealed a small red medicine bottle from his sleeve, then he threw it at Garen,"this is a special medicine prepared for me by Celestial Circle Gate members, it should have some effect. You seem to have a guest, I shall go practice my swordsmanship, if you need anything you can find me at our usual spot."

With the sound of loud wind, Andrela disappeared from where he stood, only a few maple leaves were left in his wake.

Garen sat on the bench, this rock bench had obvious eastern influences, as it was custom made by a skilled craftsman based on Garen’s memory. It was perhaps a small memento to remind him of his origins from Earth.

He kept the pieces back into the box one by one, and left the box on the table. He picked up the red medicine bottle, gave it a curious look and put it straight into his pocket.

The maplewood forest was a bright red everywhere, even the floors were filled with red leaves like a carpet.

As he watched Andrela leave, Garen felt a sense of gratefulness.

Andrela had grown stronger again, not just a small bit, but by a large margin compared to the first time they met. No wonder he was so confident and wanted to challenge Garen. What used to be a big feat like Blink was now being casted by him like an everyday trick.

Garen took a wild guess, and estimated that Andrela’s abilities were now very close to Crimson Sand Sword Gate’s evil genius Lord Clark, but what other secret techniques he hid under that sleeve, nobody knew.

Beyond the maplewood forest, light footsteps could be heard.

"Gate Master, I’ve brought the guest," Jack’s voice could be heard as well.

"Come over then," Garen replied peacefully.

Chapter 180: Closer 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Jack was clothed in a full set of black robes while he was followed by three others.

Two out of the three were people familiar with Garen, they were two King of Fists of the Black Mark Association, Ankh and Manila. Neither of them were wearing their Black Mark Association uniforms anymore, instead they both donned a white cloak contrasting a pair of black boxing globes with silver linings.

As for the other one, it was White Cloud Gate’s Corrine.

The two King of Fists stood in attention, and greeted Garen respectfully.

"Black Mark Association’s surrender is complete. From today onwards, we are King of Fists serving White Cloud Gate. Gate Master Garen, you possess great knowledge and great skill in martial arts, we dare not defy you; however, we have one request: please don’t put us in the same team as that traitor Leo!" Manila said calmly.

Garen turned around to face the group.

"Considering the conflict putting you all together might raise, I will be wary to not put you two and Leo in one group. You will each lead your own groups respectively, with your own respective names. In fact, you can just use your old names from your Black Mark Association days. Black Group and Mark Group was it?"

"Yes sir, that will be great."

Garen nodded in agreement.

"Leo will also set up his own group called the Lightning Group. Jack and Corrine, you will both lead the rest and form a group called Cloud Group in charge of gathering intelligence. Then there’s another group, that I will manage myself."

In a few simple sentences, Garen summarized and made order out of the complicated structure of White Cloud Gate.

In total there would be five groups, three of the masters of combats will lead three of their own groups, then there will be a fourth group made out of White Cloud Gate’s original followers. The remainder will be made out of freelancers and fighters from various groups in Galantia, these will form a group and be led by Garen himself.

This arrangement provided a clear distinction between the major powers within White Cloud Gate. Amongst all of them, the ones that were most loyal to Garen were Leo and the ones from the original body of White Cloud Gate. As for the rest, they were only submissive for now because they had been defeated.

However during such times, Garen could use all the help he could get, so the more power the better.

"Anything interesting lately?" Garen looked at Corrine.

Corrine nodded,"News from Cynthia, the first is about Mr. Su Lin and Celine. The two of them were collecting rare materials until they were caught in some conflict happening by the border. We still don’t know what’s their situation right now."

"Conflict?" Garen frowned,"Conflict related to the borders?"

"Only two states in the borders, the Confederation has already sent its army that way. Soon it will be dissolved," Corrine nodded,"then there’s a second piece of news: A cruise ship carrying Confederation students was boarded by members of the Weisman navy, they’re holding the passengers hostage and have already killed 13 students. Right now there are demonstrations all over the major cities condemning the Weisman government’s inhumane actions…."

"Please get straight to the point," Garen cut her short.

"Oh, the Confederation and Weisman have dispatched their respective fleets, a big fight’s is going to break out," Corrine summarized,"this came from Mr. Sulin and little sister."

Garen noticed that Corrine used ‘immediately’ instead of ‘is going to’ instead of ‘possibly’, which meant that Corrine was 100% sure about it.

"Su Lin’s father should have his own arrangements in mind for a situation like this. Manila, please make trip to the western border and see if they need any help while gathering any information you can about the country behind these conflicts."

"Alright," Manila nodded, he softly squeezed Ankh’s hand and turned around to leave.

Now all of Black Mark Association’s power was divided into three parts, one was the ‘Mark Group’ led by Manila. All of these groups were disciplined and well organised individually, collectively they were the elites of the Black Mark Association.

If it wasn’t for the Golden Hoop’s influence combined with Garen’s sheer power, the Black Mark Association would not have gone down so easily.

However, with the way things are now, if they did not surrender to Garen’s side, they would only be met with certain death should he decide to pursue revenge for what they did to him back then.

Manila and Ankh were sure about one thing, if Garen were to sent them to their deaths on some one way mission, they will not hesitate to run away. Lucky for them, Garen seemed to treat everyone the same, like there had been no conflict between them to begin with, maybe even nicer than before.

Garen watched as Manila left.

Each of Black Mark Association’s groups consisted of at least a few hundred, maybe even a few thousand fighters. On top of that, there was their wide real estate portfolio, intelligence gathering bodies, mercenaries, freelance fighters and even assassins etc.

Garen didn’t need to know too much of the details, as long as they served him with their abilities and influence, it was enough. There was still the support of the Golden Hoop, White Cloud Gate and Leo all watching his back and ready to serve at a moment’s notice.

"Ankh, once you’re done with moving your people you can begin taking over Galantia’s security. Can you assign guards for key influential people in the city?"

Ankh nodded, and turned to leave as well.

Corrine and Jack were left, awaiting Garen’s orders.

"Jack, what’s the situation like now with Leo? Have they found Duskdune Shura’s remaining Royal Generals?" Garen turned his gaze to Jack now.

Jack and Cynthia were still substantially capable in intelligence gathering. While they weren’t professionals, they were still better than most people since they were elites that underwent training with some of the world’s best mercenaries.

"Leo’s group sent back a telegram. They found traces of Duskdune Shura and Charlotte by the Sand River. Looks like the news we put out earlier worked," Jack responded immediately,"Duskdune Shura is still recovering from his injuries. The same injuries caused him to lose a majority of his power and along with it, his membership in the Immortal Palace Alliance. Right now he’s being chased by his enemies alongside Charlotte. Once we released the news, they responded pretty soon. Looks like they can’t take it anymore."

Garen nodded.

"There is no hatred between Duskdune Shura and I that can’t be settled. He should’ve heard the news about my fight with Palosa now, not to mention we even have the Blood of Eternal Life that was originally stolen by Behemoth’s Gate. All this must be incredibly tempting to him. Now let’s see what he has to offer to trade with us. Last time we were begging him, but now look at how the sides have shifted."

Jack nodded,"Lastly, we found out who it was that hurt Gate Master Fei."

"Oh?" Garen was intrigued.

"The martial artist is called Sicilian Saldin, with him was his only follower and son Chukufa Saldin. They boarded a long distance cruise towards the east half a month ago, we found them on the guest list."

Garen stood up, a maple leaf fell onto his palm, and he rubbed it between his fingers.

"The east again….."

He has always wanted to venture east, but he had his family here, his sister, parents, uncle and his friends. Should he head out to sea, it would take more than a year even with the stable routes. If something went wrong during this period of time….

"We’ll set this aside for now. We can’t do much in a short period of time anyways. Oh right, do we know anything about what’s going on with Dale Quicksilver’s side of things?" He suddenly remembered that a few days ago he had dispatched Jack to look into that famous detective.

Jack’s face suddenly turned into a quizzing expression.

"Gate Master, that detective is still in the Evenia Province. We don’t know what he’s doing exactly but it seems like he’s being watched by some others because he knows some secrets about the Immortal Palace."

"He actually hung around there for this long," Garen rubbed the stubs on his chin, his face filled with thought.

He had only two objectives for now: First, is to kill the man responsible for his master’s death. Second, is to kill Sylphalan who did not just kill the Elder but also injured him severely once.

The mysterious Immortal Palace Alliance seemed to be hiding some other big secret as well.

"Pity that my injuries still haven’t recovered completely," Garen pressed his chest softly, a great deal of pain reverberated from where he placed his hand.

"You all may retreat back to your work, if you hear anything about Dale Quicksilver, report back to me immediately."

"Alright,"

"Take care and rest well Gate Master."

Corrine and Jack both turned to leave together.

Garen sat back on his stool.

"Immortal Palace’s secret...," for now, Garen’s only enemy is the elusive Immortal Palace Alliance. Soon he will settle his score with Sylphalan.

"Sylphalan… I bet you can hear me huh?" Garen looked up into the endless sky beyond the maple trees.

*****************************

Somewhere in the middle of the ocean between the three continents.

On a small white sand island.

The island was oval, like a green spot with white borders etched into the endless sea.

In the middle of the island was a thick plot of trees, on the top of a certain high ledge, was a massive marble hall sitting on white circular pillars.

The white marble hall stood alone at the end of the black colored rock ledge with no growth about it at all.

The marble hall was like a triangle stacked on top of a rectangle. It had a simple structure, with only a slight air of complication shown through the carvings on the wall that reflected an air of eternity.

By the entrance of the hall, was four rock pillars, each with a radius of 4 meters. Around these pillars were white snakes with pointy ears.

By the ledge right outside of the entrance was a shorter pillar with a square bowl on top of it. It looked like it was made to hold something important.

As the sunset, a short haired man with a cold expression stood by the square bowl. The wind made waves out of his blood red hair.

The man reached his hand into the square bowl and took a quick swipe, then his hand was instantly stained with a hint of blood, he flicked his fingers and drops of blood flew off the ledge to the bottom.

"Sylphalan, we need an immediate replacement for Duskdune Shura."

A weak old man covered in black robes appeared from the back of the short haired man. This old man’s whole body was hidden under a black cloak, none of his body was exposed, one could only hear his voice from under the cloak.

"When do you plan to take action?"

"I do not feel like leaving now." The short haired man smiled,"if you want, you can go yourself. Trash will always be trash, he couldn’t even take a hit and he even lost the precious Blood of Eternal Life."

Sylphalan turned around and looked to his right. Suddenly there was a friendly lady standing right beside him, she had eyes that were as blur as the ocean and skin as white as snow.

"Big sister! When did you come here? Ever since I killed our older brother, you’ve been showing up more often! I knew I was right!" Sylphalan was suddenly happy, he stopped doing what he was doing with his hand earlier and rubbed his fingers clean,"Big sister, do you think I should go out this time? I haven’t even recovered from my past injuries, and this trip will be incredibly tiring. But if I don’t go, our plan has reached a key point…."

Chapter 181: Secret and Proposal 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The blue eyed girl looked back at him calmly, and just smiled warmly.

"Sylphalan, are you going or not?! Give me a specific answer!" The black shadow again echoed.

Sylphalan frowned, his gaze was stuck on the blue eyed girl, her warm smile and expression made him feel warm too from the inside out.

"Big sister why aren’t you saying anything? Is it because that old bastard behind me is too noisy?"

"Yes, it must be because that old bastard is too noisy. I have always hated him anyways, I didn’t expect you to be uncomfortable around him too. Just give me a moment, I’ll kill him now!"

His body suddenly floated like it had no form, and with a loud WHOOSH he flew towards the black shadow by the entrance of the hall.

In a split second his body suddenly dispersed into a shadow that covered the sky like an infinite blanket of mud covering all of the hall in an instance.

"Sylphalan you!!!" The black shadow was enraged as he yelled his disagreements under the shroud of the black mud.

"What mad episode are you having again?!!" The old man made a low hum and broke through the black mud, dashing towards the bottom to escape.

Sylphalan appeared out of the black mud.

"I’m still too weak… Big sister, do you think that if I were to become a little bit stronger, that I would be able to kill that cree old bastard?" He looked at the blue eyed girl again, who smiled back, filling his heart with warmth once more.

Suddenly his vision was blurred, and the girl disappeared, he was left with emptiness.

His face instantly turned into one of regret and sadness.

"Big sister are you unhappy again? I must have disappointed you." He touched the left side of his neck, and was suddenly happy again.

"My time scar has grown longer by a bit! Do you see it big sister? With this little bit, I can live another extra two days!" His face was suddenly filled with childlike happiness.

"1 month and 5 days long…. I have never had such a long time scar, big sister you would be happy too right?"

At the bottom of the mountain, a black shadow appeared, and stumbled onto a tree for stability.

A red shadow appeared beside him, it was Flamingo, he was plain faced, with his Sword of the Sprites sheathed on his waist, he looked up at the hall above.

"Sylphalan gone mad again?"

"Damn this, I don’t want to be with that madman anymore! Whichever one of you want to you may go ahead!" The black shadow emitted the voice of the restless old man.

Flamingo squinted at the direction of the hall.

"Sylphalan has always been a madman. Sometimes good, sometimes bad. Just stay away from him, he is a pitiful one after all."

"Pitiful?! If he’s pitiful, who will pity me?!" The black shadow was enraged,"His someone who should’ve disappeared a long time ago! The time scar determines how long more he has to live. He is only alive because he keeps extending his lifespan by absorbing the Blood of Eternal Life and the life force of other humans! What ‘sometimes good, sometimes bad’, he is just completely mad!"

"Consuming life force to maintain his life scar comes with a side effect. Between periods of time he will experience great pain. The more he absorbs, the more the life scar learns to fight the effects so each time the effects of the life force decreases. Sylphalan…..he won’t be living for much longer." Flamingo stood silently for a moment, then continued upwards,"let him be."

**************************

In the days after, Garen focused solely on recovering.

The medicine from Andreala was quite effective, it did away with the pus infection on his wounds very rapidly. These wounds inflicted by Palosa’s Unrivaled Skyfall were a massive annoyance to fix, each wound was a pit, like the injuries from the Mitsubishi Army, they wouldn’t close up.

This also deterred Garen’s self recovery abilities from taking effect.

However once the pus infection was dealt with, the wounds started healing rapidly. Once they reached a stage where they resembled the behaviours of a normal human wound, Garen’s recovery abilities were able to take over once more.

While this happened, Garen was hanging out in the manor every single day, playing Go with Andreala and occasionally having some causal spars, then he would try to gather some intelligence from Andreala about the world outside.

His wounds healed faster and faster each day.

The situation with the Confederation was also getting more complicated after each passing day. The third fleet positioned by the ports were finally exchanging fire with the Weisman’s Imperial Greenbird Fleet.

The Confederation was loaded and powerful. With the Third Fleet directly fighting the Weisman’s small fleet of ships, if all goes well, it should end in a total annihilation of the Weisman’s fleet.

Everyone expected the Confederation to win this battle easily. All they had to worry about was the counter-attack from the Weisman’s after.

However something shocking happened.

The Confederation’s Third Fleet was annihilated instead. Ten of their destroyers were lost in a mere 20 minute span.

Even the Weisman Empire were shocked by the results. When the news came in, they thought that it was a ruse by the Confederation to lure them into a trap.

The Weisman’s Greenbird Fleet was just one small fleet out of the Empire’s 23 small ship fleets. All of the fleets were populated by small ships with weak firepower. While these fleets have served in the wild world of the oceanic borders, one wouldn’t have expected them to win on a head-on fight with the Confederation’s Third Fleet.

Suddenly, the true face of the Confederation was revealed in the eyes of all neighboring countries.

The truth was, that it’s army was severely underfunded, its federal reserves were empty and its ships were long overdue for maintenance. Even the guns and cannons were loaded with inferior ammunition, while the ships’ armors were all replaced with cheap metal.

Ever since the Border War, the Confederation has been slowly falling into corruption. During the Border War, all the countries looked up to the Confederation as the leader of the world. Nobody dared to challenge its might, anyone who tried were wiped out in easy fights by the Confederation’s army. This led to those in charge of the military becoming comfortable and overly proud of themselves.

While sitting in the tea room of the Manor, Garen held his freshly poured tea in one hand, while he held the newspaper up to read with a serious face on his other hand.

The headlines spelled out: ‘Who Will Pay For The Death of The Third Fleet?’

"Looks like things are bad," Andreala sat across Garen and was reading an exact copy of the Confederation Daily, the primary newspaper of the entire country.

"It’s not just bad, it’s really really bad," Garen added, putting down his tea,"This is because the Western Seas Company successfully opened a new shipping route but failed to draw up a mutually beneficial profit share plan with the Weismans. This led to the Weismans to declare war on the Western Seas Company, and subsequently leading to this. If the Confederation doesn’t face this properly with proper countermeasures, they risk losing all of the respect they’ve gained over the years from the other countries, that would put us all at risk."

"A proper countermeasure would probably mean they will mobilize the Ninth Army. All eyes will be on that," Andreala frowned as well. The nation’s security was in the interest of every citizen. Afterall, when they were outside of their own country, they would be identified by their nationality first, if the country they belonged to was weak, it would make doing business or anything at all tough.

The both of them had heavy hearts, but there was not much they could do as individuals. No matter how powerful they were, they were no match in a direct against something like a destroyer. Not to mention that each destroyer was staffed by at least a hundred seamen, some even up to the thousands. Even if they could make it onto a destroyer and kill every single one on the ship, by the time they’re done, the enemy would have already won the battle.

As a martial artist in the face of real war, especially one that concerns the air, sea and even land, they could only sit and feel conflicted.

Dong, Dong, Dong.

Someone knocked softly on the door.

"Come in,"

Garen put down his papers, and put on a plain face again.

Jack walked in in a white army-like uniform.

"Gate Master, the ingredients you asked for are ready, the medicine has also been brewed according to your instructions by a master brewer. Should I go over now?"

"These small things let the small ones do it,"Garen frowned at Jack,"you should be focused on enhancing your martial art abilities and improving yourself. Has that Eight Arm Dragon King bastard agreed on coming yet?"

"No, Mr. Yoda left Mr. Su Lin’s manor half a month ago, we don’t know where he was headed to. He was followed by the small bastard as well," Jack said briefly,"Also I would like to add that for someone like me whose age is nothing close to Cynthia, practicing martial arts won’t affect my abilities much anymore. I am sure of the direction I am headed to and the choices I would make in life."

Garen did not say much anymore, and just looked at Andreala.

"Do you want to go?"

"No thanks, I am headed to the baths later. I do not have a naturally tough body like yours so I need to use different ways to train and manage my body’s flexibility," Andreala wave his hand in denial.

"Your body’s flexibility? What if your body was strong enough? Then you wouldn’t need to fuss over this then?" Garen stood up and asked.

"Of course, but sadly for a martial artist to focus on one thing is already the limit. If I try any harder I will not reach a higher level anyways," Andreala shook his head.

"I have a secret technique, it can increase your body’s strength in a short period of time. Would you be interested?" Garen suddenly said,"the side effects aren’t too bad either, and the explosive strength is pretty terrifying."

"Oh? You actually have a secret technique like this?" Andreala’s eyes lit up in excitement,"what do I have to give you for it?"

Garen shook his head and smiled.

"Just a simple exchange of knowledge."

Andreala was stunned, and just stared at Garen, unable to conjure a proper reaction.

"Do you know the true value of a secret technique that doesn’t come with a horrifying side effect?"

"Of course," Garen knew the value of the technique best, since he had acquired it back then in a trade with the Tenth Hoop where he paid a great deal of benefits, money, real estate and rare materials in exchange for this secret technique. By his rough estimates, they were worth hundreds of million, a fifth of White Cloud Gate’s total assets then.

Andreala lowered his head and said softly,

"Alright, I too have a secret technique, I suppose we could share and exchange."

Garen was slightly shocked.

The reason why he was so generous was because Andreala was technically on his side. This bastard valued martial arts as much as his own life, he even remembered the time he still owed Garen a favor, and was the first to automatically send free medication over after the fight with Palosa.

In this world, not many people stood alongside Garen on the peak of martial arts practice. The two of them were just die hard fans of martial arts, an exchange of knowledge felt like they had moved from acquaintances to close friends instantly, friends interested in each other’s growth.

Garen did not spend much time practising, so he lacked experience, but he had a lot of combat experience from his life and death situations. Whereas for Andreala, who was experienced as he had spent many years practicing and perfecting his abilities, but lacked experience in fighting high level opponents, which made it hard for him to determine his own standing.

This exchange would be perfect for the both of them to help each other.

A few minutes later, the two of them stood on an empty space behind the manor.

The empty space’s floor was made out of white rock tiles, it was specifically designed for the purpose of practising martial arts, and also for the occasional spar between high level fighters.

Around the arena was a circle of flowers, and further outwards was a perimeter of 5 meter tall black walls with electric barbed wire.

Chapter 182: Secret and Proposal 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The whole of the field of white, complemented with a sea of blue flowers, and like the sweet fragrance of flowers, a sense of calm and joy filled the air.

The both of them faced each other, on their knees in the middle of the white stone yard.

Garen started to explain the theory behind the Explosion of Heavenly Spirit. This secret technique made use of the manipulation of finger methods to concentrate the qi onto a specific point. It would then excite a particular part of the body, which would instantly increase the strength and vitality of the user.

The explosive strength was 150% stronger than one would be able normally muster.

To Andrela, this enhanced explosive force was definitely a killer weapon. His speed would increase, along with his Vitality. It was perfect for him as it would make up for his weakness, which was being unable to increase his speed due to the load on his body.

To pay Garen back, Andrela decided to pass down one of his secret techniques; Three Star Convergence to him.

Other than sleeping and eating, both of them spent their remaining time teaching each other what they knew of their secret techniques.

The Three Star Convergence, a secret technique that had little side effect, was invented by Andrela from scratch. Similar to his Blink, it was the type of technique that he would usually not be passed down to others, but In this case, he considered it returning a favor with another.

This technique, which was of the instantaneous, explosive type, was something Garen had enquired of before.

It was a tri-simultaneous attack, which carried three times more destructive power than usual. Andrela had depended on this to injure him, past his Body Hardening Technique.

While they were trying to learn the secret techniques, Garen started preparing his medicine to learn the Golden Statue Technique as well.

He decided to invest points into secret techniques as he was not able to increase his attributes at the moment.

Both of them continuously learnt from each other for the next few months. Both the secret technique’s training regimes were very complicated. On the one hand, the Three Star Convergence required an external force to progressively stimulate a hidden part of the arm, and on the other hand, the Explosion of Heavenly Spirit required one to constantly reduce the casting period of the explosion. Furthermore, he had to use the Finger Method with extreme precision to avoid any backfire that could cause him severe injury.

After they got a grasp of the the tricks of these secret techniques, they slowly broke out of the learning daze.

Garen finally got hold of the Three Star Convergence technique with the help of Andrela. Based on the requirement shown by the skill pane, this technique required both basic sword techniques and Celestial Circle Secret Technique to be at advanced level in order to achieve the prerequisite.

However, Garen successfully modified the Three Star Convergence to suit his uses, with the help of Andrela. Andrela was not called a genius for nothing, either, as he was already able to use the basics of Explosion of Heavenly Spirit for actual battles. When they both sparred, Garen estimated that the current Andrela was on par with the talented Clark of the Crimson Sand Sword.

A few days later.

Both of them started talking about Palosa’s 179 secret techniques; the terrifying secret technique called the 99 Regressions. It made the White Bird Fist became the true White Bird Holy Fist. He was viewed as a Saint as his fist technique was beyond that of the normal realm.

"There should be something above the secret techniques." Andrela thought. "White Bird Holy Fist must have came in contact with this thing before being able to invent such advanced secret techniques like 99 Acute Airholes and 99 Regressions."

"You’ve said that you were pursuing something that was beyond the limit before. Don’t tell me you’ve found something?" Garen repeatedly placed his hands in the stove to burn both of his palms to accumulate more power into his Fiery Claw.

"I do have some lead." Andrela nodded. "There are a few legendary ancient secret techniques which have the effects that I’m looking for. I’ve been looking for it high and low during the time I’ve closed myself away from the rest of the world, and I finally found some clues."

As their relations had become better than ever, they’ve stopped hiding secrets from one other.

"I found out from an ancient bible that an ancient Grandmaster of Combat called Torres knew a secret technique that allowed him to shrug off any fatigue. He once fought for three days and three nights without pause. After that, he travelled far away into the enemy’s headquarters and started again. His endurance was definitely appalling."

Garen was alarmed. At his current strength, he was able to battle with all his might for a few hours at best before he started to feel tired. He couldn’t even hold on for a day, much less three.

"What’s the clue that you speak of?"

"I found a very well hidden connection." Andrela smiled. "You should have come across the Blood of Eternal Life, right?" He continued as Garen nodded.

"The Blood of Eternal Life is the blood essence of the Everlasting Beings. This is where we draw a connection to the blood of the non-human clans."

"Non-human clans?"

"That’s right. At present, there are already a few non-human clans that we know of; namely the werewolf, catmen and mousemen. Any others have left no trace. I have understood their respective clan’s histories through my friends from within them. I have discovered a new clue by comparing their histories." Andrela reached his hand out and started drawing on the white floor.

He finished drawing a simple relations chart very quickly.

"According to the records of the non-human clans, all their ancestors have their own genetic abilities. Some of their abilities are very similar to the secret techniques used by the Grandmasters of Combat in the ancient bible."

"What you’re saying is that it is very likely that the secret techniques created by the Grandmasters of Combat mimic that of the non-human clan’s genetic abilities?" Garen asked.

"No," Andrela shook his head with respect. "I’m not finished yet. My biggest discovery wasn’t this, but another matter."

"Oh?" Garen was stunned that this was not the biggest discovery.

Andrela focused his aura and released in an instant, forming the gigantic black word ‘ten’ behind his back, which thoroughly covered the whole colosseum.

"Just to keep this between us." He softened his voice.

He spoke of his discovery softly after stabilizing his aura and confirming that no one was eavesdropping their conversation.

"I suspect that the secret techniques that we have been using are magic spells originating from the warlocks from the fairy tales! They were the ones who obtained their genetic abilities via a special stimulation method."

Although Garen’s expression didn’t change, excitement bubbled in his mind.

While Garen had witnessed the werewolves, demon hunters, telekinesis and secret techniques with ridiculous effects, he thought that he was currently in a world where the modern society was not as technologically advanced as earth. Now Andrela told him that warlocks once existed in this world and that the secret techniques were traces that they had left behind.

"Do you have proof!?" He directly asked.

"Of course I do." Andrela nodded. "Technically, my Blink is not a secret technique from the Celestial Circle Gate. It was obtained from an ancient sect. To learn this secret technique, one would require the blood of a prime male lion and draw 81 special characters onto the body."

"Isn’t this superstition? Did you really do it?"

"Of course. I thought it was superstition as well, and I ignored this step to go directly for the steps to learn the secret technique. However, there was no effect." Andrella recalled and said. "I thought that the secret technique had complications, or that the physical body of the ancient people had some slight difference with that of ours. However, the effect showed itself within a short time after I’d decided to try it once!"

He continued as he saw Garen focusing all of his attention on him.

"After that, I saw the same characters in a fairy tale’s history. The same characters I used to learn the technique."

"You could have tried to see if there are still any effects if you changed the character slightly."

"Of course I’ve tried it. There won’t be any effect if I modify it." Andrela shook his head. "According to the fairy tale, the characters represented the lions in their time. I’ve been interested in the fairy tales related to the warlocks ever since, and I’ve started collecting information everywhere. I came to a shocking theory about when the first secret method came about."

"What theory?" Garen listened carefully.

"There is a high chance that warlocks once existed in this world. I have seen a record in an ancient book that does translations of ancient fairy tales." Andrela paused.

"It was written that: the warlock had enslaved species that were not their kind, and called them demons. They have ruled the world for a hundred million years."

Garen churned his brain as he tried to recall the legends of warlocks of this world.

"If they really did exist, how did they meet their demise, being such strong creatures?"

"I’m not so sure about that. However, I still suspect that our secret techniques originate from the warlock’s magic spells."

"What’s your plan?" Garen looked at Andrela, "If it’s true, what do you plan to do?"

"I have marked down certain ruins that may be rewarding to us. I plan to invite some friends with certain capabilities and explore them together. Although these ancient ruins have been explored countless of times, we may find something new if we have a clear target in mind."

"Furthermore, The sea is vast, that there a lot of areas that humans have yet set foot on. There must be something for us to discover." Andrela spoke softly to Garen as he looked at him. "On another note, I suspect that the immortal palace and the Behemoth Gate are most likely searching for the truth of the history, and a solution to go beyond the limit in the dark, just like me. They are just using the Eternal Blood of Life in the ancient ruins as an excuse."

Garen pondered for a bit.

"How many people have you actually recruited?"

"If you agree, there will be 2 including me." Andrela answered in all seriousness.

"Stop the nonsense." Garen was speechless since Andrela rarely joke. "I have no problem with it as long as you show me you have something to go on. Who else are you exactly trying to recruit?"

"The proof is simple. I can show you the information that I’ve gathered. All of the information can be traced and validated from the Federation’s library, and some private libraries as well. The information of the secret techniques and the history of the non-human species can also be validated. There are no falsification in the information but it would take a lot of time and energy to connect them together."

"As for who else to recruit, I have one in mind that is qualified to pursue what’s beyond the limit. He has also attained the pinnacle of the human strength as well. The humans from the Stonecliff Continent have sworn loyalty to the Immortal Palace, and the Behemoth Gate has been recruiting people with potential so that they can attempt to train them themselves. There are still a few Grandmasters of Combat who were not on friendly terms with the Behemoth Gate and Immortal Palace." Andrela reached out his hand and carved a name onto the floor.

‘Stephan Ralph’

Garen looked at a name that was unknown to him.

"Who is he?"

"He is mentally ill, and is not from the same district as us. However, he is the strongest and most horrifying hypnotist. Rumor says that you could be hypnotized just by hearing his voice and be caught in an illusion if you interact with him. He was the one who caused the appalling nine one four incident in Galantia, which resulted in a few thousand deaths. He had also once founded a terrorist organization in the Fivestar continent and has been listed as the fourth most dangerous individual by the three major countries.

He was able to hypnotize both others and himself. Nicknamed as the King of Nightmares, when his body was hypnotized his physical body would reach the utmost limit." When Andrela was describing this person, he had a faintly complicated and embarrassing look in his eyes.

Chapter 183: The Legendary Power... 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"How did you get to know him?" Garen was curious.

"You don’t need to know about that." It was rare that Andrela’s face was blushing red as he seemed reluctant to answer. "He will definitely come, because he was the one who made me realize this information."

"Alright. Would the three of us be enough?"

"It’s enough" Andrela nodded. "The Immortal Palace has a small amount of people too right? We would be too weak if we want to snatch the item away from them and the Behemoth Gate. If not for the Explosion of Heavenly Spirit that I’ve picked up from you that was perfectly suited for me to increase my battle strength, I wouldn’t even have had this idea in the first place."

"True that. I hope the person you mentioned is as strong as you describe to be."

"He will definitely not disappoint! Furthermore, the members of the Behemoth Gate had already entered the ancient ruins that I’ve marked. We will intercept them when they come out." Andrela said with confidence.

"We’re still short handed. To go beyond the limit…" Garen furrowed his eyebrows and suddenly a name flashed across his mind. "Maybe… He will be interested."

"Who?"

"White Bird Holy Fist."

Andrela’s eyes lightened up. "Didn’t he seal his fist due to personality disorder? Are you sure he will leave the mountain?"

"Do you think it was just a simple spar when I visited him?" Garen pointed at his chest, indicating where he was previously injured. "What do you mean when you say he has a personality disorder?"

"Palosa has a total of three personalities, namely the good, evil and unconcerned. The situation determines the personality he’s in. He’s good when he’s in a non-malicious negotiation, evil when facing his enemies or people who try to ambush or trick him, and finally indifferent is his actual personality, which is when his strength will be at its peak. He developed the good and evil personality when he was training his fists."

It was the first time Garen heard such a saying.

"Looks like he was not at his peak when he sparred with me." He frowned.

It was obvious that Palosa was in his good personality when they met.

After discussing about the procedures, both of them started consolidating Andrela’s information. It was at this time that Garen started to come to the legitimacy of the truth. It was so unexpectedly obvious that there were traces of it, it was just that no one had noticed it until now.

After validating the proof, both of them brought the information and went to find the first person they thought of, White Bird Holy Fist Palosa.

***********

Skylark Mountain Range

Garen brought Andrela, which both of them were in white shirts, along to see Palosa, who was in the middle of barbecuing his fish.

The bonfire was easily noticeable, shining brightly in the middle of the forest during night time.

Palosa sat alone by the bonfire, his gray-white shirt was dyed red by the bonfire’s illumination.

He raised his head and saw Garen and his men coming up to him torch in hand.

The group stopped just short of the bonfire, two of the men clothed in white turned around and started off from where they had come after giving Palosa a courteous, quiet bow..

Only Garen and Andrela wereleft standing, still in a white cloak.

"You’ve come once again." Palosa said coldly and lowered his head as he continued barbecuing his fish. The meat of the fish that was once white had morphed into a golden brown, and with it came the tempting aroma of cooked meat.

Garen walked and sat by the bonfire by himself and gestured Andrela to do the same.

"I’m not here to fight you today." He glanced at the fried fish that was piled onto the bonfire and calmly said, "I think you might be interested in what we are about to tell you."

Palosa glanced at him skeptically and then focused his attention onto Andrela. "Something that will interest me?" His tone was cold and emotionless and not as kind as Garen first met him.

"Let’s hear about it."

With a smile on Andrela’s face, he quickly took out a pile of papers that he had prepared from the cloak and strew it towards him.

Palosa caught it and read it at his leisure. He held a calm demeanor initially, but eventually his expression had started to change.

After some time, he put down the material that was on his hands and closed his eyes, deep in thought..

He soon opened his eyes and stared coldly at Andrela.

"I have seen Garen’s strength, and I do admit that he’s qualified to team up with me. How about you? You don’t have the battle strength. How do you plan to be part of the team?"

Andrela smiled.

"It is true that my current strength is of no match to the both of you. However I have already considered this point since I am the one who suggested this." Again, he brought out something from his cloak. This time it was a small transparent cylindrical glass bottle filled with a viscous silver white liquid. "I have this. At the crucial moment, I can stall up some time even if it’s from the professionals from the Immortal Palace, since my abilities lies in my speed. Furthermore, I have a friend, who is in the same level as you, needs me to be the middleman to communicate between us and him."

"The White Tree’s Sap? I’m impressed that you can still get your hands on a nearly-extinct resource. Have you taken my problems into consideration?" Palosa replied emotionlessly as usual.

"Of course." Andrela nodded. "Where we are going is a deserted place. Even if there were demons, they’re not something we can’t deal with. You can kill anything that moves."

"I need time to validate the information presented. Give me at least a month." Palosa pondered for a while and continued. "What makes you think that I will join your party and not go searching for it on my own after knowing this?"

"Sylphalan of the Immortal Palace will definitely have company." Garen voiced out from the side.

The scene fell into a hush as the group stopped talking. What was left was the faint sizzle of the still burning bonfire.

"Alright. We will take our leave for now. You can send your answer to this address a month later." Garen threw a white name card to Palosa. They stood up, turned around and left where they came.

The duo’s white cloaks slowly disappeared into the darkness of the forest.

Next up was the King of Nightmares. According to Andrela’s intel, his friend had recently went on a vacation on a small private island near the Stonecliff Continent.

This issue was left for Andrela to settle on his own, as Garen had his own problems on his hands.

The connection between secret techniques and the legendary warlock’s genetic ability might be the key to to go beyond the limits. Although Garen was very interested, his current main focus was to improve his own secret techniques.

************

Splash…

A basket of cold water rained down onto Garen’s head.

He stood in the middle of the Fenglin manor’s colosseum clad in nothing but square white boxer and a faint, gold colored oil spread all over his fair skin.

What was already a strong and aggressive body was further defined under the reflection of the oil.

He looked at the skill pane. There was an addition of Three Star Convergence and the Golden Statue Techniques at the back.

Garen looked at the amount of potential points that he had been collecting having not been using them for a long time. The power of the Golden Sand Throne had been continuously transferred into his brain day and night.

His potential point had reached up to 25 points! However, it could be seen that the Golden Sand Throne had decayed for quite a bit as the rate of transfer had been decreasing.

Garen sorted his attribute and skill panes.

‘Strength 2.66, Agility 2.72, Vitality 2.65, Intelligence 2.53, Potential 2596%.’

Secret Technique-----

Mammoth Variation : Explosive (Maximum Grade), Epidermal Hardening Level 1 (Iron Body), Blood Qi Stabilization Level 1 (Boulder Martial Art).

Fiery Claw: Grade 2 (Total of 4 Grades), Burning Strengthen Level 1 (Total of 3, from the Dark Crimson Technique and Red Jade Palm’s training regime)

Golden Statue Technique: Rudimentary Level (Total of 5 Grades), Do you want to merge with the Mammoth Secret Technique.’

The three techniques, Bronze, Silver and Golden Statue, were to Garen excellent techniques. He obviously would not merge them.

As Garen stood in the middle of the colosseum, he ordered a servant to pour down a bucket of water, after which he subsequently left the premises.

He focused his vision back onto the skill pane after his surroundings had returned to calm.

"25 potential points are enough to push a secret technique to its strongest form. The Golden Statue Technique was much more stronger than the Mammoth Secret Technique since it was a third rated secret technique, albeit superimposed with a lot of enhancements. Furthermore, he still could not attain the best effect even though he had mastered it to the point that he was second to none. Although the key to attaining the level of a Grandmaster of Combat was due to the supporting battle skills, its level and power is still too low. To have it as the main skill is disadvantageous."

He looked at the Golden Statue Technique in the skill pane.

With all the time invested in soaking in potions and rubbing medicinal oil all over his body, he had finally entered the Golden Statue Technique’s rudimentary level.

"The Golden Statue Technique’s sects was once a rival of the Crimson Sand Sword. Although its technique was weaker than the Crimson Sand Sword, it shouldn’t be that far apart." He recalled the explanation of this secret technique from memory.

Golden Statue Technique: Extremely effective in attacks and defense. Increase strength, vitality and recovery. Users who have mastered this technique are impervious to attacks that may injure the inner body, as the outer body was seamlessly merged with the inner organs, which result in enhanced regeneration. It was very effective in negating the effects of poisons.

Weakness: Heavy and dense body.

The benefits of the Golden Statue Technique was obvious compared to the Mammoth Secret Technique as it had an additional recovery skill. Even the modified Mammoth Secret Technique couldn’t top this effect.

This made Garen determined to choose this secret technique as his main technique.

He took a deep breath and reorganized his thoughts, his body would definitely have drastic changes from this major shift. He had to be ready.

He focused his vision onto the recently learnt Golden Statue Tecnique.

One point of potential point disappeared.

The Golden Statue Technique had increased to grade 1.

Two points disappeared, Golden Statue Technique had increased to grade 2.

Another two points disappeared, Grade 3.

This time it was five points that disappeared, it had increased to Grade 4.

Finally another five point disappeared.

He ultimately spent 15 potential points and raised the Golden Statue Technique to grade 5, which was its peak.

Garen stood still in silence and prepared himself as he looked at the symbol slowly appearing at the end of the Golden Statue Technique.

The moment the symbol fully appeared, A loud sound came from within Garen’s cranium and waves of cool air rushed into every part of his body.

It felt like his body was suddenly filled with torrents of cold water. However the strange thing was that thought to be a stream of hot blood kept flowing out of his heart and mixed with the cold water. It was similar to when he first learned the Explosive Fist Art, which produced a strong reaction towards the change of the body.

Again, something strange was happening to Garen’s body. His left side of the body was a shade of red whereas the right side became white. The difference was obvious as two opposing fluids, which was hot and cold, reacted inside Garen’s body.

A viscous liquid incessantly secreted out of Garen’s body, covering the whole of iits surface. It was as if he painted himself over with a layer of glue.

Fifteen points of potential points had raised the Golden Statue Technique to its peak, grade 5.

Chapter 184: The Legendary Power... 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As the Golden Statue Technique had been successfully maximised, the modified Mammoth Secret Technique, together with the enhancement effects from multiple Body Hardening Techniques became one symbol and merged into the Golden Statue Technique, fusing into a new, mysterious symbol.

‘Golden Statue Technique: Grade 5. The modified Mammoth Secret Technique has been partially covered and enhanced. A part of the conflicted effects have been erased.’ The meaning of the symbol was sent directly into Garen’s mind.

He panicked as he saw it. If he couldn’t achieve what he wanted during this conversion, his strength would decrease. Whether the Golden Statue technique would disagree with the modified Mammoth Secret Technique had to be confirmed after some assessment.

Since the Golden Statue Technique had solidified in the skill pane, it meant that it would no longer be subject to change.

‘Golden Statue Technique: Grade 5. (Known as strength, response and defense).

Defense Enhancement Level 1. (Conversion from the maximised Body Hardening Technique)

It was no issue that the powerful hardening might cause a counter effect, but he was concerned if the effect of the maximised Body Hardening Technique would be retained during attacking.

Garen tried to adjust his blood and qi. Fortunately, the effect retained but he couldn’t raised it up to two dan, instead remaining fixed at one dan.

Slightly disappointed, he continued looking at the skill pane.

There were ten more potential points, and it seemed like the Golden Statue Technique could still be increased further as its name has yet to turn gray.

Without any hesitation, he added five potential points into it.

His internal organs started to feel like they didn’t sit quite right with him.

Garen didn’t turned a deaf ear to the discomfort and focused all of his attention onto the peaked Golden Statue Technique.

This technique was considered a second rate technique once it had reached its peak. However, a strange thing happened after he added five potential points into it.

A strange symbol appeared behind the Golden Statue Technique.

Garen immediately understood what it meant: Achieved the theoretical limits of the technique due to forced conclusion onto the Golden Statue Technique. Training method will be increased drastically. Name will be changed according to the information.

The golden Statue Technique slowly disappeared and a new name appeared.

Divine Statue Technique!

Garen gave a sigh of relief.

This was the pinnacle of the Golden Statue Technique that the inventor had envisioned. Nobody really knew what effects the Divine Statue Technique possessed. Only Garen knew, for he was the only one able to experience it. His body brimmed with an inexplicable energy from head to toe.

The Divine Statue Technique; its name was derived from a god, an ever constant being, standing above all, the overseer of all beings. A god was eternal, and would never change or be injured. This was the theoretical peak of the Golden Statue Technique. It required a ridiculously high spirit to be able to achieve it.

As soon as the Divine Statue Technique had been activated, countless battle skills passed through Garen’s consciousness, and his body adapted to these battle skills swiftly as well. The Mammoth Secret Technique’s battle skills that made him an upper class Grandmaster of Combat slowly faded and became normal , well practiced techniques. What replaced them were the battle skills from the Divine Statue Technique.

Haa!!

He raised his hands and a vortex rose up from around his surroundings, throwing leaves and flower petals in all directions from where he was standing.

A faint, white-gold glow radiated from the back of his hand. It was as if it were not human.

A his hand screeched a loud clang when he brought them together with speed .

"It’s different from the Mammoth Secret Technique. The Divine Statue Technique is much harder and is less tough." Garen felt that his muscles and skin become as hard as bronze, yet he still had the flexibility to move freely.

He felt nothing when the cool air of the night breeze blew on his body. The lantern that hung at the corner of the manor’s building quietly let a dim light similar to that of a sunset onto the ground as it swung about..

The light of the colosseum became unsteady.

Bam!!

An explosion rang from within the dark forest from afar. The explosion was like roaring thunder as it travelled through the whole manor, shaking the walls ever so slightly.

Garen looked at the direction and could faintly heard gunshots from the direction.

"Mark!"

Soon, a middle-aged man lead a few servants clad in white from the manor’s main building.

"Gate Master, the military soldiers are having a battle against an unknown force. We have already sent our men to investigate."

Garen looked at him.

"Has Vanhatten returned?"

"He is still in Harmony City. The issue with the Felia Sisters has yet to reach a conclusion, owing to the fact that the matter has been exceedingly complicated. He has again requested to transfer people numbered 40 and above there." Mark replied with respect.

"He couldn’t resolve such a small matter. Whatever. Send a few men and inquire of the situation. These mountains are our industry. Those who trespass and refuse to cooperate with the authorities shall be eliminated."

The creaking of metal on metal could be heard as Garen moved his fingers.

After Mark left the colosseum, two dark figures jumped over the enclosing wall and softly landed onto the white stone field in the colosseum.

As Garen was about to attack, one of the dark figures raised his hands up and spoke.

"Garen, it’s me!"

The dark figure walked towards the lantern, and Andrela’s familiar face was brought to light.

Another dark figure walked out of the darkness as well. He was a man in a classic black western suit. A small goatee hung from his chin, and his lips let out the gentle smile of an English Gentleman.

"It’s a pleasure to meet you, Saint Mammoth Garen Sir."

Saint Mammoth’s floor had a reputation in China…

The well known Saint Mammoth’s floor…

Saint Mammoth’s floor…

Floor…

Floor…

It was as if thousands of mud horses ran through his mind as the term echoed in his head.

Garen took a deep breath as he tried to suppress his urge to attack. With a stupefied look on his face, "I don’t remember having such a nickname. Who thought of such a dumb name."

"Did you not know? This is a nickname bestowed to you by the International Martial Art Alliance. The nickname of the Grandmaster of Combat typically comes from his signature technique. Isn’t it a good thing that people call you Saint Mammoth?" The gentleman asked curiously.

Garen’s face twitched. He shrugged and changed the topic after calming himself down.

"It reminded me of a joke that I heard a long time ago. I still prefer people calling me the White Cloud Gate Master. Who are you?"

The man smiled and looked passionately at Andrela who was standing at the side. He looked at him coldly and introduced him as he forced a smile on his face.

"This is the King of NIghtmares Stephen Ralph."

Garen had never seen Andrela showing such an expression before. He estimated a ridiculous guess based on the distance they stood between each other. Without waiting for his response, he caught Ralph looking at Andrela melancholily.

"Drela, have you still not accepted my love towards you? We have already served each other without clothes."

"..."

"..."

A cold breeze blew across the colosseum as the three of them went quiet.

Garen felt goose bumps all over his body.

"Both.. Both of you should go rest for a bit." He mustered out a sentence as he invited them. "Mark!"

Immediately, Mark came out from the building and greeted them with a bow.

"Bring these two esteemed guests to the guest rooms."

"Yes, Gate Master."

Andrela reluctantly smiled and moved further away from Ralph on his own.

"Ralph. You… You should rest first as I need to talk to Garen for a bit."

Ralph looked at him with resentment and focused his gaze upon Garen as he admired and rated him. He left with Mark afterwards.

Only Garen and Andrela was left in the garden.

Both of them were still quiet even when the footsteps slowly faded to the distance.

"Beware of Ralph." Andrela helplessly put a complicated smile on his face.

"What happened between you two?" Garen sat on his knees as he could still feel the goose bumps he had earlier.

Andrela slowly sat down with an even bitter facial expression.

"This incident… I have to start from where I went outstation for my training."

As Andrela confessed, Garen started to understand the whole situation.

At the same time, he had a better understanding of the King of NIghtmares Stephen Ralph.

The current Ralph was just one of his many pseudonyms. The King of NIghtmares possessed many other aliases.

The King of NIghtmares with a thousand faces, who had gone through hypnosis of himself and others, could reconstruct his body structure. With the addition of illusions in place, he was able to become an old man or a young girl with different faces and bodies.

He had a one night stand with Ralph in his womanly form. He turned into a man and became a gay friend of his after the incident. This story was filled with blood and tears and had exceeded the realm of genders.

Garen, who thought he was experienced and knowledgeable, had goose bumps again as he heard the story.

"Ralph will change his identity every once in awhile. He is able to adjust his own body, be it the hormonal secretions or his bones and muscle structure. This guy has mastered many types of ancient chinese martial arts, especially martial arts like Jujitsu. He is the ultimate grandmaster." Andrela helplessly said, "If we were to strictly measure his martial art capability, he is on the same level as I. Not to mention his skill in hypnosis."

He finally added on.

"What you need to be aware of is that his personality and temper will change every time the King of NIghtmares changes his identity. Hence you should never put your guard down when he’s around."

Speechless, Garen nodded.

"King of NIghtmares…. Living up to his reputation..."

Andrela looked at Garen as he tried his best not to twitch his face.

"You have to be careful… I think he had laid his eyes on you. He will become the person that he likes in a few days time…"

Two Garens stood against each other on a starry night as the night breeze blew across the colosseum.

"Who are you!"

"I am Garen!"

"I am the real Garen!"

"You who are inferior in battle strength! Who allowed you to impersonate me!"

"Hmph! How dare you impersonate me! What you did is outrageous!"

"Mammoth Secret Technique!"

"Ten Thousand Mammoth Retrograde!"

This scenario flashed through Andrela’s mind. Based on his understanding of Garen, it was very likely that this scene would happen.

Garen looked glazed as he obviously had a bad feeling about it.

"How did you solve it last time? This situation."

"He knocked me out and impersonate me for some time before. He will revert back to normal once he gets bored of it. He won’t be bored of you so it depends on how you want to resolve it." Andrela helplessly replied. "However he still has a few identities that he tends to stick with. One of it is the current Steven Ralph, who is also the founder of the Siren Group. There is another identity he likes to use. You’ll see it soon."

Chapter 185: Expo 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"To be honest, you really did find a rare one."

"He does have the skill though." It was as if Andrela was trying to comfort himself. "I apologize for the explosion earlier. He is, after all, on the wanted list from the Federation."

"It’s okay. So what’s your plan now? We just have to wait for Palosa’s response. If he were to accept our proposal, the four of us should be able to take on any situation." Garen said softly.

"We have to make our move regardless of his acceptance. The exchange with Duskdune Shura should be able to gives us some reliable information. We will definitely have a lead if we follow the Immortal Palace." Andrela said with confidence.

After some thought, Garen softly clapped his hands.

A person soon came out of the small building with a black metal box. Two servants carefully placed the box onto the white ground, greeted Garen with a bow and left.

Garen walked towards it and opened it with a flick of the lock. What appeared in the box was, unexpectedly, another smaller box.

He opened it again and it was filled with small ice cubes, and among them in the centre was a test tube covered by a white silk. A dark red liquid filled the inside of the test tube.

Garen took out the test tube and shook it in front of Andrela.

"The Blood of Eternal Life that I have obtained from Behemoth Gate."

"You’re really daring. Aren’t you afraid that they will ambush you?" Andrela was speechless. "You even let your underling guard this."

"I couldn’t find a good opponent that could fight me evenly." Garen grinned. "I took away their stuff as I defeated Clark. The whole Behemoth Gate’s scheme in the southern region has been foiled by me. What’s left is just trash and not worth mentioning."

"Just be careful."

"I understand."

Andrela felt emotional as he took the box of Blood of Eternal Life. "We’ll just have to see what kind of information Duskdune Shura can give us."

**********

After a few days of resting in the manor.

Garen and his team finally received Palosa’s response: ‘3 months later.’

It wasn’t specified if he would be attending the operation three months later or he needed another 3 months to consider. Or maybe he meant he would give an answer in March?

The three of them couldn’t wait any longer and brought the Blood of Eternal Life to meet up with Duskdune Shura. They had decided to exchange the Blood of Eternal Life with information regarding the Immortal Palace and a precious secret technique. At the same time, it was to clear off any resentment among them as well. This was the agreement between Duskdune Shura and Garen.

Within their own spaces, they communicated with each other with an encrypted tool without any face to face contact. Duskdune Shura had been extremely careful.

After some negotiation, the Garen trio obtained information of the Immortal Palace and Garen also obtained a special secret technique: White Peacock.

Under the suggestions from the King of Nightmares, they decided to name themselves the White Peacock as an alliance among the three men. This secret technique was able to make use of the user’s qi to mark the enemy for a long period of time. The secret technique would secretly release a special smell that was very hard to suppress within a radius of two kilometers. Only users who knew this technique could notice the smell.

Those who were under the effect of the secret technique would be like a peacock, especially eye catching during day time.

This secret technique was purely used for tracking. It had no known side effects and was very effective.

Garen tried to invite Duskdune Shura to the White Peacock but was unfortunately rejected. The old man had been very careful after his battle strength waned due to his serious injury and had decided to stay hidden after obtaining the Blood of Eternal Life. Garen predicted that he had planned to pass down his skills to a disciple and heal himself afterwards.

Their purpose was barely met. However they planned to follow their plans anyway and went to Picardi as per Duskdune Shura’s intel.

**************

Few months later…

An uncountable amount of flowers, pink and white, covered the mountains and plains, dying the hillside a pinkish red.

There was a gray-white car lane among the sea of flowers. The road had separated the sea of flowers like a thin, white ribbon.

Occasionally, there would be horse carriages or cars travelling down the road, and with them carried the sounds of bells and car engines.

The afternoon sky was showered in a pale golden color, with a dark blue on the edges in the horizon. There was a pale red within the gold sky which, when on the cloud, looked like the cloud was aflame with light.

The color of the clouds changed from gold-red to pale gold as the sunset light radiated through the sky like a slow crawling ladder.

There was a silver car en-route to the capital of Picardi through the white road. Its speed was so fast that it kept overtaking the rest of the carriages.

Behind the seat of the silver white car sat a tall man with short hair.

The man was in a suit. It looked like he was asleep with both of his arms on his knees. Although this guy was not particularly handsome except for his exceptionally smooth skin and golden white complexion, he had a presence that couldn’t seem to be ignored.

There were a total of three people inside the car. The driver was a handsome man with an eye patch with long hairs. He looked sharp yet gentle.

There was another man with a sturdy body and a cool face sitting in the passenger seat. He looked exactly like the man who sat behind.

The driver looked at the scenery through the window.

"We have reached the Four Season Road. This road spans about ten kilometers, and we’ll be reaching the capital of Picardi, Ansela soon." He looked sideways at asked. "What’s the plan, Garen?"

The man who was sitting at the back slowly opened his eyes, revealing calm, dark red eyes. "I will find a place and stay first. You guys can decide where."

"According to our intel, The people from the Immortal Palace will be here during the full moon. Although we don’t know how many people they will bring along, we are sure that they will definitely be here so we have no need to rush. We just need to wait patiently." The long haired man said as he nodded.

"You two shouldn’t make any move yet. I need to go and scour for the strength of the Immortal Palace. Whoever had provoked me, the Saint Mammoth Garen shall die!"

Garen suppressed his urge to hit him as he stared and growled softly at the strong man in the co-pilot seat.

"King of Nightmares, you better revert back!"

Another ‘Garen’ hmph-ed. "Are you provoking me as well? You have to know that provoking me means provoking the whole White Cloud Gate!"

"Stop messing around King of Nightmares." Andrela who was driving the car said helplessly.

"Alright alright…" ‘Garen’ raised his hand and surrendered. "It’s been so long I had so much fun. I don’t know why but I admire Garen so much when I see his strong body and streamlined muscles."

Andrela shivered.

He even turned into a beautiful woman before she went to bed in the hotel last night. He became the strong Garen the next morning… and cuddled with him in ‘Garen’ form…

Truthfully he was very excited when the King of Nightmares turned into a woman and stayed with him. However, it could also be horrifying as what he had experienced yesterday.

He almost vomited out gastric when he saw ‘Garen’ leaning in for a kissed as they cuddled in the morning.

"If you pull a prank like yesterday night again, I will never touch you again." Andrela said with a serious face.

"Alright alright. I’ll be careful." The King of Nightmares replied lazily as he smiled.

Garen, who was at the back of the seat, was completely speechless. The only way to differentiate them was their odour when the King of Nightmares transformed into him. Even Garen himself found it hard to differentiate them purely from look. He was slightly worried if the King of Nightmares decided to impersonate him and create trouble everywhere…

Suddenly, his eyes were brimming brightly.

"King of Nightmares, you can transform into anything right?"

"Of course." King of Nightmares nodded.

"Have you seen any members from the Immortal Palace?"

"Are you planning to…" The King of Nightmares furrowed his eyebrows in confusion.

Andrela smiled as he understood Garen’s intention.

"A simple and effective idea. The strongest influencer in Picardi, the Argentism is lending us a hand in this operation. There are also other external forces from the locals as well. We will depend on you during that time."

The King of Nightmares nodded helplessly.

"Yes yes yes. In the end I will be doing the most work."

"An able man should do more work." Andrela said with a smile on his face. "It would be best if the members of the Immortal Palace were to not appear. If they did…"

"As long as it’s not Sylphalan, don’t butt in." King of Nightmares said calmly. "Especially Flamingo… That guy still owes me an arm…" His eyes were burning calmly in red as his tone was cold and calm. "What about you Drela? What do you plan to do?"

Andrela pondered for a moment: "I’ll need to arrange to avoid any unexpected events. It all depends on you. It’s my time to shine if all goes well."

"Let’s hear about the overall situation this time." Garen asked softly from the back.

"According to Duskdune Shura’s intel, there is a collector in Picardi’s capital, Ansela. This collector showcased a strange looking ancient mirror during a public collection expo. The people from the Immortal Palace believed that it was the ancient Mirror of Secret Text, passed down from the previous generation. They then arranged for a few people to steal it. The Mirror of Secret Text contains knowledge of ancient secret techniques which the Immortal Palace have always laid their eyes on."

He continued after stopping for a while. " The identity of the collector is the high priest of Argentism. His strength is decent and his authority is even stronger. Those who are assigned to safeguard the collection are three of Picardi’s most famous and strongest warriors from Argentism. I have never seen their skills but they should be at least the same level as the Grandmaster of Combat. Furthermore, they also have a group of military army guarding the surrounding with heavy weapons, which has its own threat."

"It’s obvious that the Argentism are trying to show off their strength when they invited powerful individuals to attend the collection expo. I suspect that they have some hidden powers as well. We should take note of the Behemoth Gate too. However, their likelihood of attending should be low, since Garen you just severely injured them. At the moment, they should not be able to mobilize a large force."

Garen nodded: "That’s true. So only the Argentism and Immortal Palace are worth taking note of?"

"That’s not necessarily true. Perhaps there are some unexpected masters within the civilization?" Andrela laughed. "I have a list of the masters’ names. Do you want me to read it out?"

"Don’t waste your time naming the small fries." The King of Nightmares covered his face with his arm and his face started to slowly change. His body shrank and his body figure became more and more slender. It was like rubber moulding into another shape.

Chapter 186: Expo 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Although this was not the first time for the two of them to saw his transformation, they couldn’t help but stare with a surprise look on their faces.

"Who are you trying to change into this time?" Andrela asked cautiously.

"You got thinner Drela…" The King of Nightmares became a middle aged woman with a well developed body and reached out his hand to touch Andrela’s face.

Andrela was stunned. His face immediately turned red as his veins started becoming visible on his forehead.

"Don’t expect me to give you any quarter you if you become my mum again!!" Andrela was furious.

The King of Nightmare’s laughter could be heard all these while inside the car.

It had been actively noisy inside the car during the journey as Andrela and the King of Nightmare would argue against each other over the smallest things.

The car finally arrived a double story motel before the sky darkened.

There were a few sparse cars and carriages parked in front of the motel.

They disembarked and let the valet take care of the parking for them. The first floor of the motel seemed to have an air of liveliness as they entered.

The space of the first floor is similar to the typical bar. Although there were few patrons, the whole of the first floor was full as each of them took a spot.

ost of the customers were passers by on the first floor of the black ceilinged hall. Some of them were whispering to each other, while others were drinking alcoholic drinks in small amounts. There were even some that were looking at a map.

There was a saxophonist trying his best to play a not so melodious piece of music on the half oval stage on the first floor.

The trio looked all around them but still couldn’t find any spot to seat down.

"Why don’t we just chase one of them off and take that?" the King of Nightmares suggested.

"We are already in Ansela’s territory. Ansela is famous for its strict law. If you do not want to be targeted by the sheriff, it’s best to not make any rash moves." Andrela softly said. "It will expose our position if we make any big moves."

Garen, who had also knew about it, agreed as well.

"Let’s get back onto the road after a quick bite then. There’s no need to delay our journey to the city. If we really can’t find a seat we will just have something in the car."

"Fine." King of Nightmare shrugged. He was now in the shape of Ralph.

"Ah!"

A girl suddenly screamed beside Ralph.

Garen and Andrela looked over.

What they saw was a beautiful woman in a full body white dress covering her mouth with her hand as she stared at Ralph. The tomato sauce that was on her hand splashed all over Ralph’s shirt as they collided into each other.

"I’m sorry! I’m sorry!!" The girl kept bowing down as she apologized. Judging from the material of her dress, it was obviously a high quality product. With a silver white belt over her waist that was knotted in a flower from her left side, it enhanced her body figure even more.

"It’s ok, forget about it." Ralph frowned as he clearly made way for her earlier. He didn’t expect that the girl also tried to gave way as well, which resulted in both of them making the same gesture and collided into each other. "Be careful when you walk next time."

"Y...Yes." The girl blushed as she nodded.

Ralph’s shirt was made out of a special material. The tomato sauce quickly came off from it with just a slight gesture. By using a piece of tissue and wipe off the leftover, his shirt looked good as new again.

Three of them looked at the girl as she walked back to her seat. Those three youngsters who looked somewhat cultured and polite looked at the girl immediately started a conversation the moment she sat down. Surprisingly, the heart of the topic was Stephen Ralph.

Those three thought that their voice would be overwhelmed in this noisy motel. What they didn’t know was that Garen and his team had extreme senses and could hear everything clearly.

Among these three fellows who were not more than 15 or 16 years old, one girl and guy looked slightly frivolous and the white dressed girl was smiling happily on her seat.

"That man has class. He didn’t say anything to me even when I poured tomato sauce onto his shirt. Judging from his attire, I suspect that he must be some young master from a big household. That gaze…" The girl’s personality changed from innocent and elegant to lustful.

The guy from a side replied: "Stop dreaming. They’re are about to leave. Only I would want such a pitiful animal like you. No one can sell you off no matter how they try."

"What do you mean by that!"

"Can you finish your food quickly and stop showing off your love in front of me?" Another girl in a green checkered shirt paired with white jeans said. With short and pale yellow hair and bangs, she gave off a clear and refreshing vibe.

The most eye catching thing about her was that she had a squirrel, smashing a big walnut onto the table beneath her elbow.

"We still have to get on the road after we’re done eating. We need to reach Ansela tonight."

"Understood." Both the guy and girl responded in sync.

On Garen’s side, Andrela had pulled the King of Nightmares away and he was the only one left behind. After glancing at the three youngsters, they walked out after buying their food and drinks.

The valet had already filled up the car with petrol. They got in the car after paying the bill and was immediately on route to Ansela.

The whole journey was filled with silence. Just as they almost arrived the outskirts of Ansela, their car broke down.

"What happened?" The King of Nightmares, who was half awak, asked as he felt the car slowing down.

"The car’s not functioning and I have no idea what went wrong." It was the first time Andrela faced such a problem. He reluctantly stopped the car by the road side and got out of the car to inspect it.

Garen, who was sitting at the back of the car, could even see the white smoke coming out from the hood. The whole car was filled with the pungent smell of petrol.

He got down the car and stood at the slanted grass field which was just beside the road.

"What happened? Can it still move?" He looked at Andrela who had just popped opened the hood to inspect the engine of the car.

"No idea. I don’t know how to fix it either." Andrela shrugged after some inspection.

"I have a lot of clothes on the car; I don’t want to carry all of it and walk into the city." The King of Nightmares complained. "This car is so useless! It can’t even run for any long distance at all!"

Andrela could only pity him.

Garen started to miss Su Lin as he stood at the side of the car. If Su Lin and his limited edition car was here, this problem would have been unlikely. Even if there was, he was an expert in fixing cars.

"Although three of us are masters in martial arts, you can’t just expect us to carry our luggages and walk to Ansela right?" The King of Nightmares leaned against the wall as he started to light up a cigarette. "Why not we hitch a ride?"

"That’s all we can do." Andrela started to pack his own stuff.

Among the three of them, the King of Nightmares brought the most stuffs such as clothes, accessories, makeup, and a mysterious toy box. Andrela and Garen brought minimal items as they only brought washable clothes and boxes to store their money, which was in Picardi’s currency.

Garen stood at the side of the road as he tried to wave down a car.

With his height of 1.8m and muscular body paired with a strict face. The cars did not stop at all. In fact they flew past even faster.

"You won’t do. Let me have a go at it." Andrela pushed Garen aside and stood by the side with a smile on his face. However, it was the eye patch that made him even more domineering during night time. Even his smile started to look like an evil grin.

The driver immediately stepped on the pedal when he saw Andrela’s face. The carriage sped off like a sharp arrow.

The next few cars which passed by was the same and Andrela’s smile started to become stiff.

"Let me try." The King of Nightmares sighed as he walked to the front from behind.

He was dressed properly like a gentleman, which looked much more normal than Garen and Andrela.

After a few cars passed by, a big horse cart with four carriages finally slowed down.

The carriages were all in white and there was an initial ‘KL’ on the carriage.

"Can we hitch a ride?" The King of Nightmares asked the old man.

"Get on!" The old man pointed to the back with his whip.

The trio finally relaxed as they did not have to use their last resort, which was to snatch a car by force. Although the trio were good men who followed laws, they were not messing around during this trip. The Argentism had a lot of eyes in Picardi. They would be the first to know if anything happened.

All of the compartments were big and enclosed. As the trio pulled opened the curtains, they saw the three youngsters sitting inside the adjacent carriage.

"Hi handsome uncle." The white dress girl greeted the King of Nightmares with a smile. "It’s not a small problem to have your car break down in this area. It’s fortunate that you met Sophie’s driver."

"It’s you." The King of Nightmares let out a seductive smile. "Thank you for your help. We might have to walk to the city if not for it."

"There’s no need to thank us. Yali accidentally poured tomato sauce onto you earlier. We will repay you by bringing you along for the ride." The golden hair boy smiled as he said from one side. "Furthermore, you should thank the driver; the girl over here."He pointed at the girl with his mouth."

The girl in pale green checkered shirt laughed.

"We should help each other when we’re all on a trip. You don’t need to thank me." A small, well fed squirrel was climbing onto her shoulder. "My name is Katyusha. Where do you three want to go? I will send you guys there."

"Coconut Tree Hotel at the Northern region of the city. We have booked a room there." The King of Nightmares politely replied.

"Coconut Tree Hotel? I’m gonna ask just because I’m curious. Are you guys going to visit the ancient artifacts expo?" The girl asked.

Garen and his team sat down and the King of Nightmares nodded as he heard the question.

"Yes. We’re here just to visit the ancient artifacts expo. I heard that they will showcase a lot of legendary treasures. We are also a hobbyist collector so we can’t miss this opportunity."

Chapter 187: Expo 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I heard a lot of the participants this time brought their own collections, probably to exchange with other people as well. That’s why the expo is made into an exchange instead." Speaking of antiques, the girl Katyusha suddenly became interested. "Speaking of which, the vehicles coming into Ansela today, at least half of them were heading toward the expo. Rumor has it that the largest natural emerald Heart of Yggdrasil will make an appearance, as well as the legendary Balbia’s Box, it’s one of the best known Millennium Antiques…"

"Balbia’s Box? That’s not a usual Millennium Antique, I heard its owners always end up in a failed marriage. Dunno if it’s real. I’ve heard about the Heart of Yggdrasil, but isn’t it in the hands of a Weisman Duke?" Garen’s interest got piqued and joined the conversation.

"It was a long time ago, something happened a while ago…"

The conversation in the car split into two.

King of Nightmare, Andrela, the boy, and the girl in one, Garen and Katyusha in another.

After a while, Garen found out from the girl about a number of hidden Antiques of Tragedy and their owners.

"I have collector friends from all around the world." Katyusha said proudly, "A part of it are my dad’s collector friends, but they know me. The others are my own friends I made. Mr. Garen is from Yalu Confederation but has knowledge far beyond a normal person. I don’t suppose you know Green Pine Auction House?"

"Green Pine?" Garen thought it sounded familiar.

"Yeah, it’s by a friend in the Confederation. You can find some decent stuff in there too, you should check it out. Just say you’re a friend of Katyusha, their director would definitely give you a discount." Katyusha proclaimed. "The director, Fenistine, is a good friend I made when I was in the Confederation."

"Fenistine?" Garen finally recalled from his memory about Green Pine Auction House and its history. "Fenistine, isn’t she the girl with the light blonde hair and blue eyes?"

"You know her?" Katyusha was slightly astounded.

"A little, but we’ve been out of contact for a long time." Garen shrugged.

"She’s not doing very well now." Katyusha looked at Garen weirdly. "Her family is a huge family with very conservative attitudes. They don’t like her having interest in antiques. Now she’s even selling her prized collections because of some new problems. I wonder what it is, any idea what?"

"Not even a little. I haven’t been talking to her." Garen’s brows furrowed. They had a pretty good friendship, but she never talked about her family in front of him.

"Better take note then." Katyusha’s gaze at Garen is a little loaded. She didn’t believe in pure friendships between a man and a woman.

"I will." Garen nodded.

"What about your car?" Katyusha asked.

"We’ll hire someone to pull it over. As long as we keep the important things with us." Garen shrugged.

"Any friend of Fenistine is a friend of mine, I’ll ask someone to tow it over to Hotel Coconut Tree."

"Thanks."

Andrela, King of Nightmare, and the other two on the other side also went apart. The two sat together and spoke to each other in a voice so soft, it’s like they’re only lip reading each other.

Garen asked Katyusha about Picardi and the situation with the expo before quietened to rest.

He silently listened to the other people while putting his hand into his jacket pocket, feeling the Golden Sword Throne he brought around the whole time.

A cool Potential breeze still flowed out of it, but it’s already running thin.

"I heard there’ll be a Mirror of Secret Texts, do you think it’s true?" King of Nightmare asked suddenly.

"It’s true. I heard the owner lent it out for exhibition. It’s definitely a rare treasure. I came here to admire and to appraise it actually. Mirrors of Secret Texts are not something you hear often these days."

She started talking nonstop about the history of the Mirrors of Secret Texts, obviously being excited having someone listening.

Garen just sat aside and listened.

Garen decided he doesn’t need a breakthrough at this moment. He’s still young, unlike Palosa, so he doesn’t need to even worry.

Old Man Gregor’s death has become more like an obsession at this point. He only wanted to locate Sylphalan and fight him. Mastering his Divine Statue Technique, he currently feels he’s stronger than ever. He can clearly sense he’s that much tougher than before.

His only motive of finding the Mirror of Secret Text was to fight the people from the Immortal Palace Alliance. Of course, finding Sylphalan would be the best case scenario.

As Garen was quietly combing through his thoughts.

Thud!

A dull sound came from in front of the carriage.

"What’s up?"

"I felt the carriage shook for a little."

Katyusha stopped talking as well, her face was struck with a moment of panic, but she recovered her composure almost immediately after.

"Sciara, is everything okay out there?"

"It was nothing, just some animals running across us. Took me by surprise." The old coachman’s voice drawled in from the front.

"Be careful."

"Yes miss."

Garen, Andrela and King of Nightmare exchanged a glance. They definitely heard the short but distinct exchange of blows. Obviously, the opponent was defeated in the blink of an eye.

But Garen had a hunch something was wrong.

His chest was radiating heat.

Confused, he pressed his hand on his chest. It was the pendant in the shape of a book Old Man Gregor gave him. It was burning slightly.

The pendant hadn’t done anything since he’d gotten it. Sylphalan seemed to have come to recover the pendant that time. Garen had not been able to uncover its secrets no matter how long he analyzed it.

But now, the pendant is starting to heat up.

"Is there anything wrong?" Katyusha looked at Garen, confused.

"Oh, it’s nothing, just spaced out a little." Garen smiled. He had a feeling something was wrong, but he didn’t understand where.

Maybe I’m just paranoid, he said to himself.

This Katyusha may not be as simple as she seems. The strength of the battle outside does not sound weak, they’re at least as strong as a member of special forces. If they had tried to rob…

The moment the sound came up, Katyusha’s body tensed, as if she could burst out a fighting stance at any time despite her size.

"Excuse me." Katyusha stood and steadily made her way out of the carriage before closing the door.

She sat beside the coachman who was slowly driving the carriage to their destination. Katyusha frowned.

"Another batch?"

"Yeah, the Argentists. Don’t think they want us to be there."

"Hmph. We have twelve squadrons and five main forces mixed in with the travelers, the Argentists could not possibly stop us. They are only filtering out possible opponents. They’ve got pretty good intel." Katyusha smirked. "Their going back on their words in the meeting last time has cost us much damage. I will definitely take my revenge."

"What’s your plan?" Sciara inquired.

"The five main forces are already here, so let’s see how they react. They didn’t only offend us Black Snakes."

"As long as their bishop stayed put, the others are easy to deal with. It depends on who’s got the Mirror of Secret Texts." Sciara nodded, breaking out of his coachman persona.

In the car, Andrela and King of Nightmare exchanged looks, while Garen closed his eyes again.

Looks like the capital city of Picardi had attracted lots of people with ulterior motives.

The carriage treaded the path for another half hour before stopping at Hotel Coconut Tree.

The Anselan streets at night were filled with crowds as busy as they were in the day. People swarmed the streets for entertainment and enjoyment.

Garen and the other two booked a room each in the hotel.

Katyusha had a villa near the hotel, so her group went there instead. Katyusha was obviously not her real name, but Garen didn’t mind. This woman was here with the same intention as everyone else.

Similar to him, all these people would be coming in by the pack in the very near future.

　　**************

Ansela was an exotic city littered with buildings with white round top. Located in the city center, in a dark room of the highest tower-slash-hotel, two figures, one old and another young, sat.

The old one was a lady close to her centenary. She sat by her bed with a walking stick made of blackwood in her hand, staring closely at the girl in front of her.

The girl looked confused, but as the old woman kept her silence, so did she, just sitting at the wooden chair quietly.

None of them spoke to each other, the silence in the room amplified by ticking of the clock.

Soon, a set of faint steps shuffled up in front of the door before waiting outside the room.

Knock, knock.

The door opened by itself.

A young man with the blue and white uniform of the hotel room attendant walked in with a silver dining cart.

"Madam, your food is served."

The door shut itself with a click.

As soon as the door closed, the room felt as if it was detached from the rest of reality by an unknown force. The buzzing from the streets disappeared, leaving only the clock ticking in an otherwise pindrop-silent room.

The girl was visibly discomforted. She glanced left and right, hoping to find out what had happened.

"Don’t worry." The attendant’s voice switched to one of an old man’s. He pulled at his face, unveiling his wrinkled face under a thin mask facade.

"I rushed here as soon as I got news of you coming here. I didn’t expect you to be this early." The old man left the dining cart, pulled up a chair and sat down slowly.

Chapter 188: Expo 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Julie, this man is my old friend in Picardi, Tom King Cruise." Old woman introduced the old man to the girl. "He’s also one of tens of millions of people in Picardi who’s like us."

The girl was stunned for a little while. She turned to the old man, who flashed her a kind smile. "I’ve heard about you since a while ago, little Julie."

"Right, let’s skip the formalities and go on with the topic," The old woman finished introducing. "The Argent Mirror is a treasure from eons ago, we cannot let the Immortal Palace Alliance have it. We need to come up with an strategy to deal with this."

Tom King frowned.

"The Argent Mirror is called the Mirror of Secret Texts amongst laypeople. It was said to have records of ancient Secret Techniques of the Mirror. Immortal Palace Alliance will definitely send their strongest members here. It’d still be fine if it’s former Weisman Admiral Griffith, at least we’ve fought him a few times and are familiar with his modus operandi. If it were other people, then it’ll be troublesome."

"What about you locals? I trust you have a plan ready even before we arrive?" The old woman asked with a frown.

"Of course. The Argent Mirror has a seal on it, therein lies the true Secret Text, alongside it was the terrifyingly strong, ancient Will of the Origin. Once it is released, the Will will be unleashed, toppling the whole world. This is also Immortal Palace Alliance’s scheme. So we found the Time Pin. So long as we put it on the surface of Argent Mirror, we can stop the unsealing process when need be." The old man explained.

His eyes darted back onto Julie.

"But since you brought Julie, I reckon we’ll not be using the Time Pin anytime soon."

"No, if they sent Flamingo this time, even Julie…" The old woman interrupted, "You don’t understand the danger with the Will of the Origin. It’s so incredibly unstable, the Immortal Palace Alliance is practically burning themselves with its flames. Which is why we need to have both plans prepared. Julie, I, and the others will stop Immortal Palace Alliance directly from the front, only with the nature of her telekinetic abilities that we can suppress those in Immortal Palace Alliance who had taken Blood of Eternal Life. We will also need to prepare the Time Pin, in case."

She added, "We must not let them succeed, once unsealed, nothing in the world can stop the Will of the Origin. I thought that thing had been long lost in history."

"How’s Julie doing? Is her power gonna be enough?" The old man asked in a hushed tone.

Julie hesitated, looking a little guilty.

"I’m not that talented, I’m only at Third Level."

The old man’s eyes twitched and his face flashed a slight shade of red. He inhaled deeply, and waited a while for his urge to yell at this unfairness to subside.

"Third Level, that’s not bad, that’s… not bad."

"Alright then, since it’s all planned out, you will execute the your original plan, and we will wait for the Immortal Palace Alliance to show up." Old woman nodded. "Remember to keep casualty to a minimum."

Julie asked, unsure. "Teacher, why can’t we ask the Argentists to help? A friend of mine told me, elites from all sort of places have shown up this time. If we can attack Immortal Palace Alliance together, wouldn’t it help a lot?"

"You don’t understand, normal people with no abilities to Immortal Palace Alliance is like lowly ants is to giant elephants. They won’t even be able to expend their stamina." The old woman answered seriously.

Julie processed the information with a sense of doubt.

"All the telekinesis elites in Immortal Palace Alliance have a Secret Technique. They can flood the space around them with an aura of intimidation, anyone who saw them would be deeply affected physically and mentally, some may even collapse. With that ability to intimidate, swarms of enemies doesn’t even worry them." The old woman sighed. "But at least we got that book. Through my transfusion of its telekinetic power to you, you have acquired great power, but you yet to learn to control it."

"I understand, Teacher. I will work harder." Julie nodded in commitment.

"Glad you understand," Old woman stroked Julie’s face in endearment. "I know it’s hard for you. You’re only nineteen, but this responsibility was thrusted upon you…"

"I’ll be okay." Julie tried hard to look nonchalant. "Teacher and the others were the one who were stressed out. All these years you have been fighting Immortal Palace Alliance unbeknownst to normal humans, no one have seen your sacrifices and hard work. In comparison with you, what’s this little stress I’m taking?"

"You don’t know… This was our fight, the clash of our ideology…" The old woman murmured. "It’s late. Time to rest. Remember, when you intercept the Immortal Palace Alliance, you must lead them to somewhere remote, it is impossible to not hurt the normal people around accidentally with the power of your fight. Once a telekinesis elite uses his strongest form, even the elites of normal people will not be able to take it. That is why you have to remember, no matter how strong a normal human is, only talent can withstand talent. Looking for help from friends might just hurt them."

"But my friend said there are Grandmaster of Combat-level fighters amongst the Argentists, maybe…"

"There were already countless of Grandmasters of Combat who lost their lives to the Immortal Palace Alliance."

Julie finally shut up.

"Rest. You are our hope in this battle." The old woman softened her expression and caressed the girl’s hair.

"Yes, Teacher."

　　*******************

Top floor of Hotel Coconut Tree, Luxury Suite.

Garen stood in the center of the room, his arms raised to shoulder height, resembling a cross. Eyes shut, his breath was slow. Together with his whitish gold skin, he looked like a standard metal statue.

Knock knock.

"Come in." He muttered without even opening his eyes.

The door was slowly pushed open and King of Nightmares Stephen sashayed in.

"Practicing again?"

"What is it?"

Closing the door, Stephen sauntered past Garen to the full length windows, pulled the curtains apart and looked downward.

"Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate has news from Palosa, interested?"

"Spill." Garen’s raised palms slowly moved toward each other in front of him, but wind started blowing in the room. The draft licked the thick black curtains, lifting them without stopping.

"Within the Immortal Palace Alliance, they’ve categorized their members to The Founders and The Comers." Stephen sat in a chair he set his eyes upon, "The Comers were members who joined after it’s been founded, like Duskdune Shura and former Weisman Admiral Griffith. The Founders were actually only two people, Flamingo and Sylphalan."

"What’s the difference?"

"A lot." Stephen grinned. "The Founders were said to be active internationally since decades ago. We weren’t even born yet. On the other hand, The Comers members have been changing for years."

"I thought Palosa and Sylphalan were both heavily injured in their fight?" Garen opened his eyes, confused. "I’ve seen Palosa’s power, even though that wasn’t his strongest persona."

"You don’t think his strongest state is his Indifference persona?" Stephen chuckled and shook his head, "His true strongest state has already been defeated in the battle with Sylphalan. The merging of the three personas, that’s his perfect state. Having three personas essentially means having three Palosa sharing one memory, heading toward three different directions in Martial Arts. The Virtue persona fights head-on, Vice persona utilizes tricks and deception, and Indifference persona merges them both. Only when the three meld together that Palosa will be at his strongest state. It was then that he was worthy of the title Holy Fist."

It was Garen’s first time hearing this explanation.

"No wonder. When I fought him, I felt White Bird Holy Fist lacked a sense of majesty."

"Someone senior told me before. In the Azure Continent, there was a yoga master. He witnessed Palosa in his Holy Fist form. According to him, every movement seemed to be made from Secret Technique. His 178 Secret Techniques are actually the special effects of his 178 Fist Techniques in Holy Fist form. Under normal conditions, they could only be activated with Secret Techniques." Stephen told him another secret.

"Every movement seemed to be made of Secret Technique… If that’s the case, what Palosa said…" Shocked, Garen thought about Palosa’s reply before he left.

"Who knew?" Stephen shrugged. "But you’re not bad too. Your title given by the entire Southern Martial Arts community, the next Holy Fist, Holy Mammoth Garen has already spread to the Northern Martial Arts Union."

"You’re pretty in touch with the situation within the Confederation."

"Can’t help it, the nation with the strongest, largest amount of Grandmasters of Combat, which fighter wouldn’t take notice? But my news was from Andrela. Palosa’s Holy Fist form got defeated, but Sylphalan is also in bad shape."

"This is an opportunity." Garen’s brow furrowed.

"Let’s see how this goes. Immortal Palace Alliance is made up of monsters, he might even have healed."

　　********************

Three days later, the expo started on schedule.

In a massive hall with golden ceiling and black floor tiles.

Black pillars erected on the floor, showcasing the treasures in a transparent glass cube in the center.

In the hall, hundred of black pillars like this held a single item each, with visitors fluttering about.

Garen is in his black suit. He was holding a glass of hot green tea and stood in front of a black pillar at the edge.

His gaze fell on a antique vase in the pillar.

The thin-necked vase was made of white porcelain and decorated with blue patterns. It looked like an enlarged medicine bottle with its ceramic blue willow pattern and pictures of human activities on its large body.

Several other antique lovers were admiring it in awe.

"This is a rare treasure from an ancient country from the East." An old man with a pair of golden glasses was staring at it in amazement. "This is a wine pot from that country. Why do they make a wine pot this pretty? It’s such a waste. I like the tribal utensils from the Fivestar Continent. They are so wild, so mysterious, so much more attractive." A noblewoman sighed from the bottom of her heart.

"The Ancient East does not only have porcelain bottles! There are other antiques full of detailed delicacy, and at the same time survived history. Many pieces have mystery woven into them as well, like that silver plum blossom candle holder over there…" The old man wanted to have the last say.

With hushed voices, both of them started debating. Soon after, other people joined in the debate.

Garen set his ears on the debates quietly. He circled around the hall, noticing that debates were spurring at almost every black pillar.

Some were discussing the authenticity of an item, some were confused about the true worth of a piece, some of them even got ready to buy pieces off of their original owners.

The expo had just started, but it’s already crowded with participation.

Garen didn’t see King of Nightmares and Andrela, they each have their own plans and execution style. The three were together because of a common goal, but the means to their ends took a vastly different approach depending on their personalities.

Chapter 189: Argent Mirror 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen strolled casually and occasionally looked at the antiques in the black pillars.

He left the one holding a hollowed out golden bow to walk to a row of railings at the edge of the hall.

Behind them were thicker black pillars with even more precious items.

Garen walked a few steps and stopped beside some college students.

These students wore blue and black uniforms, three guys and four girls. They seemed to be having an aggressive discussion about the treasures.

"Antas’ Blue Wing, it symbolizes freedom, joy, happiness, and the yearning for the perfect paradise in the skies. It’s a mythical item from Antas, only nobles are allowed to craft it," A girl with a blue ponytail claimed. "It’s impossible to appear in a lowly merchant family."

"Normally that is true, but this is different. Look here, that’s the famous Asha Mark from the famous Asha Business Alliance. You can also tell from the details here, here, and there." A white haired boy retorted gently but firmly.

"I think Karen is right, this item can not be simply crafted during that period."

"Maybe someone secretly constructed it for their own collection? Like how some rich dudes like to go to parties all night."

The students each took their sides, splitting into two.

Garen scrutinized the item they were debating about.

It’s a sky blue statue of a single wing. It’s about one meter tall, two meters wide, and looked as if it’s soaring. The textures of the feathers were meticulously sculpted. It’s like a real eagle’s wing.

With a single glance, Garen could already tell it was made with an imitation style Old Man Gregor had talked about. He couldn’t go close to it, but there was a tiny section of the base that made him suspect its authenticity.

Subconsciously, he frowned slightly, his gaze stopping at the crack-like fissure on the base. It didn’t look like it cracked by itself, more like someone made it so and left an "S" shaped mark.

"You saw it?"

A white haired gentleman noticed where Garen fixed his eyes on. He was wearing a tuxedo and stood straight commandingly. He stopped by Garen and gave the Blue Wing and once-over.

"The mythical wing that symbolizes freedom and paradise, but it’s only a fake." The gentleman sighed.

"I was not so sure myself, I didn’t expect you to be so sharp, sir." Garen smiled humbly.

"No, you’re already pretty good." The old man shook his head, "How much do you know about the Antasan Civilization?"

"Not a lot, I’m afraid. I’ve only read a little here and there in some books." Garen picked out some information he knew about the civilization and listed it to the old man.

The gentleman became more interested as he listed on.

"That’s quite a bit that you knew. Tell me, from which class do you reckon this imitation was trying to imitate?"

"From the texture and the sculpting, I’d say it’s by small time merchants who wanted to add to their collection." Garen didn’t try to sugarcoat his thoughts.

"It can’t be. If it were for the collection of small time merchant, how would they dare to include the royal coat of arms?" The old man shook his head again.

"The royal coat of arms does not mean anything."

"You don’t understand how strict the law was then. Even using a noble’s family symbol callously could get you onto the guillotine, let alone the royal coat of arms." The old man said seriously.

"Then you do not understand the uniqueness of the situation. If I’m correct, this imitation was made during a time of special circumstances when Antas was already near its end, the power structure is failing, and the royals no longer has any real power over the commoners." Garen disagreed.

"From where did you infer its specific creation year? After all, this is a fake. How would you know the imitators wouldn’t just make it up as they go?"

"Obviously the wing looks like it’s about to take flight, almost all of the Blue Wings you can find look like that, but did you notice? This has a little hesitation and weight to it, right here…" Garen pointed at the root of the feathers. "Do you see the shape? This is a red hawk’s wing."

"Red hawk?" The old man had not noticed what the original models of Blue Wings are.

"Blue Wings, Royal Sculptors used to base it on the blue hawks that were bred in the palace. There are pretty much no blue hawks outside of the palace, so people can only base their imitation on the red hawk wings which are the most similar. Unfortunately they are still slightly different. Furthermore, only during that period would Picardian sculptors use red hawks to imitate royal objects." Garen shook his head.

"Very detailed observation, you surprised me with your knowledge. But you also left out one spot. The inscriptions on this item." The gentleman was still not convinced.

"There are three symbols on the inscription, signifying the three sculptors. And it just so happens that I know this one. This one belongs to the most famous Blue Wings Royal Sculptor Robert Niggen."

"That doesn’t mean anything, sir." Garen disagreed.

"What do you think?" The gentleman turned aside to a female student who listened to their conversation.

This was a girl wearing blue and black uniform with a white denim pants. She was so entranced by their conversation that she didn’t realize the gentleman was talking to her.

"I… I think both points were valid."

"Don’t be scared, child." The old man softened his voice, "I saw your gaze just now. Among all these people, only the three of us noticed the few weird points about this Blue Wing. Why don’t you share your thoughts on it?

Garen observed the girl from her side.

She looked about eighteen to nineteen, fair skin, silky shoulder-length dark hair. The way she stood highlighted her purity of heart. She had long lanky legs and rounded hips, as shown by the thinness of the material she was wearing.

"You’re too anxious." The old man shook his head, "Take a breath. From I can see, you’re a student from the Picardi Women’s College, isn’t it? You are already not bad if you can recognize that much, believe in yourself."

Garen and him were both staring at the girl, waiting for her to speak.

The girl shifted her weight in discomfort.

"Both of you have your points, but I think… this Blue Wing is by a Royal Sculptor during a peace period. If I remember correctly, the Royal family gifted slightly different Blue Wings to descendents who are going away to their territory…"

Before she could finish, she heard a soft clap from in front of her,

She looked up and saw the two agreed with her.

"You noticed something that we couldn’t." The old man smiled. "I can’t believe such knowledge came from a normal schoolgirl. Do tell me your name, child."

"My… my name is Ophany…" The girl hid her face with her hair in embarrassment, not knowing how to accept the praise.

"Ophany," The old man produced a black card from somewhere and gave it to her. "Take this, it’s my name card."

Ophany took the name card thoughtlessly, but there was nothing on the card aside from a big symbol of an eye.

"Keep it safe, when you’re in a pinch, this card will bring you luck." The old man told her mysteriously.

Garen looked at the old man for being cryptic.

Obviously he’s some sort of important person, seeing how his bodyguards spreaded out to look after him.

"Congratulation, miss Ophany, looks like this old sir isn’t just a normal expo-goer." He smiled at the girl.

Ophany blushed, not knowing what to say.

"What about you? Why do you act so mature? Teenagers should look like teenagers." The gentleman looked at Garen with admiration, "Your knowledge is on par with mine. I wouldn’t expect the younger generation to produce someone like you." Another black card. "For you."

Garen smiled looking at the gentleman’s card. He was about to say something.

"Who goes there!" Someone yelled outside the expo. "Alert!"

The voice was cut off.

The crowd in the expo started to make noise. People were worried, and those with bodyguards quickly surrounded themselves for maximum protection.

The gentleman was the same. Within seconds, seven bodyguards with different clothes surrounded him, and under his orders, kept Garen and the girl under their protection.

"Don’t move." The gentleman told Garen and Ophany calmly. They both nodded, looking slightly worried.

"Micah, go check out the situation, be careful." The old man told one of his bodyguards.

"Yes sir." The man with a tall nose nodded and left the protection circle, and slowly make his way to the entrance from the wall, his gun drawn.

Several other people were doing the same thing.

Garen faked his serious and worried face.

Looks like it’s going to start. He didn’t want to stand out so early, or else he’d have wasted his advantage being hidden in the crowd.

He checked out the situation through the gaps between the bodyguards.

The other students were ushered into a corner by a middle-aged man, looking either curious, fearful, or excited.

Several other middle-aged men looked grumpy. They drew their guns and gave out orders to their subordinate to maintain order in the hall with the cooperation of the staff.

The security captain also stood forward. He led his teams to calm the emotions of their guests, while sending a team outside in full caution.

Chapter 190: Argent Mirror 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Outside the expo, at the plaza between Hotel Coconut Tree and the convention center the expo was held in.

Yellow street lamps littered the circular gray plaza. Half of them has already died down, damaged.

Two white pillars were erected in the plaza, each measuring about fifteen meters tall.

There were two bronze statues on the top of the pillars, one of a girl of nobility with a horse whip, the other a knight on a majestic warhorse.

Below the pillar with the knight, some security guards with blue uniform gathered around two guards who fainted, examining them.

Some passersby rounded up to watch. It looked somewhat crowded.

Creak!

Two police cars with black and white stripes sped into the plaza and stopped. Two officers stepped out of their vehicles. The one in lead had a strict face and a fake eye emphasized by the unnaturally white eyeball.

He saw the few bystanders in a crowd. His real eye twitched when he saw a beautiful lady in white miniskirt in the lead, and marched toward the fainted.

"Move aside, give way!"

The other two policemen made way for him.

The man with a fake eye marched near the woman, and stopped for a split second.

"Well somebody’s moving quick." He grunted.

"We aren’t interested in your little tricks." The lady retorted, "Looks like somebody else is confident."

"Not as much as you are." Fake Eye smirked. Both of them moved away from each other, he approached the people who fainted and started examining them.

The woman with white miniskirt did not stay for long. She left the crowd with several other people.

One of them was an old man with walking stick. "Are they all here?" He eyed Fake Eye from afar.

"Almost. The five main forces are here. When should we start?" She nodded.

"Let’s observe for a little," The old man’s voice was soft, but it was clear as day to the woman. "The main problem here is not the random party starting a riot. Our main opponent is still the Argentists. Watch them with constant vigilance."

"I know, Katyusha and Wendy are waiting for them. Even though our main opponents are the Argentists, we can’t let the small fries get the prize." She smiled.

On the other side, a group of expo-goers walked out. Among them, Katyusha stood behind two of her friends and watched.

"Let’s go. It’s boring stuff. Some people want to break in, but the guards chased them away, but they were also downed." The woman with brown hair in front of her said. "This place is messy."

"It is messy," The girl at the back echoed, she had a short and dulled red hair, her face wasn’t memorable, and she looked like she hasn’t been getting enough sleep with the dark circles on her eyes. She was dressed like a thug on the street.

"I’ve lived here for many years, there were stuff happening almost every week. I wonder if the two guards were okay, but let’s get back in. Fake Eye is here, nothing bad will happen once he’s here."

She was one of the collectors who sold the host of the expo one of her collections. However, different from the other collectors, she only qualified the entrance by selling her item. She only pretended to be interested to try and find a rich man for herself.

Katyusha looked at the red haired girl. If she wasn’t the original owner of the Mirror of Secret Texts, she wouldn’t have tried to get close to her.

The other girl is one of the other main force, Wendy.

The three were going to turn back into the expo.

A dull thud.

"Duck!" A man roared.

Boom!

A ball of golden flame burst out from the center of the plaza. White smoke accompanied by the shockwave flooded everywhere. Innocent people screamed and tried to escape, two cars nearby even got flipped over. Several horses got scared. Neighs and tyre screeches filled the air near the plaza.

Within a second, the peaceful plaza were disrupted with chaos.

Six or seven people laid strewn about, it was impossible to tell if they’re dead or alive. As the white smoke dissipates, several figures in white dashed soundlessly toward the entrance of the expo.

"Now!" At the same time, three people by the woman in white miniskirt zoomed toward the back door of the expo.

Beep! Beep!

Alarms went off from inside the hall.

　　***************

Inside the hall.

Garen was standing in the middle of the bodyguards when the explosion happened followed by the alarm. He knew someone had made a move.

Chaos broke out in the hall. A few people by the entrance got knocked down first. White figures zipped in and toward the black pillar in the center.

"Die!"

A low growl. Three people rushed at one white figure each, and zoomed out of sight to fight them.

Bang! Bang bang!

Some people started shooting, sounds of guns firing started getting more intensive.

Yelps and screams filled the rampageous hall. Some visitors with their own bodyguards hid in corners followed by people who wished to get protection.

The hall quieted soon after. The hall packed with people suddenly became empty. On the ground, there were a dozen of bodies, everyone else had retreated to the corners to hide.

Garen noticed Ophany’s paleness, her eyes were overflowing with fear and worry. Her gaze shot outside, worrying about her schoolmates.

The other university students crouched not far from there, hiding behind some of the pillars. It’ll be safer. Two of the girls were sobbing quietly.

Everyone was on the floor, so no one were able to see outside. Only a few bodyguards kept watch around them.

Blows were exchanged and guns were fired from inside and outside of the expo. When some of the attacks hit the walls, they even shook violently.

Soon, a white figure escaped, leaving blood trails and roaring his opponent behind. One of the windows at the side of the hall was broken as he escaped, leaving broken glass on the ground.

"He took the thing! Stop him!" A huge black man punched a hole in the wall with his bare fist and chased after.

Tut tut tut tut tut…

Submachine guns were fired, sandwiching some shots from shotguns, it’s like several parties were engaged in gunfights all at the same time.

Outside, two opposing forces were in trigger happy mode with their weapons, the box containing the Mirror of Secret Texts kept changing hands between the two parties.

The three Argentist elites were all Grandmasters of Combat, by their side, they have several Level three Sharpshooters. Katyusha and her team were fighting off the other party who wanted the Mirror of Secret Texts, all four of them were disciplined and speed-focused Sharpshooters acting harmoniously with each other. They don’t have the auras of a Grandmaster of Combat, but with their own weapons, they were able to keep the Argentist elites at bay.

The main shooter was the woman in white miniskirt. She was holding two enlarged silver pistols and moved at high speed while she fired at the three Grandmasters of Combat. The power of the pistols were so strong, holes as large as fists appeared wherever the bullets landed.

On the side of the Argentists, the black man as imposing as a tower led the fight. He held a black shield, blocking every bullet coming his way, and pushing away any opponents who managed to get here.

"Give up, Chris!" The black man blocked a bullet from the woman with white miniskirt and took a few steps backward. His shield had a small dent in it where the bullet hit. "Even if you managed to secure the item, you will never be able to get it out of this city!"

"Unwavering Shield Marvin, you don’t have a say in whether we are capable of bringing it out of the city." The woman sneered. She continued shooting with one hand and magically changed the magazine with the other. "With just three Argentists, you won’t be able to stop us."

"Hmph, don’t you understand? We could exhibit it, we already have necessary preparation for situations like this!" The black Grandmaster of Combat smirked.

"So you are prepared, but did you think we didn’t?"

Boom!

Another grenade exploded.

The box with the Mirror of Secret Texts was blasted into the air.

None of the both parties glanced at the box, but instead started barraging the other side with attacks, obviously planning to do the other side in while they’re distracted.

Clink! Clank!

Marvin’s charging figure stopped, his shield had yet again stopped another bullet. Both of them were planning the same thing.

At this moment, the box in the air started its downward motion.

Fwoosh!

A barely audible draft of wind sounded. A black figure leaped from behind Chris toward the box like a swallow in flight.

On the other side, two white figures charged out from behind Marvin, arriving at the box at the same time.

Thump! Nobody managed to catch the box, leaving it to drop on the ground.

"The Argentist bishop?" One of the white figure yelled. All three of them fell backward, landing on the ground.

The two figures in white stepped on the stone tiles several times before they could neutralize the impact they received, leaving a few black marks on the tiles.

It was only until they regained their balance that other people could see their faces. They were two middle-aged man and woman. They had a winding black snake stitched on each of their right sleeves.

"Aren’t you at the Fivestar Continent? How could this be?" The man in white growled unbelievably.

The black figure stood still, revealing a middle-aged man with black hair. He looked like an average person, but his skin glimmered silver, and his most prominent feature was a dark red mark on the left of his face, burning like a crimson fire.

The man stood with his hands at his back, and calmly stared at the two on the opposite.

"Trying to snatch my possession at my place? You were pretty daring."

He shuffled left, leaving the wall behind him with two deep bullet holes.

Chapter 191: Argent Mirror 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Enough talk! I've heard about you for a while now, now let us Black Snakes get acquainted with you!" The woman of Black Snake couple yelled with a shrill. "Attack!"

In an instant, the plaza echoed with guns firing and bullets wheezing. Gunners swarmed the plaza from all directions and fired at the Bishop of the Argentists, who dodged the bullets with ease.

The Black Snake couple brandished their guns, attacking the Argentists with a series of aimed shots. Together with Chris' attacks, they managed to keep the Argentists at bay.

Only the Bishop managed to avoid the attacks simply by stepping left and right. He walked straight toward the box despite the bullets wheezing at him.

Determined to win, the Black Snake couple threw their weapons away and charged at him.

The three exchanged blows in the plaza. Within seconds, the Black Snake woman was hit by a palm strike and shot away, the Black Snake man was also pushed back. Soon, the Bishop would have caught the box.

An obviously empty bullet thudded against the floor tile in front of the box. Weirdly, the bullet did not pierce the tile, instead it rebounded straight at the Bishop's face.

Bam!

The bullet exploded, spreading a flame that devoured the Bishop.

The Black Snake female smirked and wiped away the blood on her forehead. "This is my first injury this heavy, let's see you dodge this Snake Bite Bullet!"

The explosion blasted the box high up once again, this time toward the other direction.

The Bishop grunted and covered his face, but alas, he suffered a minor burn. "Die!"

He ignored the box and bolted at the two Black Snakes.

Both sides were the strongest elites in Picardi, each having their own fame and followers. The Argentist's influence was strong in Picardi, and Black Snake was a top assassin syndicate in neighboring countries. None of them had a simple background, anyone from their organizations would be considered fierce and ambitious. Meeting here was definitely not planned.

Both of the parties have long been trying to fight each other, this was a good opportunity to do so.

Black Snakes are assassins with a kamikaze attitude. When they saw the Bishop charging at them, their eyes reddened and charged back at him.

By that time, some of the lesser underlings had already retired from the battle, leaving the more witty, agile fighters on field with their injury.

The main battlefield was for the leaders. A pillage-turned-head on fight was not expected by the Black Snake. However, Black Snake wasn't planning to avoid the Argentists either. They weren't good at surprise attacks, but they are famous for their ruthlessness within the other assassins nearby.

Both parties intertwined exchanging blows mixed in with the occasional gunshots, somehow forcing the battle into a stalemate. All over the ground were numerous debris and scraps broken in the fight. Street lights kept falling after fracturing.

Boom!

Flame burst between the three leaders, forcing them to separate once again.

Regaining balance, they were prepared to start the assault again.

A sudden red silhouette shot at the box with the Mirror of Secret Texts.

"Don't you dare!"

The Argentist Bishop and the Black Snakes yelled simultaneously in fury. Trying to snatch the box in front of the three of them? That's a provocation of the highest degree.

Without much thought, the three attacked the figure in red. The Bishop rushed over and the Black Snakes fired two shots aimed at the red figure.

Boom!

The two shots exploded together, causing two balls of scarlet flame to erupt in mid-air.

At the same time, the Bishop's hands struck at the figure. He wore silver gloves on his palms, bringing a storm-like gust with him. Striking the figure in the chest, he seemed to want to rip his opponent into two halves.

Psst!

A sword shone red.

Argh!

The Argentist Bishop yelped and took a few steps back, his steps quicker than before.

At the same time, a fine red line spread outward, reaching the Black Snakes in an instant. They both cried aloud before furiously retreating.

The fire slowly dispersed revealing a sharp-featured man standing there in stillness. In his hand was a red long sword with runes sparkling like diamonds.

Shing!

Placing the sword in front of him, he used his hand to caress the sword.

"Worlds will moan, Sprites begone!"

Fwoosh!

His eyes glowed a fluorescent red.

A terrifying huge psychic explosion burst out like a storm ravaging the plaza.

If there were people who can see the source of this outburst, they would have seen a red peacock. Its massive tail feathers flowing gently in the storm, spraying crimson sparks periodically.

　　***************

Inside the hall, Garen suddenly feel a massive mental threat from outside. It felt familiar.

"Maybe it's time…"

He scanned around at the other people.

The gentleman was mumbling something under his breath while holding an item with one of his hands.

The girl Ophany stood behind the gentleman uncomfortably, looking a bit fearful.

Sounds of bombing and guns firing slipped in occasionally, scaring the survivors from even moving. Most of them were elites from the city itself, some were even higher government officials.

Placing their trust at the government and the Argentists, everyone were waiting for the chaos outside to subside.

Garen calmly observed the rest of the visitors, not finding Andrela and King of Nightmares. He wondered where these two went.

"Don't worry, trust the government." Garen looked at the scared Ophany and soothed her in a soft voice.

Ophany gulped, nodding in anxiety.

"Not bad. This is the headquarters of the Argentists, they will soon arrive to calm the situation here." The gentleman nodded in agreement. "Trust the government, that's a good one." He stared at Garen with appreciation with a sense of 'not bad, I expect great things from you'.

Garen was dumbfounded with the comment and was prepared to step out to join the battle.

A few streams of mental pressure only slightly less than Flamingo's surged into Garen's senses. It was so subtle, only a Grandmaster of Combat was able to detect through their enhanced senses.

"Flamingo! I didn't expect you to be sent!" A tiny voice belonging to an old woman came from outside.

"It is him." Finding the answer he seeked, Garen hesitated, and decided he would follow the original plan, which is to wait for Andrela's signal. He calmed himself and continued to wait.

　　****************

Outside, Katyusha and the owner of the Mirror of Secret Texts hid behind the wall behind the entrance, peeking out with caution.

The situation at the plaza was as if a bombing plane barraged, scattering rubbles, soil, and earth everywhere. The pillars had fallen with the statues left at the side. Black street lamps were sliced neatly in halves. The air was reeking with the thick scent of gunpowder and artillery fire.

Both Black Snake and Argentists were heavily injured by the man who appeared out of nowhere.

The only one left from the five main forces of Black Snake was her. Wendy and the other three either escaped or were killed. The two Bosses of Black Snake were also badly wounded, having both their left arms cut off in an instant during the battle.

Not only them, the Argentists had it worse.

The one with the title Unwavering Shield, the black man Marvin, as well as two other Grandmasters of Combat got knocked down during the ring of red line and haven't been able to get back up.

The Bishop of the Argentists had his palms cut off by the wrist, his blood spilling out from his sleeves. He glared at Flamingo with fear and disbelief.

This man, even with so many elites attacking him at once, was able to cut them off one by one, as if he was killing chickens. The illusionary red light possess extremely damaging powers. It didn't matter if it were bullets, explosions, or melee, as soon as the red light flickered, any incoming attacks were nullified.

In front of this man, all of the elite fighters were just like livestock, he could kill any one of them any time he wanted.

As if that wasn't enough, anyone who saw him was immediately paralyzed, with the exception of the Bishop and the two Black Snakes.

If it weren't for the newcomers, they would have all been exterminated.

"Flamingo! I didn't expect you to be sent!"

About ten meters in front of Flamingo were four old people dressed in black. Beside them, a good looking brunette girl wore two golden metal claws, lengthening her reach like ten cold steel spikes.

The one speaking was a gray haired woman. She stared at the white haired man coldly, as did the other three. They all had a dark gold crest on their chests in the shape of a Three-headed Hydra.

"You again." Flamingo frowned, as if he recalled unpleasant memories. "Last time you almost made me fail, how dare you appear in front of me again."

"The Argent Mirror is not something you can touch." The old woman said, "Julie, all yours."

"Leave it to me." The brunette answered.

　　****************

Some time had passed as Garen hid in the hall. He could hear the gradually softening sounds from outside. The backup forces from before had somehow disappeared, he heard nothing from them since.

Subconsciously, he touched the spot on his chest where the book pendant had hung. He had previously hid it in the hotel room safe together with the Golden Sword Throne out of worry that it may be destroyed.

"What's happening? Why has no sound came from outside?" The old gentleman asked, confused.

"Not sure, but let's not go out yet." Garen shook his head, "If it was safe to go out, someone would have come looking for us."

"You look pretty composed. Not bad. After all this is over, I'll let you have some of my wines I'd just gotten from Tina's Winery." Not one scent of worry was seen on the old man's face.

Bam!

Before he could finish, the entrance door as well as the wall around it was blasted open by an invisible force, revealing the situation from outside.

Chapter 192: Argent Mirror 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Everyone inside the expo hall buried their heads. Only after the smoke and dust had cleared, then people were able to start making out the situation inside the hall.

A white haired man with a long red sword was walking towards the hall, and in front of him was a brown haired girl struggling to get up on her feet amidst the rubble.

Obviously the main entrance wall was blown open by this girl just now.

What was even more shocking was how the hall was now littered with heavily injured or comatose people. Corpses and limbs were also all over the place. Amongst them there were some Argentists and some folks of unknown origins. The floor was filled with shrapnel and bullet marks, the air was thick with the scent of gunpowder.

The crowd in the hall suddenly turned into a mess as some tried to run through the exit formed by the explosion early, but were quickly shot to death by a quick succession of silenced bullets.

"Ish….looks like our drinks tonight will have to wait another day," the old man took a deep breath and mumbled under his breath.

"Didn’t you say to trust the government?"

Garen asked bemusedly.

"That belief depends on situation," The old man balked at Garen talking back at him,"you little one, later just watch out and follow me. We must find a way outta here, this place is too dangerous! Damnit, why did this have to happen on my rare day off?! What shit luck do I have to deserve this!"

The girl called Ophany squatted by the side, upon hearing the two of them joking about in a situation like this, her heart started to calm down.

The crowd now all stared at Flamingo, nobody dared to raise their voice or breathe too loudly in fear of attracting his attention.

While Garen was talking to the old man earlier, Flamingo had easily killed two assassins who attempted to attack him, all while casually blocking a rain of bullets.

Through all of this, his steps never changed, he continued walking towards the girl.

Four old men’s bodies were covered in blood, two of them had their heads and bodies in separate spots, while the other two were heavily injured.

Flamingo looked at everyone in the room calmly. Not too far away, a few police cars started to stop around the perimeter, but none of the policemen who got off dared to come close. With Flamingo as the epicenter, nobody dared to walk to close to him within a hundred meter radius, and nobody could leave either. It was as if an invisible force field had covered this entire area.

"What a pity. Is this your surprise for me? By suppressing my blood’s power?" Flamingo said plainly,"in my eyes, you are all like worthless trash. Nothing but stronger ants."

Julie struggled to get up.

The monster in front of her had gotten stronger again. Compared to the time they fought in the Water City Moyako, Flamingo’s sword was now at least twice as tough as his last one. It was even able to slice through her telekenisis abilities.

"You still talk a lot of crap, when all you want is to just show off how powerful you are." As she spoke, blood flowed out from her mouth, making her look incredibly miserable.

"We’re done, we’re so done. The more we know the more likely we’re going to be killed," the old man’s face started turning bitter, even his bodyguards were starting to lose their cool.

"Boss, isn’t that a little un-auspicious to say?" one of his bodyguards asked.

"We’re about to die, screw being auspicious!" the old man’s face scrunched up.

"We can’t be sure, who knows maybe he’s a good guy, and it’s because of what happened that’s why he did what he did," Garen interjected.

"Does his face look like a good guy to you?!" the old man was dumbfounded.

"Well, I know that you shouldn’t judge a book by its cover."

Garen suddenly smiled softly like he just noticed something, he reached out his right hand softly and his skin was glowing a soft white gold.

"Excuse me, I need to go now, I have something to do."

The old man and Ophany looked at Garen stunned, especially the old man who was still dumbfounded, he opened his mouth like he wanted to say something.

Ding!!

Suddenly a loud ring echoed from a distance.

In a split second, Garen disappeared from where he stood and turned into a shadow, alongside two other mysterious white shadows, they all dashed towards Flamingo.

The three shadows appeared almost at the same time in front of Flamingo. Boom!! A big ball of fire exploded from Flamingo’s body.

"You lot!!!" in the explosion, one could hear Flamingo angrily yelling.

The three shadows dispersed and stood in a circle around Flamingo, turning into three humanforms. Turns out it was the King of Nightmares Stephen, Andrela and Garen.

The three of them had completely surrounded Flamingo.

The King of Nightmares excitedly licked the dagger in his hand.

"Since you’re out, don’t go back."

"It’s you!" Flamingo’s pupils shrank, like he recognised the King of Nightmares. Right now, Flamingo’s left arm hung limp on the side of his body, seemingly broken after the initial hit.

"If I want to leave, none of you can stop me!" Flamingo did not spare any more chatter, and dashed backwards in retreat, in the direction of Garen.

"Divine Statue, Thunder Sprint!"

One of Garen’s hands expanded and turned into a greenish black colour, swinging directly in the direction of Flamingo.

Boom!!

His palm and Flamingo’s sword collided and burst into a ball of sparkles. Flamingo was pushed back by the impact, leaving behind two footprints dragged through the floor.

At this point, nobody cared about the Argent Mirror anymore, everyone had their eyes on the four of them fighting in the middle.

The King of Nightmares and Flamingo were having a arch nemesis reunion, their eyes were especially filled with anger towards each other.

"You guys stay out of this, let me handle this alone!" Stephen raised his hand, indicating Garen and Andrela to stand their ground.

"Go ahead," Garen shrugged.

"Don’t take too long," Andrela stood in attention, blocking one of Flamingo’s potential escape routes.

For someone as powerful as Flamingo, nobody could be sure how many secret techniques he had hidden under his sleeves. Folks like the King of Nightmares, Flamingo and Sylphalan had reached such a level that even if they fought each other, they would not be able to be completely sure that they could kill their opponents.

To be able to defeat each other and killing each other were two distinctly different levels of difficulties. Just like the time when Flamingo teamed up with other skilled fighters to hunt and catch the King of Nightmares, while they were able to almost defeat him, a slight mistake still allowed him to break through and escape.

Julie studied the arena and was stunned. Earlier she was struggling to even put up a fight against Flamingo, yet here he was being surrounded by these three bastards so easily. Looks like the trio had come just to hunt and kill Flamingo. They had all forgotten about her existence at this point.

Killing Flamingo? An elder level member of the Immortal Palace Alliance?

She couldn’t make out their motivations, for the Immortal Palace Alliance were undefeated across the board, they ruled every land they stepped on, where did these people muster the stupid courage to even launch a hunt and kill operation against one of their elders?!

Julie instinctively went towards her teacher for answers. On the wall, half lying down against the wall, was the old woman. Like Julie, the old woman was also at a loss of words. Evidently, nobody saw this coming. If they had known that someone was coming to kill Flamingo, they wouldn’t have wasted their efforts on trying earlier.

"Garen, are you sure you want to become an enemy of the Immortal Palace?" Flamingo was struggling to defend, and looked absolutely miserable as he yelled at Garen between punches.

Garen’s face was unfazed, like he hadn’t heard him at all.

"Garen?" the old woman’s face suddenly turned into a shocked expression,"could it be…?" She started carefully studying Garen’s face,"didn’t the Old Man Gregor once say that he had no potential? How can this be?"

"Teacher, can you tell the origins of these three people?" Julie ushered up to the side of the old woman and whispered.

"I too, am unsure…."

"Teacher didn’t you once say that normal people would not be able to hold up against Telekenisis users like us? What’s happening now then?" Julie was filled with questions.

"I can’t be wrong, these three people are so powerful, they must have some hidden talent!" the old woman was certain she’d nailed it this time.

Hidden talent her ass that is….

Julie was helpless. Her teachers had spent too much time locked within their own confines, even with the truth right in front of their eyes, they still deny it, believing that one can only become powerful if they possess the talent at birth.

She saw that since amongst the original three elders, two were dead and one was injured, she was better off just standing where she was and observing the situation.

The old man who was still crouched on the floor looked at Garen with an expression like he was constipated.

"I actually discussed about antiquities for a half a day with a terrorist! I must be going mad!"

Ophany on the other hand, showed no signs of distress of fear.

"I feel that, that man is a not a bad man…"

"You’re still young, you still can’t see pass their facades hiding their evil side." the old man shook his head in disagreement.

"Boss, I think it is better if we retreat for now," one of the bodyguards carefully advised him.

"I dare you to move, I bet in a split second you will find your brains hollowed by bullets if you even try!," the old man grunted.

****************************

Garen stood alone in his part of the arena, occasionally blocking a stray shrapnel or two casually.

The way the King of Nightmares fought Flamingo was different from usual, it seemed as if Flamingo had been downgraded to an amateur from a master. The way he was swinging his sword was like a young boy just learning about swordsmanship for the first time. The Sword of the Sprites in Flamingo’s hand was twisting and turning, slicing nothing but air over and over again, like he was playing along in a play fight with Stephen.

However, Garen could tell from Flamingo’s strict face that he wasn’t giving way, instead he was pushed to a really tough spot by his opponent.

Unconsciously, Garen clenched his fists in pain. After blocking Flamingo’s sword with his bare hands earlier, he seemed to have sustained some minor damage to his fist. If he was still using the Giant Mammoth Secret Technique from back then, even if he was at the peak of his Body Hardening Technique form, he probably would not stand a chance in a direct hit like that.

"Oy, speed up! We’re running out of time!" Garen nagged.

The King of Nightmares did not respond, but he started speeding up his attacks.

Stephen’s body allowed him to attack from different angles as his arms could twist and turn like noodles. His eyes were even more mysterious, their beautiful blue hue were like the ocean, attracting the attention of anyone who looked at him, and subsequently distracting his opponents.

Garen and Andrela stared at Flamingo attentively, anyone at Flamingo and Stephen’s level would definitely possess an unusually resilient amount of life force. Especially some who has lived for so long, they must have a plethora of tricks to extend their own lives, should a small mistake be made, Flamingo could easily escape.

Clang!

Suddenly there was a loud noise, one of the stray gravel hit the metal box holding the Argent Mirror. An oval white and silver mirror slowly rolled out from inside the box.

"The Argent Mirror!" the old woman beside Julie exclaimed,"Julie!"

"Understood!" Julie’s body bent in aggression and dashed towards the mirror immediately.

Chapter 193: Truth 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Hmph!" Andrela scoffed, and turned into a shadow, appearing in front of Julie,"go away unless you want to die!"

The Argent Mirror was one of the trio’s objectives, he wasn’t going to let anyone else get it.

"The Argent Mirror is related to the Will of the Origin, if you acquire the secret technique in it you will also learn of the method to disassemble the Will of the Origin!" Julie explained hurriedly.

"Will of the Origin? What’s that?" Andrela asked with suspicion.

"It’s something evil and destructive. It can transform a person’s mental willpower and enhance physical limits. I don’t have time to explain. How about this, let’s work together. You want the secret technique, I just want to disassemble the Will of the Origin, so we can team up. How’s that?!" Julie answered rapidly.

Andrela studied the girl’s expression, and by the looks of the people behind her in such a dire situation, they had no reason to lie.

"We will be in charge of keeping the mirror!" with a quick swing of the tip of his sword, he threw the Argent Mirror into the air and caught it with his other hand,"give me a means of contacting you."

Julie hesitated.

"Give it to him Julie!" the old woman yelled from behind her.

"Fine," Julie revealed a red card and threw it at Andrela.

Andrela caught it, and was about to respond before suddenly turning around and dashing towards Flamingo in distress.

At the same time, Garen’s calm expression dropped as well, he stomped his feet onto the ground and took off in the direction of Flamingo.

Flamingo had turned mad of sorts, the Sword of the Sprites in his hand suddenly turned into a drizzle of red raindrops, pouring like a hurricane towards the King of Nightmares.

What was even more mysterious was that the runes on the sword itself suddenly lit up in a blindingly bright red light.

"Peacock!!" Flamingo jumped, and his body suddenly split up into three different shadows, each headed for one of the trio.

Clang! Clang! Clang!

The trio each took a step back, their bodies all hit by an unknown attack.

The King of Nightmares scoffed coldly, and lifted up a single piece of rock with the tip of his leg, with a loud bang it shot towards seemingly empty air in the sky. Mid-air, it suddenly collided with something that turned out to be Flamingo who was moving so fast that he had turned invisible until he was hit by the rock.

At the same time, Stephen snapped his fingers.

Loud roars could be heard from around the perimeter, over a dozen smoking rockets suddenly flew towards Flamingo.

Over a dozen shocked, but professional soldiers calmly lowered their rocket launchers, and proceeded to fire at Flamingo in frenzy with their sidearms.

They were unfazed by Flamingo’s aura of suppression at all!

Rumble!!

Suddenly there was a loud screech and rumble in the sky, a big ball of blinding yellow light shot through the sky. Along with it came a circle of white smoke that spread across the entire arena.

Before that settled, an invisible pressure seemed to press down from the sky.

Hum....

The pressure spread about like invisible bubbles across the entire battlefield in the direction of the trio.

The ground started shaking as well, causing the houses around to shake as well, the air twisted and turned, and even the fire was breaking and burning over and over again.

Pow!

Flamingo landed from the sky, and calmly knelt beside a silhouette that appeared out of nowhere.

The silhouette was wearing a black cloak, he slowly lifted up his head, pulling off his cloak’s hood to look at Garen.

"Long time no see, Garen."

"Sylphalan... you actually showed up."

Garen stood silently in the middle of the chaos that was erupting, looking at the cloaked man with a plain expression.

Garen slowly lifted up his arms.

Rumble!!

An aura as large and powerful as the pressure that had struck started spreading as well.

With him as the epicenter, everything within a radius of a hundred meters was now covered in wild winds in the color of white gold. The white gold air flowed around furiously, before gathering into a giant upper body humanoid that looked just like Garen.

This monstrous giant was made out of white gold, it had a height of tens of meters, so tall that its shadow alone covered over half of the arena. The aura formed giant looked like an exact copy of Garen’s upper body, it looked down on the crowd below with eyes that were filled with black space and infinite stars.

"Heh, heh. This is good, each of us gets one to fight." A slim man with a black beard jumped down from the upper floor. With a loud crash, he landed on the ground; as he landed, he emited a blue aura around him that formed an opaque mermaid that stood meekly between Garen and Sylphalan’s.

Boom!! Boom!! Boom!!

Multiple blasts of mental blows reverberated in everyone’s head.

Behind Garen, Andrela and the King of Nightmares had respectively formed their auras. At the same time, Flamingo released his massive red peacock aura again.

With Sylphalan and Garen at the heart of it all, an invisible aura faced a white gold half humanoid. Further away from them were the four smaller, and varying colored, smaller auras.

At this moment, no matter how little Andrela and the King of Nightmares wanted to admit, or how little Flamingo and Griffith understood, everyone had to admit that in this arena, only Garen was capable of fighting Sylphalan.

Regardless of the outcome, the both of them were on the same level now. This was proven simply by the sheer scale and force of both their auras, this was made out of pure energy, not just mental strength.

At this point, everyone that wasn’t a high level martial arts practitioner such as the pedestrians and policemen around the area, were all starting to get knocked out by the sheer force of the auras enveloping the atmosphere.

Only those who stood further away from the actual battle could roughly make out what was going on in the expo hall.

While normal people couldn’t see the aura forms, they were still intimidated by the way the six of them stood facing each other. The tension alone was a clear enough indication of the impending dangers.

The passed out policemen and onlookers were good enough evidence that this was beyond their logical comprehension.

In the hall, the old man looked at Garen and the lot afar with a perplexed face.

"Fuck me, could this be….the legendary...subsonic boom attack?! This is too much! Where is the government? Where is our beloved government? In this key moment why isn’t my dear government coming out to save the world?!" he was starting to utter gibberish,"just a quick shiver, and everyone around us has fallen, is this also the mythical Tiger Body Shake? The air of a king?!"

"What is this so-called Tiger Body Shake?" Ophany asked innocently.

"Small children who don’t know anything shouldn’t ask stupid questions!" the old man felt light headed now,"No, no, no, I must stay calm," he used all of his might to shut his eyes, and rubbed his temples in hopes of calming himself down.

Very rapidly, he led his small group of bodyguards and Ophany to hide in an even more obscure spot away from the epicenter of the battle. As the old man stared at Garen and the black cloaked man, he knew just how much danger they were all in; he was only joking in hopes of relieving the fears of the people around him.

The university student Ophany didn’t seem to be aware of how thick of a situation she was in,"Old Sir, I think we should try to sneak out of here!" she whispered.

"It’s no use, if we touch whatever’s covering this place, we will fall and die." the old man said as he pointed to a seven or eight people who had fallen without a sound while trying to sneak out of the area.

Ophany felt a chill run down her spine.

At this time, the old lady and Julie’s group had all moved to a corner to rest. The two old man whose heads and bodies had been separated also had their parts moved to a corner by Julie.

Studying the monstrous energy facing each other in front of her, the old lady’s face started to lose colour.

"It’s him...Sylphalan...he has finally come. Julie, if you see an opportunity you must help Garen! Who knew that the seed planted by Gregor so many years ago would grow into such a powerful being today." her gaze turned to Garen, while she was still hesitant, she couldn’t help but admire him,"what a pity. If Gregor was still alive today, he would be so proud and relieved to see how powerful this one has become."

"Teacher…" Julie’s face was red,"if I go, what will become of you all?"

"Don’t bother with us! None of us know for sure what that madman will do. If they start fighting you must try to help Garen whenever he needs it. He’s the one whose skin just turned into white gold!" the old woman desperately explained.

Julie clenched her teeth, seeing how serious her teachers were about this, she forcibly nodded.

The powerful auras were still facing off each other, pushing against each other ever so slightly, stirring up a mental hurricane between the streets and the hall.

Garen raised his right arm with its palm facing upwards. He lightly clenched the air. Boom! A bubble of white air blew up in his hands.

"I’ve finally caught you…" his whole body was like it had been dyed, as it glowed in white gold color,"this time, I will avenge the Elder properly."

Sylphalan was shocked to see their auras facing off each other as equals as he looked up at them,"I haven’t seen you in a while, and you’ve already grown to this level. I must say I do regret not killing you, but just a bit."

"You sure you can kill me?" Garen scoffed. He swung his arms about casually, as he did so, the Divine Statue behind him too followed suit in his actions,"today, we will settle all our scores once and for all!"

Garen lifted up his right hand, aimed it at Sylphalan’s group and made for a grab.

Boom!!!

A circle of shapeless aura exploded on the spot where Sylphalan stood.

"Let’s go!"

The three villains jumped up in response, avoiding the explosion by flying in the opposite direction.

"Trying to run?" Garen reached his hand out again and aimed at the three of them, forcing them to disperse with another grab.

Boom! Boom! Boom! Boom!

Like grabbing insects out of the sky, the giant Divine Statue kept going after Sylphalan and his two followers’ shadows.

"Attack!" Andrela bellowed, and dashed out with the King of Nightmares.

A black cross sword flew towards Griffith.

At the same time, the King of Nightmares casually, and soundlessly appeared in front of Flamingo.

"This is not a good place to fight," Flamingo commented coldly, as he looked up at the massive Divine Statue.

"I don’t think so," the King of Nightmares swung his arm, releasing millions of paper shreds. The shreds were like snow, floating across the sky in a beautiful dance, causing Flamingo to go into a daze.

Both Andrela and Stephen each caught up with their opponents and flew away to fight them respectively.

Leaving behind only Garen to face Sylphalan alone.

Chapter 194: Truth 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen stood on the same spot, his right arm reaching out over and over again in the direction of Sylphalan. However, they were all only catching air as Sylphalan skillfully evaded them.

"You planning to wear me out? But you have grossly miscalculated!" Garen smiled coldly. The strongest part of the Divine Statue Technique was in its ability to defend and heal. At the rate that Garen was healing, he could easily go on for dozens more hours.

Sylphalan took a backflip, and landed gracefully atop a lamp post.

"It’s like…." he mumbled under his breath while looking at Garen, his eyes revealing an inner mix of loss and struggle,"it’s really like….."

"You can run pretty fast!" Garen was still now. He knew that if Sylphalan was not willing to fight him, he couldn’t force him into it either. At this point, both of them were tough characters that were near impossible to kill. Just like Duskdune Shura, even if one of them were to sustain heavy injuries, they could still confidently pull out. All masters of combat have a secret trick under their sleeves for the express purpose of escaping let alone that this was Sylphalan we were talking about.

"No…" Sylphalan seemed to think of something, his expression changed suddenly,"you’re not like older brother, you ended up on my path?" he suddenly started laughing like a madman,"Truly! Truly I am the only one who is right!"

"Only I am right!"

"Only me!’

Sylphalan suddenly pulled back his invisible aura, and did an elaborate backflip flying towards the buildings behind him. With each step pushing off a building after another, he sped off in lightning speed so fast that even Garen couldn’t make chase. With the blink of an eye, Sylphalan was gone, only the distant silhouette of his body hopping between building erratically visible.

Garen looked at Sylphalan from afar, feeling a little pissed off. For a moment he thought he had Sylphalan, but the next he was gone. While he had managed to acquire the Argent Mirror, this but only his secondary objective.

He raised his hand casually, the white gold Divine Statue melted into golden fog and disappeared. Compared to the Giant Mammoth, the Divine Statue was at least twice more powerful.

Afterall, the Divine Statue technique was based off the Golden Statue sect, which once stood toe to toe against the Crimson Sand Sword Gate at its peak.

Not far away, there was a rumble, and in the midst of a massive explosion a red shadow appeared. Boom! There were sounds of glass shattering as the red shadow dashed through a few buildings and escaped.

The King of Nightmares tried to make chase, but still lost Flamingo.

"Damnit! He ran away!"

At the same time, Andrela appeared with a bitter face and a broken sword.

"I almost didn’t make it, thank heavens that guy ran away."

"Who knew that even with the three of us combined we still can’t match the Immortal Palace," Stephen looked defeatist,"if only Palosa was here…"

"Stop overthinking," Garen took a deep breath and tried to loosen up himself,"Palosa wasn’t here, the Immortal Palace also didn’t all show up. It’s too early to call the results. However all in all, we are definitely at a disadvantage against them."

"This is so underwhelming!" The King of Nightmares started cleaning up his wounds, apparently in that short fight he had been stabbed by Flamingo in his chest once. From the looks of his face, it wasn’t a small wound.

Garen also now understood that if all of them were pit head to head, they were definitely still not a match against the Immortal Palace. If today had been their final fight, even if they managed to shave the Immortal Palace by one or two members, they would do so at a hefty price. Perhaps they might’ve even all died.

This newly formed troop was simply too weak.

"Masters of combat at this level all have their own tricks to stay alive. Defeating them is easy, but to kill them entirely is next to impossible unless they’re suicidal." Andrela shook his head,"now we have the mirror, the Confederation is probably sending troops over now. We ought to leave."

The other two nodded, and the three of them leaped together in an instance, disappearing into the distance as three shadows.

"We should retreat too." the Old Woman clenched her teeth and bellowed as soon as Garen left. Julie helped the Old Lady up, and with the bodies of their dead comrades in hand, they disappeared into the shadows as well.

The remainder of people also started leaving.

At the corner of the hall, between the rubble of what used to be some pillars and statues, a man emerged from the dust looking horribly miserable.

With a body full of ash, and both arms visibly broken, it was the Bishop of the Argentists.

"I can’t believe that I, the great Bishop of the Argentists, would see the day where I had to act dead in order to survive!"

A few moments later, the Black Snake couple emerged as well.

"Aren’t we the same as well? Once we realized we couldn’t put up a fight we had to hide too!" the female Black Snake said,"if you’re so cocky, why don’t you bring the fight to them then!"

At this point, both sides had lost all intent on fighting each other after seeing what had transpired earlier. In retrospect, their abilities were just like how Flamingo put it: nothing but stronger ants.

"It’s just a stupid mirror, yet it attracted so many insane characters. Heck, even the Immortal Palace showed up!" the male Black Snake frowned as he studied the hall, seemingly in deep thought.

"What’s on your mind?" the female Black Snake looked at her man.

"No..nothing."

*************************************

In an open field, not too far away from the hall.

Beside an abandoned dirt road, stopped a black truck.

With a loud "KA CHA" the door swung open, out came Andrela, Garen and the King of Nightmares.

Andrela leaned against the door of the truck and swung out an oval white silver mirror.

"This is the Argent Mirror, it is also the Mirror of Secret Texts. Stephen, you should know how to use it right?"

He looked at the King of Nightmares.

Stephen nodded,"Of course. I’m still disappointed that I wasn’t able to severely injure Flamingo. Who knew that he wouldn’t even properly fight us, and just run away in the end!"

The King of Nightmares took the mirror over and studied its detailed carvings carefully.

"To unlock it will take some time. Before that happens, perhaps we can go take a look at that group that popped out of nowhere opposing Flamingo?"

"That old woman seemed to know me," Garen frowned, he reached out to take the mirror from Stephen’s hands. He couldn’t sense any hidden potential, which meant that item wasn’t one of those cursed antiquities.

As he studied the mirror, he seemed to hesitate.

"Those folks said that there’s something about the Will of the Origin in here? What’s that?"

"I’ve never heard of anything like that before," Andrela shook his head.

Even Stephen was baffled,"that’s why I said we should pay them a visit, they probably know more about this than we do."

Garen touched the pendant on his chest, it was starting to heat up again. It was heating up irregularly a lot lately for reasons unknown,"Do we have a means of contacting them?"

"It says so on the card."

Stephen took the mirror over again and studied it,"if we translate the runes and carvings on the mirror, it seems to say that the Hidden Text inside the mirror is a record for a secret sealing technique. It can seal up energy accumulated over time and convert it into a deadly blow when needed. However according to intelligence reports, the Immortal Palace found something similar once too, but I’ve never heard anything about a Will of the Origin."

"I think I might have an inkling of who that old woman is…." Garen finally found a piece of memory from a distant past that matched the face.

In the old man’s dolphin antique shop, he seen a woman bearing a similar face enter the shop.

He suddenly had a feeling that he was about find out where Sylphalan was very soon.

*************************************

In the night.

Following the address given by Julie, the trio quickly arrived at a small jungle by the suburbs.

In the middle of the jungle was a dried out well, this was the entrance as told in the card.

The three of them hesitated, but they could see some light coming from the end of the well. A man in black overalls climbed out from beneath.

"Please follow me. The teacher awaits you below," the young man greeted the trio respectfully.

The trio could feel that a lot was happening underground, they could even hear the occasional music reverberating from the well.

Following the young man, they took turns climbing into the well, then climbing into a corridor just about the height of a grown man by the left of the well. The corridor quickly opened up to a spacious rock basement.

The walls were made out of rectangular stone bricks that looked pretty well aged. By the corner was a black grand piano with a young girl in black clothes playing a tune on it.

The girl, was Julie.

The music started slowing down before coming to a halt as the trio entered the room.

"Teacher, they are here," Julie stood up and spoke to the other corner of the room.

It was only then that the Trio noticed that there was an old woman sitting on a black chair made out of ratan by the other corner. Her breath was almost silent, her presence invisible unless announced.

This was the same old woman who sustained heavy injuries earlier in the day.

"Something here makes me incredibly uncomfortable," the King of Nightmares frowned and sniffed with his nose before covering it with a white silk cloth.

"You have really sharp senses," the old woman smiled and nodded,"I still haven’t thanked the three of you for your heroic acts earlier today. Had it not been for the three of us, we probably would’ve suffered severe losses."

"You lost two of your elders, and that still isn’t a severe loss?" Andrela asked rhetorically.

"It’s not," the old woman nodded,"the two of them were just telekinetic surrogates, their hosts have already started recovering in a secret location. It’s just one severe injury, no big deal."

"Telekinetic surrogates? One severe injury isn’t a big deal?" Garen repeated her words,"looks like telekinesis is a lot more interesting than I thought."

"Three of you, please sit and we’ll talk."

The old woman served up three cups of coffee.

Chapter 195: Truth 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A few people sat in the rock basement. The King of Nightmares refused a chair by himself and instead went over to squeeze onto the same seat with Andrela. While they were both expressionless, one could easily sense the intimacy between the two.

He realized that everyone was puzzled, so he reached his hand to his face in a massaging gesture and very soon, a thin piece of human skin mask was torn off his face, revealing a beautiful feminine face.

He had suddenly went from a moustached gentleman, to a stunningly beautiful flat chested young lady.

Andrela reached his arm over around her waist, the two of them pecked each other like there was no one else in the room.

"Alright, let’s get talking. I heard from Garen that you said you know him?"

The old woman looked at Garen upon hearing this, and squinted her eyes at him.

"The truth is, I do know him, Mr. Garen Lombard."

She slowly lifted up the coffee and took a sip.

"The reason I invited the three of you over, is because I have news about the Argent Mirror that I wish to inform you all about."

The trio was silent, awaiting for her to continue.

The old woman stopped for a moment, and introduced herself.

"I am Zhaoxing Qin. Just like you guessed, I am from the east. My father and I are telekinetic experts from the east.

As for telekinesis, it is the manipulation of reality with one’s mind, it deals with the fundamental form of matter. To be able to wield it and master it, one must be one in a million possessing talents beyond logical comprehension."

"I have heard before that superpowers around the world tried researching something like this. They wanted to activate some inert human potential or something," the King of Nightmares said softly. At this point her voice was clear and high pitched.

"That was a long time ago, all they got out of it is a bunch of failures," Zhaoxing shook her head,"just as you’ve seen, the Immortal Palace’s elders: Flamingo, Sylphalan and all, are all masters in telekinesis. They were famous even at a young age, but as the years and decades passed they started to disappear into the shadows and eventually formed the Immortal Palace Alliance in hopes of absorbing the elites of every generation. However, nobody knows what their true intents are."

"Famous since many years ago? How old is Sylphalan anyways?" Garen cut her short and asked.

"He came here with my father, when my father arrived he was already 45 years old," Zhaoxing didn’t answer his question directly.

Garen frowned.

"I need to know if you knew a man named Gregor, he used to run an antique shop. What’s his relationship with Sylphalan.?"

Zhaoxing wasn’t surprised at all, it seemed like she was expecting Garen to ask that.

"We will discuss that in private later. That is related to one’s privacy, we can talk about the Argent Mirror first."

She reached out her index finger and used it to draw a small circle in the air.

An unknown invisible energy seemed to emanate in the air. From the mat on her knees, a thin thread floated up and started stitching itself in the air.

In less than ten seconds, it had formed a perfect copy of the Argent Mirror.

Andrela was shocked and sat stunned, squinting in disbelief.

The King of Nightmares however was plain faced, obviously she had experienced supernatural phenomena like this before.

As for Garen, he was totally unfazed.

"This is the so called Argent Mirror, I’ve made a copy to ease explanation." Zhaoxing looked at the copy in the air and sighed,"the Argent Mirror is a relic from ancient times designed for sealing. It is not a treasure, and it is definitely not a container of some secret technique. Instead…"

She stopped for a second,"...it is a tool for sealing willpower."

The trio was now incredibly engrossed.

"In ancient times, there were many telekinesis experts. Some were good, some were bad. The Argent Mirror was made to seal off evil intent and the will of evil thoughts," Zhaoxing explained.

"What would happen if it is unsealed?" Garen asked.

"The evil intent and willpower will contaminate all living organisms within a one mile radius. The kind of thoughts and willpower stored within here can turn a normal man into a ruthless dictator, wielding absolute power but also insatiable greed for power and blood. A man contaminated by the Argent Mirror’s unsealed intent can only be killed, and not defeated," Zhaoxing sighed again."the evil intent within is ranked according to different levels, the highest of which we’ve named the Will of the Origin. Aside from that particular one, there are also the evil intents of many powerful telekinetic wielders from the past. Their greed, lust, and ruthlessness, even their perverted interests are stored inside. Should it be unsealed, the potential for harm is exponential!"

"We can’t just trust what you say at face value. For what it’s worth, the Immortal Palace really wants this mirror. I refuse to believe that they’re unaware of its secrets, in fact they might be after exactly that" Andrela shook his head.

Zhaoxing lightly poked the copy in the air, and the mirror suddenly broke into many pieces, revealing a small ball in its heart.

"The Immortal Palace Alliance is a bunch of madmen. They’re hell bent on pursuing the path of the Blood Warriors. In pursuit of immortality, they’ve spent billions of dollars and years on research. However the Blood Warriors have all disappeared in the last era. In the last era, the Blood Warriors were defeated by other practitioners, and the battle of which they lost were recorded as myths and legends in our culture."

Zhaoxing pointed at the small ball floating mid air and said,"but I’ve digressed. Now back to this ball, this is the heart of the Argent Mirror. It contains an extraordinary amount of contamination potential. If it were completely unsealed, it will affect the thoughts of organisms far and wide. The Immortal Palace plans to allow one man to control and absorb this thing."

"What’s the benefit in doing so?" Garen looked at Zhaoxing.

"The evil intent and memories of hundreds of incredibly power people are stored inside. If the person who absorbs it is able to put up with the immense stress, he will receive the experience of some of the greatest fighters of our time. He would even know how they trained, what they trained, where they kept their money, with all that he who absorbs it will have access to an unspeakable amount of power and influence. However, whoever tries to do so will surely lose their mind and also according to legends, he would have also lose a great amount of his potential and life. On a good day he will live on with just schizophrenia, on a severe hit something called a Time Scar could even appear on the user’s body. The Time Scar will show the remainder of one’s life, and the amount will definitely be a staggeringly low amount." Zhaoxing explained seriously.

"From what we know, Sylphalan already absorbed one of the Argent Mirrors about half a year ago."

"As long as one absorbs it, one will get schizophrenia?" the King of Nightmares asked curiously.

"This is definite. Whoever uses the Argent Mirror, regardless of their personal willpower, or how powerful their base is, they will all suffer from permanent brain damage and thus schizophrenia. Some even turn into a different person altogether, like their own personality’s been completely drowned by the Argent Mirror." Zhaoxing replied definitively.

"That’s a pity, I was going to ask you to let me try it," the King of Nightmares was visibly disappointed,"but screw it, I’d rather not turn into a schizo."

"Sadly, only masters in telekinesis are able to absorb the Argent Mirror. Perhaps the three of you might possess some hidden talent that I could help activate?" Zhaoxing shook her head.

She looked at the trio sitting before her.

"To be honest, I asked you three to come here in hopes of convincing you not to unseal the Argent Mirror."

"We took the mirror with the sole purpose of discovering the ancient secret technique, and now you want us to give it up? Do you actually think that’s possible?" Andrela smiled.

"I know this might be asking too much, but this is relative to the lives of hundreds of thousands of people, maybe even millions across the planet. If just a thousand people are contaminated by the fact that you unsealed that mirror, their ill intent paired with the experience of the evil within, they will definitely take over the whole planet."

"This means if we want to unseal it we should do in a place where there is nobody?" Garen frowned.

"It’s useless, without an organism as a bearer…" Zhaoxing didn’t even finish before Garen cut her off.

"What if I found a butchery then?"

"Oh..a living organism which is too low levelled will just expand and die, their pre-death struggles will just further enhance the evil intents inside the Argent Mirror. If it were so easy, I would’ve gotten rid of it long ago." Zhaoxing replied.

"It sure is a fuss," Garen nodded,"what if we took used prisoners then? Criminals on the verge of their death, instead of executing them we will just expose them to the Argent Mirror’s ill intent and then kill them after."

"If that’s the case, you will need to kill way too many people…" Zhaoxing squinted.

"But there is a chance of success right?" Garen squinted back at her and sat up straight,"this sounds like a potential plan. So how many criminals will we need?"

"That’ll depend on how powerful the Will of the Origin in this mirror is," Zhaoxing did some conservative calculations and was suddenly stunned,"...at least ten thousand people…"

Julie who stood at the side turned pale, visibly shocked as well.

"Let me settle it," the King of Nightmares snapped her finger,"I’ll make up some cover story about some chemical fallout. It will be easy. But of course this is all taking into account that what you’ve told us so far is the truth."

Her words sent shivers down every body’s spine. The way she held so little regard for human life made it no wonder why governments around the world treated them like terrorists.

"I have no reason to lie to you. Plus, you’re the ones who came up with this plan," Zhaoxing shook her head.

"Let’s set this aside for now. The Argent Mirror stays with us, as long as we don’t unseal it we will be fine," Garen rose his hand to stop this topic,"that’s it for the mirror, we will continue after we have validated your words. For now, we need to talk about my personal issues."

Chapter 196: Truth 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Alright," Zhaoxing nodded, and looked at Garen,"follow me. Julie, please take care of our two guests."

"Yes teacher."

Zhaoxing stood up and headed towards a wall on the right side of the room. The wall suddenly rose up and revealed a stone door.

Garen followed closely as they went in one after another.

The door closed behind him, Garen was now in a quaint study room.

A few ash white shelves sat in a corner, while some small tables paired with black sofas and yellow lights on the wall. It was a simply furnished room.

"Sylphalan plans to head east. He knows you’re looking for him, so perhaps he’s running away from you, or maybe he has other plans, but he is already preparing a boat. Him running away from you today was not a coincidence."

Zhaoxing said that once they got in.

"What’s your relationship with the old man Gregor?" Garen asked.

"My mother is Sylphalan and Gregor’s sister. The three of them were perfect siblings until one day my mom died in an accident trying to save Gregor." Zhaoxing casually turned on a gas light on the small table, illuminating her’s and Garen’s face with a flickering yellow light.

"Sylphalan believed that it was all Gregor’s fault, so they fell apart. At that time, Gregor was incredibly handsome and very powerful. His position among telekinetic practitioners was just like the position of the Immortal Palace Alliance today. Sylphalan couldn’t fight him, so he distanced himself," Zhaoxing sighed,"Sylphalan seemed to have some sort of perverted affection towards my mother. Since the accident he started relentlessly pursuing greater and greater power in hopes of challenging Gregor one day. Finally, in the end, he killed Gregor."

Garen could sense that there was more to this, but the general summary seemed to be true.

"Sylphalan once had the opportunity to kill me, but he let me go, why?"

"He only has two lifelong objectives, one is to kill Gregor for revenge, and the other is to revive my mother," Zhaoxing said softly,"his relationship with Gregor was complicated. Everything he knew, he learned it from Gregor. Gregor was more than just his brother, he was his teacher. You are Gregor’s heir, so I believe he spared you for the sake of Gregor."

Zhaoxing shooked her head.

"Actually, Sylphalan went mad many years ago."

"I can see that," Garen nodded,"his mental state surely isn’t normal right now."

"So what is your objective?" Zhaoxing looked at Garen,"find Sylphalan and avenge Gregor?"

Garen sat down and cupped his face in his hands, he couldn’t come up with a response.

After a long silence, he finally spoke.

"Sylphalan killed Gregor, he also almost killed me once. I will find him, and I will kill him. This is my objective."

"Aren’t you interested to know if Sylphalan found the path of the Blood Warriors?"

"Do you know?" Garen laughed,"I don’t know anything about what you people call telekinesis. Even if he finds it, it has nothing to do with me, I’m not one of you."

"As someone who is able to achieve this level of power at such a young age, the three of you aren’t just ordinary people. I trust my guts, mere mortals would not possess talent like yours," Zhaoxing said definitively,"well? Would you like to test it?"

Garen hesitated.

"Sure, but how?"

"It’s very simple," Zhaoxing walked to the front of one of the shelves and took out a few books, revealing a hidden compartment in the back. From the hidden compartment she took out one thick book.

The book was covered in a black hardcover, and on the cover were some twisted text that Garen couldn’t recognize.

"This book.." Garen could however feel a sense of familiarity towards the book.

"This is the book of potential I got from Gregor. This used to be his telekinetic tool, it carried the potential of his abilities within it. Now that he’s dead, he mailed this to me before he died," Zhaoxing said,"open it, it will trigger the potential inside your body. The strength of your inert telekinetic abilities will be shown by how many words turn red as you open the book."

"Turn red?" Garen took the book over and casually flipped a few pages. The words on the cover, the words on the page, all remained in their typical black ink.

"Perhaps I’ve gotten the wrong book," Zhaoxing stared at the pages, feeling something was off.

"No, this is the right one," Garen disagreed,"I’ve actually flipped this book before in Gregor’s shop."

"You’ve flipped it before?" Zhaoxing was stunned, she checked the cover again and was certain that this was the book of potential.

Her face started to turn displeased.

"This can’t be! How can someone like you acquire such great amount of power without any potential at a young age?! Keep flipping, maybe you need to do it longer."

Garen shrugged, he couldn’t understand why this old woman was so tense, it was just telekinetic energy, not like it was a big deal.

"Alright, I’ll keep flipping."

As time passed in the study, there was only the sound of Garen occasionally turning pages.

Zhaoxing’s face also started turning more and more displeased. The excitement that was once in her eyes slowly faded away.

"It’s not that serious right?" Garen noticed her changing expression.

"I shouldn’t have had high expectations…" Zhaoxing sighed, her face seemingly turning older,"and there I thought our generation was saved. But all of it was just a dream."

"Well, I just don’t possess telekinetic potential, what’s the big deal?" Garen frowned.

"You don’t understand. Gregor was the greatest master of our generation. He represents the continuity of our millennia of traditions and culture. But now, all this is for a naught, we will just die out…." Zhaoxing replied softly,"He gave you that book and that pendant. Only you have the right to inherit his abilities sealed within that book. Yet now, you don’t just not have telekinetic potential, you can’t even open the pendant…."

"As I said, don’t you think you’re taking this whole thing a little too seriously?" Garen asked plainly.

"Telekinesis is everything to us," Zhaoxing closed her eyes, and replied in immense sorrow.

Garen slowly understood her perspective. Everyone has something that defines them in life, for this woman, it was the telekinetic culture.

"Screw it, let’s not talk about this for now," Zhaoxing opened her eyes, they were still filled with waves of tiredness,"now we can only rely on you, Garen. You are our last hope. You’ve given us hope, even though you failed to live up to my expectations," she smiled bitterly.

"Sylphalan seems to treat you like his enemy?" Garen asked,"he doesn’t even care if you live or die, looks like he’s just going to bulldoze over everything that comes in his way."

What this meant was that Sylphalan never even treated Zhaoxing and group as enemies, they were merely like ants on the road that Sylphalan couldn’t even be bothered to step on.

That, was the truth.

"While it sounds harsh, it is the truth," Zhaoxing nodded,"However i must ask you again. Garen, are you sure you want to completely settle your vendetta with Sylphalan?" her face suddenly turned serious.

"Of course, that’s the whole reason why I’m here." Garen replied plainly,"I am different from the King of Nightmares and Andrela. This is the sole reason why I’m here."

The whole reason why Garen went on this quest to destroy Sylphalan was because of the fact that he killed Gregor, and almost killed him.

Ever since he arrived on this world, he’s had little close friends or relatives. If he were to rank them, the first would be his sister, the second would be Gregor and his teacher, his uncle, parents, then followed by Su Lin, Andrela and the rest. As for everyone else, he had known them for too brief a time to say much.

"What do you mean by asking that?"

Zhaoxing shook her head,"I just needed to be sure. The Immortal Palace’s plans are way too elaborate, should you choose to pursue them, you must be prepared for the worst."

"Do you hear what you’re saying?" Garen stared at the old woman,"I don’t think I can run into much danger given my abilities. Let it be Behemoth’s Gate, or even the Immortal Palace, nothing can stand in my way. Heck they’ll only serve to entertain my journey."

Zhaoxing did not expect him to answer like that,"You are insane! Do you even realize how powerful Sylphalan is?! He even…"

"You should have more faith in me." Garen smiled as he cut her off.

"If you continue to be cocky like that, you will lose everything the next time you face the Immortal Palace!" Zhaoxing was visibly angry now.

"I am not cocky, I am just confident about my own abilities." Garen shook his head.

"This is cockiness! You aren’t even certain of how powerful Sylphalan is, and yet you dare talk about him so lightly!"

"I told you, I am not cocky," Garen frowned,"Nevermind, I shan’t waste my time on pointless arguments like this with you."

"You have no potential, you can’t possibly fight Sylphalan! Today he was not being serious but if he goes into his full form…" Zhaoxing couldn’t help but shiver for a bit, like she was recalling some brutal scene.

Garen saw the woman who was scared out of her mind before him, and was at a loss for words to comfort her. He had to respect her still, after all she is a relative of the late Gregor, and an elder.

"For his next step, Sylphalan is going to travel somewhere at a specific time, not sure if he’s running away from you or he’s planned this all along. If you are as powerful as you claim to be, then go ahead!"

"Where and when?"

Chapter 197: Absorption 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"The ancient ruins on the Smoke Island in the Harp Sea are the largest ancient ruins that have been discovered to date. Only masters in telekinesis are able to accurately pinpoint the entrance of the island’s ancient ruins." Zhaoxing Qin said. "Rumor says that visitors on the island have disappeared without a trace recently. I’m guessing that thing has appeared again."

"What on earth is that thing?" Garen furrowed his eyebrows.

"The Black Smoke Pot. Legend says that it releases a black smoke that allows people to communicate with the dead. It is a relic left by the Ancient Endor civilization." Zhaoxing Qin looked at Garen, who seemed to want to ask something. "I know what you’re thinking. The answer is, I don’t know. There are a lot of Ancient Endor treasures but only a few of them had mystical effects. And even then, they are not reliable as the effect tends to fluctuate. Hence we are not sure if this Black Smoke Pot has such a mystical effect or not currently."

"How sure are you that Sylphalan will definitely be there?" Garen questioned.

"Definitely. He became strong because he wanted to resurrect my mother. There’s nothing more useful for that than the Black Smoke Pot." Zhaoxing Qin replied.

"Do you know when he will be there?" Garen asked again.

"I’m not sure about that. The entrance of ancient ruins on the Smoke Island can only be found during the night of a full moon, or it would be extremely difficult. The next full moon is about four months from now." Zhaoxing Qin explained. "The Smoke Island is located at the border of the Federation’s sea. It’s not that far, and if you’re really set on going, I suggest you set off a month before the full moon rises."

Garen understood very well that Zhaoxing Qin had no reason to bluff him. She had always been in the position of fighting against the Immortal Palace, as well as being in the position of the Old Man Gregor. Although she was not strong, she was very knowledgeable in the secrets buried by history.

"I understand the overall situation. How do I get to Smoke Island?"

"We can arrange the best boat for you if you depart from the Siberia Port. There are very little tourists there because the island is covered in mist most of the time. In addition to the rumor that the smoke on the island is poisonous, there are even less tourists once the mist is up. It’s good timing for you to do your business there." Zhaoxing Qin gave Garen the gave she had directly to him as she knew that he had already decided to go, no matter what.

"Alright, since we have more or less finished discussing, I should let my partners know of the matter as well." Garen stood up. "As allies who go against the Immortal palace, they will cover my back to ensure I’m safe. Similarly, while I don’t have the knowledge of telekinesis, it doesn’t mean my allies are in the same shoe as I."

"It was a memento from Gregor, which was a book that contained all of his telekinesis. Unlike the Eternal Starry Night Pendant that you’re currently wearing, it has an amazing ability to repel anything except the memento. It was also an item that Sylphalan attempted to get his hands on. However, he doesn’t really need this anymore since he had absorbed the Argent Mirror. Soon, I will pass this book to Julie and if possible, I hope you can take care of her."

Garen softly touched the pendant in front of his chest and nodded.

"I promise I will do everything within my power."

Zhaoxing Qin nodded and finally gave a sigh of relief even though she still felt extremely disappointed and dejected.

Both of them got up and left the stone chamber one after the other and went back into the stone room from before.

Andrela, Julie and King of Nightmares were gathered around the charcoal fire, having a soft, casual conversation. It looked like they had gotten closer within this short time span.

The three of them stopped the moment they saw Garen and Zhaoxing Qin came out of the chamber. Julie immediately stood up and looked at the book of potential which was in Zhaoxing Qin’s hand skeptically. As if she immediately thought of something, the girl who was about to speak out held herself back.

"I have performed my test towards Lord Garen and unfortunately, he doesn’t have the talent in telekinesis.." Zhaoxing Qin said in a deep tone. "With the request from Garen, I hope I can test both of you. Are you guys…"

"Of course. It’s just what we wished for." Andrela and King of Nightmares replied in sync.

Both of them seem to be very curious and excited about telekinesis.

"Alright then. Who shall go first?"

Andrela and King of Nightmares stared at each other and the latter pushed the former to the front.

"I will go first then." Andrela smiled leisurely.

After the simple explanation given by Zhaoxing Qin, with the same process as what Garen went through, he flipped the book softly as he took possession of the book of potential.

Unfortunately, there was no trace of changes to the pages and cover of the book.

Zhaoxing Qin shook her head.

Andrela couldn’t help but to feel disappointed.

"Please pass the book to this lady."

Andrela passed the book to the King of Nightmares. The latter took the book as she couldn’t help herself but to reveal her excitement and interest on her white and tender face.

As she grabbed hold of the book firmly and opened the first page.

The wordings on the cover of the book of potential slowly became red, as if fresh blood had crept across the cover page’s letters.

At the same time, the first page of the book started to become red as well, just like a book written in red ink.

"It’s reacting!" Garen and Andrela were staring at the King of Nightmares.

"Pale red, I see.. This level can be further categorised into three tiers." Zhaoxing Qin nodded. "Congrats miss, you indeed have the potential to learn telekinesis." Her reaction wasn’t excited as if this was a very common thing.

Judging the reactions from Julie and Zhaoxing Qin, the three of them knew that the King of Nightmare’s potential in telekinesis was fairly common and standard.

"Alright then. Miss, would you like to stay back and learn our style of the telekinesis battle strategy?" Zhaoxing Qin offered out of Garen’s reputation. Increasing the King of Nightmare’s strength meant that she was increasing the strength of the enemy of Immortal Palace. Furthermore, she was Garen’s ally.

"Battle strategy? Of course I’m very interested." The King of Nightmares licked his fingers with a strange look in his eyes. Whenever she did that gesture, it meant that she had some troublesome idea in his mind.

Andrela, who was off to the side, had a strong hunch. He remembered that the last time when he saw the King of Nightmares did the same gesture, he had been horrified that she attempted to transform into a man the next day and attacked him with all of her new techniques. He was so horrified that he didn’t dare touch her for the next few months.

"What are you planning to do this time?" Andrela quickly asked in panic.

"To be honest, I want to know how it feels like to absorb to Argent Mirror, rather than learning the telekinesis battle strategy…" King of Nightmares started laughing softly.

Zhaoxing Qin was not that surprised as she had already anticipated it.

"It might be too much for you to absorb the Argent Mirror. It’s a very dangerous thing to do."

"It is also very exciting as well." The King of Nightmares continued. "Do you think I am able to?"

"Yes. as long as you don’t regret it, any person who has potential in telekinesis is able to absorb it." Zhaoxing Qin said coldly. "A lot of people have actually tried it and without any exception, they either fail mid way through or became crazy."

She looked at the King of Nightmares coldly. "To be honest, your personality is very similar to of my mother, and hence I’m not surprised that you have made such a decision. However we may require some time as absorbing the Argent Mirror requires a lot of preparation."

"How much time do we need altogether?" The King of Nightmares whispered.

"About three days. There are some materials required which we would need to obtain from an old friend of mine, who lived very far away. So this is the earliest we can manage. We also need some materials to isolate the Argent Mirror to prevent any pollution if it leaks." Zhaoxing Qin calmly explained. "The price of the material will be borne by you since we don’t have any extra money laying around."

"That’s only natural." The King of Nightmares nodded in agreement.

"What should we do then?" Andrela looked at Garen, who was supposed to be the leader of the team as he was the strongest.

Garen shrugged his shoulders.

"If possible, I hope to stay here and have a deeper understanding of the fighting style of a telekinesis master. We have too little knowledge about Sylphalan and his gang since they have yet to show their telekinesis to us yet."

"I, too, think that to be advisable." Zhaoxing Qin nodded.

**************

Hence, for the next three days, Garen and his team decided to stay a hidden basement, secretly constructed from an entrance to a tomb.

It was spacious; so spacious that it had more than ten rooms. The rooms were quite clean as well, a janitor having obviously made some rounds in this place.

What was most surprising, however, was that this basement was connected to other basements, and there were outsiders who used these basements to deliver essential products and food to customers.

The whole basement was like an underground kingdom, or an underground social circle. Garen and his team found out from a few people that these basements were like nodes connecting to other nodes, forming a complete, labyrinthine system.

The two old men that the trio thought had killed visited them on the second day. They even provided some intel and news as thanksgiving. They thanked them for saving his life.

It was just as Zhaoxing Qin had said, they were perfectly fine. However, they looked rather pale as if they had lost quite a lot of blood.

When Andrela was bored, he followed Julie to a specially designed basement which contained an isolation field for training. The isolated field was a field created by telekinesis with a metal enhancement. It’s hardness and toughness were well above all the metals on the surface. Andrela tried slicing it with his sword with all his might but there was only a fine scratch on its surface. This was nothing to a wall that was nearly half a meter thick.

This made both of them able to train at ease.

On the other hand, Garen had been studying extensively anything related to telekinesis, including the knowledge in advancing the telekinesis’ strengths from the books. Although he didn’t have the talent in telekinesis, that didn’t stop him from obtaining knowledge.

As a person who once lived on Earth, he knew very well the importance of information. It was much easier to deal with a dangerous situation or formidable enemy when one understood well the enemy’s techniques and strengths, rather than not knowing what the future held.

Three days passed in a blink of an eye, and the King of Nightmares had gathered all the necessary materials with his money. Together with Zhaoxing Qin, he had spent up to a few hundred million in Pi dollar. This wealth was equivalent to a billion RenMinBi on Earth where Garen once lived.

With the cooperation of a few old men and Zhaoxing Qin, the ritual to absorb the Argent Mirror was finally finished.

Chapter 198: Absorption 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Knock Knock Knock.

Garen gently knocked on the brown wooden door in front of him before pushing the door open.

Inside was a spacious, enclosed black stone chamber. The walls, ceiling and floors were all made out of black, reflective marbles.

In the middle of the stone chamber, there was a blue, pentagonal pool filled with clear blue liquid.

At the edge of the pool erect was black scepter with two hawk-like wings that spanned over two meters across. The construction of the wings was so detailed and clear that even the feathers were crafted.

The design of the scepter was simple; the top of the scepter was shaped like a rounded diamond, the engraved musical notations largely faded due to wear.

Garen walked past the pool and saw the King of Nightmares and Zhaoxing Qin, along with the two old, white haired men behind the scepter.

Zhaoxing Qin was standing just behind the scepter with a black engraving knife on her hand engraving something onto the back of the scepter. She was so focused that she didn’t seem to notice Garen’s presence at all.

After some amount of time had passed, Zhaoxing Qin finally stopped moving her hand and tiredly let out a sigh. It was only then that she looked up at Garen who was standing to the side.

"You’ve arrived?"

"How is it? Is it finished?" Garen nodded.

"Almost. A final step remains." Zhaoxing Qin placed the engraving knife down tiredly and shifted her focus onto the King of Nightmares. "When do you want to start?"

"Anytime." The King of Nightmares replied with a smile. She had changed into Julie’s attire, which was a T-shirt paired with a pair of jeans. Although there was nothing much going on on her chest, her body figure was still rather proportioned due to her small and exquisite size. She gave off a teenager’s vibe instead even though she was in her thirties.

"Then let’s start straight away. The flow of the ritual depends entirely on you, as disturbing the ritual with an external force would be very difficult." one of the old white haired men replied from the side. "We can only help you set up the ritual and nothing else."

"Isn’t this better?" The King of Nightmares nodded satisfactorily. She took out the Argent Mirror from her jeans. "I just need to placed this on the scepter and jump into the pool. That’s it right?"

"Yes." Zhaoxing Qin nodded.

"We shall head out first. The medicinal effect here is too strong."

"Thank you for your help, both of you." Zhaoxing Qin politely thanked the elders.

Both the old men bowed slightly before leaving the stone chamber.

"Once you jump into the pool, open a slight wound on your eyebrow and the rest will follow suit." Zhaoxing Qin turned around and gave the simple piece of instruction to the King of Nightmares.

Andrela and Julie, who had already received the news, came to see the ritual as well. They stood alongside the old men in the transparent stone chamber, which was next to the ritual chamber and looked into the ritual room through the glass panel.

Both chambers were separated by a layer of telekinetically enhanced crystallized glass. It was purpose-crafted for this situation to ensure the safety of the observer outside. This chamber was originally used to conduct telekinesis experiments.

They could clearly observe what was happening in the experiment room from the observation room. Furthermore, the enhanced crystallized glass panel was retardant to high temperature, erosion, frost, etc. Even hard-point metal was no match for it.

This guaranteed the safety of the observer.

"Alright. We should take our leave." Zhaoxing Qin started ushering the party out once the King of Nightmares was ready.

Garen and the others went out, and he saw Andrela standing in front of the glass panel with a worried look on his face.

"Why don’t you stop her if you’re worried."

"Everyone has to be responsible for their own actions, her and I are no exception. We only depend on each other when we are lonely and we definitely won’t allow our relationship to affect our decisions." Andrela calmly replied.

"A very abstract answer." Garen replied. "I only know to achieve my objective. Taking care of other people’s emotions has no important value to me."

"You should be careful. Looks like the Divine Statue Technique has some side effects."Andrela squinted his eyes as he looked at Garen, as if he had noticed something.

Garen was slightly stunned. He felt something was wrong when he spoke just now as it was not his usual style and personality.

"I’ll keep that in mind."

The Divine Statue Technique was a top tier technique that no one had ever obtained before. No one knew the overall effect of this technique, even the inventor himself might only be able to manage a guess. Although its power was huge, the side effects had started to show itself.

Garen could faintly feel his personality secretly starting to change. It was as if it was a direct effect of using the Divine Statue Technique, where he felt like a God, a being so high and above everyone that they would be as insignificant as ants to him.

"Prepare to start." Bam, after the experiment room doors were shut, multiple metal rods thick as arms mercilessly sealed the door, accompanied by a series of mechanical whirs and knocks.

Garen, who was standing beside Andrela, had snapped out from his thoughts and gazed into the experiment room.

Zhaoxing Qin, Julie, and the two old helpers were monitoring the King of Nightmares closely.

"Everyone listen up. Julie, I want you to be alert at all times. You will immediately release the sleeping gas and stop the experiment if you notice something amiss!"

"Understood!" Julie nodded her head.

Zhaoxing Qin gave the King of Nightmares the OK gesture as she looked into the experiment room.

The King of Nightmares nodded his head and gave a sweet smile to Andrela as she looked at him, before hastily jumping into the blue liquid in front of her, which was about waist level deep.

The King of Nightmares gently scratched her eyebrows with her thumb nail. Her nail was as sharp as a knife as it easily drew a thin wound across.

She then immediately threw the Argent Mirror with one hand, which came to a stop hanging onto the scepter.

With excitement and curiosity, the King of Nightmares dipped her whole body into the pool, up to the point where her wound was being covered by the blue liquid as well.

Then, it was all silent.

"It’s starting." Zhaoxing Qin murmured.

As she finished her sentence, a splash came from the pool all of the sudden and the King of Nightmare stood up and started to vibrate. At the same time the water from the pool started to vibrate as well as if there was an earthquake.

However, even more curious was the faces of strangers flashing across the Argent Mirror’s smooth surface, which sped past one after the other. It was as if a lot of people were taking turns using the mirror.

Among the faces, expressions of pain, cold laughter, cruelty, anger. The only emotion that they lacked was one of calm and normalcy.

Garen and the others who were standing outside of the room couldn’t see or hear the situation inside. They only saw the King of Nightmares shutting her eyes tight as she frowned. It looked like she was in some sort of pain.

"What’s going on!?" Andrela couldn’t help but ask. He clenched both of his fists tightly as he felt involuntarily nervous.

"She’s absorbing it." Zhaoxing Qin replied. "It has just begun. There’s still a long way to go."

Andrela felt assured the moment he saw Zhaoxing Qin’s calm expression.

Garen had been setting his eyes on the King of Nightmares as he continued monitoring her status. He had to be careful as the King of Nightmares was their main source of strength going against the Immortal Palace. She might also be the only one who was strong enough to go against the top master Flamingo.

Time continued on its slow passage.

An hour went by...

Two hours went by...

Three hours… Four hours…

After a full six and a half hours later.

"There’s a progress!!" Zhaoxing Qin shouted out of nowhere.

Garen and the others immediately rushed towards the glass panel and looked at the King of Nightmares nervously.

They saw King of Nightmares opened his eyes, covered in thin, sprawling blood vessels. The worm like blood vessels travelled from the pupil to the sclera, to the temple point and to her cheeks and even her neck.

Hmph!!!

A strange power suddenly diffused through the experiment room and rippled the blue liquid.

"Attempting to suppress me? In your dreams!!" The King of Nightmares suddenly growled as the veins started to recede.

It was at this moment that everyone noticed at some point, the faces in the Argent Mirror had disappeared and only one face remained.

It was a face of a powerful man with eyebrows resembling knives. He had a black scar on his nose and his gaze was overflowing with confidence and violence. His hairs were short as nails.

The man in the mirror opened his mouth and he seemed to be talking to the King of Nightmares. When he stared at the King of Nightmares, his gaze were so cruel that it felt like he was trying to squash an ant.

"She has reached the final phase, which is to fight against the first generation’s Argent Mirror holder." Zhaoxing Qin explained. "The first holder is the strongest in the Argent Mirror. This is universally known. They are also the only one qualified with the ability to restrain and capture evil telekinesis users. He is the person in charge of the Argent Mirror and at the same time has sealed his negativity into it as well. That man should be the strongest holder in the Argent Mirror!"

"If she fails this phase, what will happen?" Garen asked.

"She will be severely injured and at the same time, she will suffer psychological damage." Zhaoxing Qin answered in confidence.

Andrela clenched his fist even tighter as he listened.

Garen kept quiet as he looked at Andrela. After that, he shifted his attention back to the experiment room.

The King of Nightmare’s veins kept expanding and shrinking. This probably meant that she was fighting against the strongest holder of the Argent Mirror.

"I feel like I have seen this man’s drawing…" The old man suddenly said as he came forward. His face was so frozen that it was as if he thought of something very serious.

"He’s Ansheli! He is the evil empire Ansheli!!" The other old man continued the sentence. He looked like he was in disbelief and shock as if he just saw a ghost.

Chapter 199: Handling 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"The legendary emperor who ruled the ten countries for nine generations??!!" Zhaoxing Qin was stunned. "How is that possible!? That was just a legend!"

"No. I’m sure of it. It’s definitely that man. I saw that his left ear had a ring gap!" The old man kept swallowing his saliva as he was too scared to look away from the Argent Mirror.

"According to the legend, the Evil Emperor Anshela’s left ear was wounded by a woman under orders. The wound was formed as she pierced his ears with all her might with a sword! I’m very sure of it! It’s definitely him!" The old man was about to panic. "Damn it! How could a legendary person actually exist!!?"

"Maybe you’ve mistaken him for someone else…" Zhaoxing Qin was very skeptical as she didn’t believe that a legendary person would appear in the Argent Mirror.

"Oh?" The deep toned voice of a man penetrated through the glass and entered the observer’s ear. "There are still people who recognize me?"

"Quick! Activate the sleeping gas!!" The old man quickly rushed towards the trigger on the right. "Stop the experiment now!! Now!!"

"At this moment, Zhaoxing Qin and Julie sprang into action, the severity of the situation having dawned on them. As their faces went pale, the both of them rushed towards the trigger as well.

Boom!!!!

A telekinetic wave was as dark as ink exploded from within the experiment room. Zhaoxing Qin and Julie suffered were shellshocked from the explosion and dropped to the floor, having completely lost their sense of balance.

"Hmph!" The man in the mirror gave a cold hmph as the King of Nightmares' veins had started to travelled throughout her body from her head.

Garen and Andrela had no idea what was going on at this point. A few seconds had passed as they saw Zhaoxing Qin and Julie collapsed to the ground.

"What’s going on?!" Andrela’s raging aura started swelling up and held his sword by the waist with his right hand, preparing to attack at any given moment. They did not hear the old man’s whispers, and were still in the dark even then.

"Looks like the experiment has failed." Garen sighed. "Zhaoxing Qin, I don’t care how you do it. Tell me what to do now!"

"Stop… Stop the experiment!!" Zhaoxing Qin’s body was still numb from the shock inflicted by the telekinesis. It felt like her organs had completely rearranged themselves inside her body.

"Stop the experiment?" Garen started, his right fist.

At this moment, the King of Nightmares, who was in the experiment room, jittered her body and all her veins disappeared in an instant. She seemed to have calmed down.

Ah!!!!

Suddenly, an ear-piercing scream erupted from the King of Nightmares. Within the shrill voice was the voice of another male, layered on top of hers.

"I hadn’t expected to be able to return to this world…"

"Over my dead body!" The King of Nightmares raged as she shouted.

"Now, this isn’t your decision to make." The man started laughing.

A force field started to engulf the whole experiment room.

Boom!!

The highly enhanced telekinetic crystallized glass was smashed into a million shards by Garen’s fist. He then walked towards the King of Nightmares without any expression.

"You!!" The King of Nightmares' male voice seemed to be surprised as if she was about to speak out.

Garen’s right hand instantly flexed outward and he threw a punch with his golden white colored hand.

Boom!

Two fists collided into each other.

Hmpf! The opponent cried out as she retreated back to the experiment room and immediately dashed sideways. Kaboom!! The wall behind her was punched through by Garen’s fist.

"Hah! Divine Statue - Thunder Sprint!!" Garen shouted as he raised his left hand. In an instant, his hand was glowing white in color as he attacked from a completely still posture and landed a punch of the King of Nightmares' left shoulder.

Another explosion was heard and the King of Nightmares was sent rolling on the ground and crashed into the wall. She screamed out of pain and collapsed to the ground.

Garen walked towards her with his expanded, beast-like right arm which was at least half a meter thick. With this very arm, he grabbed the King of Nightmares by her hair and pulled her up.

With a fist, Bam!

The King of Nightmares' body arced.

"No!!! I don’t want to return!! Never!!" The male’s voice came out from the King of Nightmares' mouth.

Bam! Another punch!

"I am the almighty Evil Empire Anshela."

Bam!!

"Garen!!" Andrela shouted as he couldn’t bear it any longer.

"I know what to do!" Without even looking at Andrela, Garen took the King of Nightmares up and throw her against the wall.

After a thud, the King of Nightmares laid still on the floor and was completely silent.

Hit after hit, pound after pound, the King of Nightmares was completely defenseless against the onslaught, and was in rough shape.

Finally, her gaze changed back to normal. She laid on the ground and stared at Garen, unable to utter a word.

The whole interaction lasted less than 20 seconds in the experiment room. In this short amount of time, Garen managed to put Anshela, who had taken over the King of Nightmares' body, down onto the ground.

Zhaoxing Qin and the others who were outside of the experiment room started to gradually recover as they got up from the ground. They sluggishly set their gaze upon Garen who had just taken down the King of Nightmares who was in the experiment rom.

No. The one who was taken down was Anshela who had taken over the King of Nightmares' body.

The King of Nightmares, who had showed signs of personality disorder and mental breakdown was brought back to normal conditions?! Zhaoxing Qin, Julie and the others witnessed Anshela, who was controlling the situation like a great devil beaten by Garen into submission in the experiment room.

It was like an adult hitting a small child. Even the pure and innocent Julie couldn’t watch the horrible state Anshela was currently in.

Fortunately, the King of Nightmares regained control over her body, but she was so badly injured she was left unable to speak.

"You alright?" Garen reached out his hand and picked up the King of Nightmares. He walked towards Andrela with a wry smile and threw the King of Nightmares into his arms. "I will let you take care of the rest."

"You scared the hell out of me. I really thought you’re about to kill her!" Andrela helplessly hugged the King of Nightmares. From her eyes, Andrela could see that even though the King of Nightmares was severely injured physically, at the very least she wasn’t in any mental danger anymore. Furthermore, the injury on her body was not considered a big issue to the King of Nightmares, even though Garen had in fact pulled his punches.

"How is that possible? Do I look like someone who couldn’t control his strength?" Garen stared at him. "If I hadn’t reacted any faster, It would be so much more difficult to call her back when that man got used to the King of Nightmares’ body." He read about this from a book. Since the King of Nightmares wanted to attempt to absorb the Argent Mirror, he collected a lot of information so that he could understand the overall situation better. With his learning pace, which was inconceivable to a commoner, as long as he met the condition of having a maximum point in intelligence, he would obtain photographic memory and the ability to understand the information instantly.

"Alright, I will carry her inside to rest." Andrela quickly brought the King of Nightmares into their room.

Zhaoxing Qin, Julie and the two old men slowly got up from the ground at this moment.

"That was a shock wave used to target at telekinetics. Fortunately the shockwave didn’t affect either of you since both of you didn’t possess any latent ability in telekinesis."

"Indeed. I doubt I would have such an easy time if that guy got used to his new body." Garen agreed as he nodded. "Luckily this incident is threatening but not dangerous. The King of Nightmares shouldn’t have any sequelae from being forcefully brought back, right?"

"The absorption process of the Argent Mirror had been interrupted, so at least half of the personality had been absorbed back." Zhaoxing Qin shook her head, as if she was still in pain. "However, Anshela should still be inside the King of Nightmares’ body. As long as she is careful not to be mentally excited, she should be able to slowly eliminate his consciousness. However, some essential memories are lost forever.."

She finished with a tone of pity.

Garen, too, nodded in regret.

He was able to fight against Anshela with ease because the King of Nightmares' consciousness was fighting with Anshela to regain control of her body back. Hence Anshela was unable to fully control the body or use any telekinesis.

The most important thing to note was that the King of Nightmares was a novice and had little latent ability in telekinesis. To be able to produce a telekinesis shockwave was considered amazing. When Garen rushed in and forcefully interrupted the absorption process, it was equivalent to throwing a punch directly into a living being’s brain.

These few aspects must be met. If the opponent had successfully control of her body, the Evil Empire Anshela would reborn. Being a person who stood at the pinnacle of all telekinesis practitioners during the ancient era, only God would know what damage he could cause in this generation.

"To be able to cause so much damage to us with the King of Nightmares' little ability. If it was Sylphalan who absorbed the Argent Mirror…" Zhaoxing Qin’s face started to turn pale.

Although Sylphalan had absorbed one Argent Mirror, albeit a weaker one, he would definitely be someone very hard to deal with as the consciousness inside the Argent Mirror had a lot of telekinesis secret techniques.

"Master…" Julie held Zhaoxing Qin as she was very worried.

Speechless, Garen looked at the old lady as she was definitely afraid of Sylphalan. Unlike Garen and the lots who practiced martial arts, who would feel excited as they could see themselves being stronger in the future than being scared when they encountered a strong opponent.

"Alright, since the absorption process had been interrupted, everyone should take a rest. We will gather again when everyone has recovered and move on based on the King of Nightmares' status." He suggested.

"I guess that’s our only option." Zhaoxing Qin was standing on her own as she told Julie to help the remaining two old men.

************

It didn’t surprise anyone that the absorption of the Argent Mirror had failed. What was surprising was everyone finally understood the troublesome side of the Argent Mirror when Anshela’s consciousness appeared before them.

This item was just like a pandora box, where countless of treasure and secret techniques were stored inside it. One might possibly released an evil and horrifying being once one opened it. Anshela might have successfully reborn and took over the King of Nightmares' body if not for Garen and Andrela. He might even be a telekinesis practitioner stronger than Sylphalan.

Garen and his team finally understood the pros and cons of the Argent Mirror.

After recovering in the basement for some amount of time, Zhaoxing Qin observed the King of Nightmares everyday. Once she confirmed that there were no major issues, the crowd finally felt that they had placed down a boulder from their shoulders.

Garen, Andrela and the King of Nightmares had wasted too much time here as they had their own matters to settle.

Chapter 200: Handling 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was the gate master of the White Cloud sect, and thus had a lot of underlings. Since he had just laid down his foundation not long ago, he couldn’t be away for too long, for fear of trouble brewing.

On the other hand, Andrela was the senior fellow apprentice of the Celestial Circle Gate, and the master who had long since surpassed the gate master and elders of the sects. He had to go back to sort out some internal affairs.

And then there was the King of Nightmares, the founder of the Siren Group and an internationally wanted criminal with lot of enemies. She had a lot of troublesome things to deal with as well.

The three of them agreed to meet at Hilda City, which was located in the Federation’s bay, on the fourth month. They had also officially settled on the name that was originally a joke: Flamingo.

The King of Nightmares had decided to took the opportunity to spread the Flamingo’s reputation in the dark since there were quite a few witnesses during the battle with the Immortal Palace. The Immortal Palance had abused their power for too long. No one could stand against them except for the Behemoth Gate and the government from the big countries. They could collect enough information as they ran amuck around the world.

Garen took the train and returned to his country following the proper procedure. Once he had entered the country, he immediately arranged a military airplane and flew to Galantia using his authority from the Golden Hoop.

It was currently the first month, which in fact wasn’t that far off from the fourth month. He had to arrange everything in detail to prevent any trouble arising, as this trip towards the Smoke Island might take him a lot of time.

************

Ten days later….

Galantia’s Huaishan Province.

Kachak.

Garen slowly opened the door with a key.

"I’m back." He shouted.

Immediately, rushing footsteps could be heard from far as the father Eisen Lombard and mother Vania came rushing in.

"Why are you back all of the sudden? You should inform beforehand." Mother quickly gave Garen a brand new cotton slippers to wear. "I thought that there’s a thief in the house."

"Mum, did you think a thief would shout I’m back? You’ve such a rich imagination/." Garen smiled as he closed the door and wore the shoes.

The family gathered in the living room.

Mother went to brew some hot coffee, whereas the father Eisen and Garen were sitting opposite each other on the sofa.

"How is it? Did you learn anything in school today?" Eisen looked so much different from before as his face was now smooth and clean since he had shaved his beard. He was wearing a tidy white shirt, a black tie and even applied some hair oil onto his dark purple hair. He was like a successful man. "Living alone outside is definitely different from living in a home, right?"

"It’s alright. I’m still getting used to it." Garen took an apple from the table and started peeling off its skin. "There’s not much difference between the life of a middle schooler and college. Oh right dad, I’ve received an internship offer from a big corporation, I might go there for an internship on the third month. Just a heads up."

"Not bad. This internship is an opportunity given to you or…" Eisen was no longer in the dark about the whole ordeal as he had a clear understanding on in the influence of the White Cloud Gate. He finally witnessed his son’s succession as the Gate Master of the White Cloud Gate since the funeral.

"This wasn't arranged by me. The opponent is much stronger than the White Cloud Gate so there’s no need to be concerned with it." Garen shook his head as he explained.

Mother Vania came in and served three cups of hot coffee.

"Let’s drink something to warm you up first. It’s cold outside."

"Oh yea, where’s Ying Er? Is she still in school?" Garen asked as he lifted the coffee cup and drank from it. The rich aroma of mixing coffee and milk that entered his mouth, albeit slightly hot, made him feel warm and cozy.

"She said that the school was organising an event. She had to go to school and do some preparation as a committee member. She thought that you wouldn’t return so she went out early. You should know your sister well; she would definitely wait for you if she kenw that you were coming back." Mother Vania looked at Garen gently, since Garen was her biological mother whereas Ying Er was Eisen’s biological daughter. Both Eisen and Vania had realized Ying Er’s feeling towards Garen. It was not of a sibling relationship but something more intimate.

Both of them weren’t opposed to such a relationship, since Garen and Ying Er was not biologically related.

"You should rest early Garen, since you came back at such a late hour. Now that most of the stuff has been passed down to the workforce, your mum and I are not as busy anymore. In fact, we have more and more free time as the days pass. Let’s go play hockey tomorrow. It’s not often that we get to hang out together and have a good chat." Father Eisen patted on Garen’s shoulder. "What dense muscles. All thanks to training in martial arts for such a long time!"

"It’s also called body building." Garen laughed. "Oh right dad, mom, I thought you guys were planning to buy a bigger house and move in. What happened to that?"

"There’s no need for that. Although we are rich now, we have already gotten used to the communities here. I have been hanging out with our neighbour madam Davis at the orchestra on a weekly basis. Occasionally we would gather and have a tea. Life is more entertaining when you have company. We don’t know who to mingle with if we actually moved to a new area." Mother Vania shook her head as she explained. "Don’t worry about this. You should think about your marriage."

"Eh, isn’t that too early?"

"Our son has just reached home and he must be tired. There’s no need to raise that topic." Father Eisen cut it off. The parents had realized Ying Er’s unusual affection towards Garen when Garen rejected their offers of introducing women to him. They’ were testing the waters now.

"Yes, yes…"

The whole family had dropped the topic after that, and the conversation slowly moved towards lifestyle matters.

Garen started to feel at ease when he saw that his parents were starting to have more time to enjoy life due to the White Cloud Gate’s arrangement.

He stayed at home for a few days. Everyday, he would accompany his father to play ball and occasionally he would drive to the swimming pool nearby for a swim. He even attended the tea sessions and orchestra as well. His schedule was packed with leisure events for the past few days.

As a core leader of the greatest profit organisation locally, the news of Garen returning was spread throughout Galantia province in a short time span.

Invitations to parties kept coming as time went on. The same went for the visitors who knocked on their door as well. On top of that, most of the visitors had brought along their nieces or daughters over with a smiles on their faces. They were obviously hoping for Garen to fall for one of them.

It was unbearable to such a point where Garen hadn’t bothered to return home and decide to go to his dojo instead. The place was in good shape under the management of his disciples, Simon and Corinne, and the White Cloud Gate had returned to its former prosperity. The White Cloud Gate had expanded its community in a lot of schools within Huishan City and nearby cities as well.

Garen had no need to worry regarding the growth of the White Cloud Gate. Both Simon and Corinne had gone out for an experience exchange and were no longer in the city.

He then went to the Golden Hoop headquarters only to find out that the Eighth Hoop Cyclops Dragon was the only one sitting there. Since both of them didn’t really know each other, Garen chatted for awhile and left the place immediately.

For the next few days, Garen visited the local governors, his third fellow master apprentice and his respective family under the Gold Hoop and White Cloud Gate’s body guard protection.

Afterwards, he went to his uncle’s place.

According to his uncle, Garen had not seen him since the cursed ring’s incident. Since he had treated Garen well in the past, he decided to visit his uncle out of politeness.

***************

Huaishan Pennington Street

Inside a five-story building next to the street.

Tyr was sitting on a rattan chair in a black thick tee shirt as he was looking at the noisy children in the living room as he dangled a tobacco pipe from his mouth.

For the past few days, he had successfully closed a big trade deal, and his business had been getting better and better as the days passed. His place was constantly packed with visitors and all of the elite cousins from his wife’s side even visited him of their own accord. It was obvious that they wanted connections with him. He found himself slightly annoyed, as he couldn’t reject their visits either.

"Lombarth… Lombarth!" He raised his voice.

His son, Lombarth, was happily chatting with a tall girl. He quickly ran to his father when

he heard his father’s call.

"What’s the matter father?"

"Where’s Phelia?"

"She’s playing chess in the basement with some of her friends."

"I knew you can’t count on that girl. Please take care of the visitors for me. Most of them are around your age. The son of Minister Jeter has finally come to visit us. You should accompany him and talk less with these beautiful girls." Tyr suggested.

"Alright." Lombarth was very happy as Garen was not going to fight against him for the properties, and his father had started to nurture him. It seemed like his father is preparing him to become a worthy successor.

Vaeneris Westin and Delai Ando were elite siblings who once tried to snatch Tyr’s property as well. He was a little bit unhappy, he didn’t know why they had come to his house.

Before he left his father alone and walked to the corner of the living room to meet a golden haired man, he walked towards the girl and politely apologised to her.

"Lombarth, you don’t want to talk to these beautiful girls anymore?" Delai Ando’s voice came from a corner. This gloomy person who mixed with the underworld was gently swaying a glass of wine as he tried to act elegant, even though his rough body figure was keeping others at bay. His hand seemed to recover from the injury he had gotten from Garen last time.

Vaeneris was beside him with a feminine smile. He didn’t speak much and just hung out among a few guys and girls, like the stars were surrounding a moon.

"Who’s coming? There’re so many cars down stairs!"

"That car plate number… It’s the governor’s car. Could it be the governor’s cousin?"

"There’re seven V8s opening the path. What a huge scene, each car costs up to millions! Who’s causing all this balze?"

The visitors who were sitting by the window started to gather and look down as they murmured.

The black cars stopped beside Pennington street one by one.

A strong, bald bodyguard swung open the door of the car.

A tall and muscular guy with red eyes emerged from within. He had a simple, short black hairstyle and though his body was very muscular, it was very symmetrical and not bulky in the least. He gave off a strong sense oppression even though he wore a simple tee shirt and jeans.

The man was wearing a golden earring on his left ear. This gave off a slight sense of barbarity. This man was none other than Garen, who had been everywhere recently. With his current social standing, this scene was a must or would affect how others viewed the White Cloud Gate. What made it even more more eye catching, however, was that he was also a member of the Golden Hoop.

Chapter 201: Preparation during the Eve 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen slammed the car door behind him and walked into his uncle’s house.

The car was slammed again and Cynthia stood still behind Garen, with a black full body tight leather shirt.

"I don’t like causing such a scene. It’s too troublesome." Cynthia whispered.

"This situation is a must since the Federation’s government had failed their operations a few times already. I don’t want to forget that they are still supporting and assisting me." Garen calmly replied. "These are all small matters. The federation is so huge that it would take at least a few decades before it falls. With such a big treat ahead of us,we need to be careful to not bite off more than we can chew."

"A hero appearing in our most desperate times?"

"Sort of." Garen turned his head and looked at one of the cars.

A middle aged man with a beautiful, curled beard appeared from the car. He was in a white suit and held a white cane in his hand.

"Sir Garen, please go ahead."

"That’s very kind of you Minister Difana." Garen nodded.

This minister was in charge of the whole of Galantia Province’s econom and investment. He was ‘coincidentally’ passing by Huaishan City so he had met up with Garen. He was also a member of the Golden Hoop inner circle, the uncle of the Seventh Hoop.

He heard that Garen was going to visit his uncle Tyr Anjer. Since he had seen Anjer once in a party before, he decided to visit him as well.

In his eyes, Garen of the White Cloud Gate had obviously became a strong force that he could not afford to ignore. No matter if it was in terms of personal strength, or in the military, he had an irreplaceable influence.

Since the Federation’s Government was at a disadvantage, there were rumors of separatist regimes blooming up all over the province. The powerful White Cloud Gate was the most concerning of all to the Governor. This was especially true since the White Cloud Gate had been expanding at an incredible rate recently and had been involved with almost the half of the districts in the whole province. Their members were increasing on a daily basis and they were also representing the martial art in the civilised community and the underground world. In addition, Gate Master Garen was also one of the high ranked leaders of the Golden Hoop, who had a lot of power and support.

If the governor really wanted to become a king, he must first face the two major forces, military and the White Cloud Gate. He could only truly control the whole of Galantia when he obtained the support of these two major powerhouses.

This was one of the main reasons he had sent the finance minister Difana to investigate Garen’s attitude.

Both of them walked into the building with lunging steps.

Bodyguards flanked and followed them as they walked up to the fifth floor together.

Uncle Tyr had already been waiting for their arrival at the front door.

"Long time no see, my beloved uncle." Garen walked up and gave his uncle a gentle hug.

"Long time no see indeed Garen. This is…?" Tyr looked at Difana who was standing behind Garen. "Is this Minister Difana?"

"It’s a pleasure to meet you again Sir Tyr." Difana placed his cane onto another hand and greeted Tyr with a handshake.

"That is rude of me. Please come in." He took off Difana’s jacket and the three of them walked into the living room.

"I have a gathering going on currently. I hadn’t expected that Minister Difana and Garen would come over, I’m sorry if my hospitality isn’t up to my best." Tyr smiled as he introduced.

"Lombarth and Phelia, come over now!" He shouted.

Both of the kids had been waiting at the side as they had already heard the fuss.

Tyr Garen and Minister Difana was at the center of everyone’s attention the moment they entered the house.

Lombarth swiftly went into the room to call his sister out. When she heard the call, she quickly went out and greeted obediently with her head bowed.

"Nice to meet you brother Garen and Minister." Lombarth bowed with respect as he greeted them.

Phelia held her knee height shirt and greeted them as well. "Nice to meet you brother Garen and Minister Difana. Long time no see brother Garen."

"Long time no see indeed." Garen reached out his hand and pinched Phelia’s small cheeck as he smile gently.

Difana who witnessed this at the side took note of it in his mind.

"These two are the kids from my wife’s side of the family." Tyr gestured Delai Ando and Vaeneris to come over with his hand. These two are the most outstanding teenagers on my wife’s side of the family. They had no choice but to lower down their head when they met the finance minister of the whole province. This person was on another level compared to their family background so they had to becareful.

"Good to see you minister." Delai Ando’s face was stiff when he walked over to greet him. As he finished greeting Difana, he looked at Garen and his faced turned red as he didn’t know what to tell him. He had had a conflict with Garen in the past. The current Garen was far above him and was looking at him from above. The feeling of knowing someone looking down on him made him embarrassed and wanted to find a hole to jump into.

"Brother Garen… about the past, it’s our fault. Hope you can forgive us." Vanaeris smiled awkwardly as he apologised to Garen.

"I don’t hold any grudges on it. You should be more careful when doing your tasks next time and don’t assume what you do will definitely go well. Don’t rely on others too much because you’re not as bad as they are most of the time." Garen smiled and he said. He didn’t have any hostile intent towards these two who viewed him as an enemy. These two more or less was at a loss under him and since he was on the winning side, he naturally didn’t have any hostile intent towards them.

"Alright. We will talk about the past later. Minister Difani and Garen, this way, please. We will go to the meeting room." Uncle suggested as he leaded the way to the study room.

Garen and Difana followed closely behind, with multiple strong body guards and Cynthia guarding the door ensuring no one comes near the occupied room.

As the black door was shut tight, Lombarth, Vaeneris and Delai Ando looked at the meeting room with complicated feelings.

"Looks like us taking him for an enemy was useless after all. He is no longer at the same level as us." Vaeneris whispered helplessly.

Delai Ando was completely silent as held his fist tight and exhaled intensely, as if he had just released a load from his body.

Lombarth felt awkward within. He was very cynical towards Garen back in the day, and Garen hadn’t given it a second thought at all. However, he was slightly relieved as well, Garen was currently much stronger than his father and the relationship between his sister and Garen had always been good. Not to mention his father had treated him even better than his sister. Based on this, Garen’s power would be a strong force towards his family as well.

Just like the three of them, Phelia was staring at the meeting room quietly, her mind seemingly churning incessantly.

***********

Inside the meeting room

Garen, uncle Tyr and the finance minister Difani were sitting opposite each other, forming a triangle from the round table.

The big study room was quiet as there were the only the three of them. None of the bodyguards had entered the room at all.

"I think Sir Garen should know the purpose of my visit today. I come here on behalf of the Governor Wahana."

"I clearly understand Governor’s Wahana current point of view, however the extent of your power and influence is still unknown to me. The White Cloud Gate is just a small sect, and we have been through a lot lately, and we can’t have any more on our plate at the moment." Garen said calmly as he crossed his fingers.

"You’re too modest. The Governor had hoped that you would come and support our work. This would be a huge contribution towards the stability and safety of the whole Province." Difani smiled. He paused for a moment, and it dawned on him that it would be better to talk about the issue directly to a martial artist like Garen, as martial artist didn’t seem to like to beat around bushes. "As long as you show your commitment and improve the stability of the province, the government would definitely help the local development. In this era, it is very difficult to become a leading country. Hence we need to focus on local development to prevent the foreign economy from invading our country."

Difani added on as he looked at Garen.

"Not too far from now, the government plans to release a series of supportive measures that would help in economical development. However the overall structure is still under observation and they need the comments of the district to maximise our efforts."

Garen had finally understood his intentions.

This meant that as long as he agreed to support the Governor, as long as it was within the scope, any recommendations were welcome. Furthermore, if there were any good things from the government, he was sure to get his share as well.

He started thinking about it. He personally didn’t mind about it but there were a lot of people who worked under him. Hence he needed to improve the whole organisation’s development and profit.

Uncle Tyr was sitting at one side in shock as he looked at the other two negotiating between each other.

In the past, he knew the power and influence of Garen and the White Cloud Gate. However, they were still a small sect at the time and had little influence. At the most, they could only influence the local city. Who would have thought that the influence of the White Cloud Gate had grown so fast that Governor Wahana had to take note of his existence and lower his position to request for a cooperation. Compared to his nephew that he knew so well, his influence hadn’t even reached that kind of level yet.

It was at this moment that he realized that he had underestimated the influence of the White Cloud Gate, or the speed at which the White Cloud Gate was developing once Garen had become the successor.

After the discussion between Garen and Difani, they finally came up with a exaggerating mutual agreement.

Garen would tacitly approve of the Governor’s actions and in return the Governor would go against the White Cloud Gate’s current industry policy: The workers of the White Cloud Gate shall not be imposed of any taxes and at the same time the would had the rights to the internal criminal department.

The rights to the internal criminal department! This meant that if anyone related to the White Cloud Gates had committed a crime, it would be internally sorted and the police department had no say in it.

They allowed such a ridiculous policy towards the White Cloud Gate.

Speechless, Tyr looked at the two of them signing the agreement and each of them kept a copy. It was obvious that the power the Governor gave to Difani had not reached its limit and Garen could have requested for more. However Garen had stayed his hand for more.

After the agreement, Difani started to consult Tyr on the local economy and recommended an overall rectification. It was obvious that he was giving face to Garen and at the same time keeping an influencer like him in check and offered a series of offer conditions.

Ultimately, the three of them reached an agreement and everyone obtained what they wanted.

Difani left the house after they left the meeting room.

After Garen and his uncle sent the minister off, both of them went into a single room to reminisce about the past.

They also called Lombarth and Cynthtia to enter as well.

Chapter 202: Preparation during the Eve 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The door closed slowly.

Lombarth and Phelia stood in front of Garen and his uncle.

"Garen, seeing you succeed, I’m happy for my sister and brother-in-law. With us Jody’s, I’m still considered to be pretty well off. And now there’s you." Garen’s uncle Tyr said earnestly. "I’m old now. Some things are harder to manage, more tiring. You’re different, you’re young, you can still go for a long while."

"Uncle, you don’t have to beat around the bush with me, you can tell me anything straight." Laughing in spite of himself, Garen leaned forward, suggesting he’s genuinely interested.

"That’s good to hear," Tyr nodded in appreciation. "I asked Lombarth here, so you, as his elder cousin brother, can help advising him in the future if he messes up anything. Of course, only if you have the time. The Anjer household can still afford to keep him fed and housed without much difficulties."

"Of course." Garen nodded, "Lombarth was a little immature then, but people do change. You needn’t be so worried, uncle, maybe he’ll even do something huge in the future, no? Quite a number of people only made it later in life."

"And Phelia too," Tyr held his daughter’s hand. "Your younger cousin sister has always been obsessed with the war chess, to the point of neglecting everything else. Even now, she’s preparing to take part in this King of War Chess Competition in the Bolsha province. It had really taken over her life!"

"Don’t worry, uncle. Phelia is still young, she’ll learn to prioritize after she matured a little more, it won’t affect the important things in the future, I can assure that." Garen had heard about the popular war chess, it was said to be unusually complicated in that everyone who participated will win or lose something, even sacrificing their lives.

"War chess is not a game for children." Phelia protested, pouting. "This is an Open Sea Championship with a reward of one billion dollars*! And I am one of the three representatives for the Galatia province! Don’t underestimate me!"

"One billion!" Tyr and Garen both flinched.

"A championship with such a large amount of reward? That’s crazy!" Garen’s uncle frowned.

Garen shook his head, "I’ve heard of this war chess game. It’s said to be peculiar in the sense that winners will get stronger while losers get weaker. People who always win would achieve immense success in whatever they do, while the more people lose, the more they suffer from bad luck. The war chess has rumors of it being dangerous and mysterious."

"Fine, just be careful." Tyr shook his head, "I’ll let Kerrigan escort you there."

"Thanks dad!" Phelia grinned happily.

Garen shook his head, speechless. He resumed his conversation with his Uncle Tyr about the issues with the development and arrangement of the province. He accepted his uncle’s suggestion about employee’s benefits, transforming White Cloud Gate into a for-profit organization with each aspects of the welfare of their employees. That way, he’ll be able to utilize everyone’s capabilities and influence the best possible way.

This inspired Garen a lot.

He decided to use this same concept on other newer influences like the teams from the former Black Mark Association, Cynthia, Jack and the other mercenaries, as well as some other new elites in the Martial Arts community.

If they were bound together with their subordinates, even if the forces under White Cloud Gate were to leave due to issues, they would not have huge issues running on their own.

Garen finally left his uncle’s place after dinner. The opinions and advices Uncle Tyr had given him were valuable experiences. Even though he’s a member of the Information Era from Earth, many things will not work with just pen-and-paper theorizing. In that aspect, Uncle Tyr provided Garen much needed help.

Back at White Cloud Gate, Corinne finally got back along with representatives of Circling Dance Gate and Seven Moon Gate to greet Garen.

After arranging White Cloud Gate’s new system of operation, Garen took a flight to Hubo City

His sister Ying Er had left to Shengying University, he wanted to meet her there.

Soon, he’d be leaving to a closed off Smoke Island, where he planned to destroy the ship to force Sylphalan out to fight with him. Before that, he needed to make sure he had prepared for every situation.

　　************

Shengying University

On the yellow field in front of the library building.

Garen was wearing black T-shirt and jeans, blending in with all the other university students. Garen sat on a white marble bench underneath a tall Japanese pagoda tree. The winter sun sprinkled its light onto Garen, bringing him only a slight warmth.

The library of Shengying University was a maroon building with a roof resembling two cones. On the steps in front of the entrance, students were walking in and out of the entrance.

Two long-haired girls exited the library. One of them had black hair and red eyes, the other one had blonde hair and purple eyes, both were equally pretty.

On seeing them, Garen slowly stood up.

"Big brother!" The red eyed girl squealed when she saw him, and started jogging toward Garen before giving him a big hug.

"How are you here all of a sudden?" After a while, Ying Er looked up and asked.

"I’ll be going away soon, so I can’t visit for a while. I just had to drop by before that." Garen smiled, "How’s it going with the school?"

"It’s okay…" Ying Er curled her lips indicating her indifference, "Lots of assignments lately, a little tired. Thank goodness Nina’s helped." She pulled her friend up, "Big brother, this is my roommate Nina, Nina, my big brother. He came here to visit from home, he’s studying at Harmony City."

"Nice meeting you." Nina greeted Garen with grace.

"Nice meeting you too," Garen smiled politely, "Thanks for helping Ying Er with her things."

"It’s nothing. Ying Er helped me a lot too." Nina replied with a slight shyness.

They both gave Garen a tour around the cafeteria, the sports field, as well as other places like the indoor swimming pool. If it wasn’t for the restriction of boys in the girls’ dorm, Ying Er would probably want to bring him to her room.

Ying Er was pretty popular at school, very soon, the parade was joined by two other girls.

The girls were all very interested in the mysterious big brother Ying Er kept mentioning, including how she used to bully him when they were kids.

Everyone had always imagined Garen to be a scrawny, androgynous boy. Upon meeting him, they were surprised by his good looks and lean, muscular physique.

It was almost lunchtime when they finished touring the campus.

The five young people went straight to the cafeteria to order dishes.

The lunch was simple, only some raisins, white bread, potato soup and some turkey meat*. Simple as it may be, it was pretty nutritionally balanced.

After lunch, the girls brought Garen to the hawker street behind the campus, where all sorts of street food can be found due to the food variety, or lack thereof, available in the cafeteria.

It wasn’t until they were stuffed that they returned onto the grassy park.

The sunlight at noon was much warmer than the morning. Garen and Ying Er strolled behind the three girls who conversed among themselves, drawing glances and gazes all around.

"Just a while ago, the dorm keepers caught Ivy keeping a squirrel she caught in the woods over there. You should have seen the squirrel, it’s so cute I wanna kiss it!" Ying Er recounted funny stories she’d experienced spiritedly.

"Remember grandma’s house at the farm? There were lots of squirrels in the woods behind, you can go catch a squirrel or two to keep." Garen smiled.

"I know, but I can’t even take care of myself properly…" Ying Er kicked at the turf.

"Big brother Garen, can you play badminton? Do you want to come play with us at the badminton court over there?" A girl in front, Ivy turned around and asked.

"Badminton…" Garen was about to nod when a tall man scuttled to him and whispered in his ears.

Surprise flashed on Garen’s face before he returned to normal.

"Excuse me ladies, I have some urgent business to attend to. Maybe next time?"

He pinched Ying Er’s face lightly.

"Study hard, I’ll visit again when I can. Try to visit home during the holidays."

"I knooooow, I’m not a child." Ying Er swatted at Garen’s hand.

"Let’s go, Garen shook his head and turned around, leaving in a hurry with the tall man following without a word.

It was only then that the girls realized some five or six pedestrians trailed behind Garen as he leaves. Obviously, the men were Garen’s hidden bodyguards.

"Such an illustrious send-off!" Nina’s jaw dropped. A few white limousines with silver patterns stopped in front of Garen at the entrance before him and his bodyguards got on and left quickly.

"Who is your brother? How do we not notice the bodyguards before? That’s so extravagant!" Utterly confused, Nina turned around and bombarded Ying Er with questions.

"That’s so over-the-top, not even the trust fund babies can compare to it. That’s a send-off fit for a government official! Ying Er, be honest, what is your brother!"

"Spill it! This goldmine cannot be let out before we could take a bite off it! Let us, your roommates, have him!" The last girl teased before bursting out in giggles.

Ying Er turned bright pink, unable to answer anything at all.

Translator’s Notes:

1. Author didn’t specify the currency unit in this chapter. Translator is part of the group that took on the project after the previous one abandoned it. Readers should be able to do the math.

2. It wasn’t described, but the dishes implied a traditional Chinese meal setting i.e. every sitting around a table sharing a few dishes a la Chinese dinner. Google image Chinese dinner for reference.

Chapter 203: Preparation during the Eve 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen sat in the car with his eyes closed and his brows slightly furrowed. The tall man who relayed the message sat in front, driving.

"How are they doing?"

"The doctor said it’s not a huge problem, but they need some time to recuperate." The driver answered.

"Su Lin and Celine were not that weak, how is it possible that they were driven to this point? Cynthia, did you hear anything from your end?"

Cynthia who sat beside Garen only shook her head.

"I only knew they were pulled into the riot at the border, it was impossible to investigate otherwise. You’ll have to ask them yourself."

"What did Leo say?"

"They were already unconscious when Team Leader Leo found them. We don’t know who attacked them." Cynthia’s answers were short and sweet. "Gate Master, do we…"

"We need not be too hasty. Su Lin’s father is an official of the Confederate, he will not let this go easily. Tell Leo to cooperate with their investigation. If he suspects anyone, he can take action against them, no hesitation needed."

"Isn’t this too…" Cynthia felt some discomfort with the order.

"It’s fine. Right now is not a peacetime. If we don’t act aggressively, no one will be scared of making a move on us." Garen snorted.

As one of the White Peacocks, the three secretly collaborated for exchange of information as well as fighting power when needed, and even the means to do things if required.

Right now, White Cloud Gate have been able to get intelligence and military support from the Sirens’ influence overseas. Celestial Circle Gate was also able to provide enough help from the army as well as the political circles.

In return, White Cloud Gate provided support to Celestial Circle Gate’s underground operations, they also helped the Sirens with intelligence exchange as well as operations.

Technically, the three had already been bound together by the mutual benefits they get from each other.

Arriving at the airport, Celestial Circle Gate had already arranged for a military plane to transport them. The military power here was still mostly affiliated with the Celestial Circle Gate.

After arriving at Harmony City by flight, they proceeded to switch to a car to drive to Su Lin’s manor. It was already 9 o’clock by then.

　　*************

In a clean white bedroom.

Su Lin leaned against the headboard of the blue bed, his lower body was covered with a cornflower blue blanket. He was in white pajamas and looked pale, and even his fiery hair seemed dry and depressed.

Aris wore a thick black windbreaker and a pair of black gloves, and was feeding Su Lin herbal soup.

The room was filled with the pungent scent of the herbs that was slightly similar to traditional Chinese medicine.

Garen took a whiff of it when he arrived before frowning while he sat by the bed.

"How do you feel? Better?"

Su Lin looked at Garen wryly.

"Lost too much blood, almost couldn’t make it."

"I told you to not go around so much! Look at you now, now you can’t even move aside from staying in your bed and rest." Aris grumbled resentfully. This outburst was a first for the lady who was usually graceful.

Still grumbling, she stuffed the spoonful of herbal soup into Su Lin’s mouth.

"Yes, yes, I’m wrong. I should’ve heeded your advice. Hey, do you think you can leave Garen and I to ourselves for a bit? We need to talk." Su Lin asked in his helplessness.

"Fine. Talk all you want." Aris stood up and handed him the bowl with the remaining herbal soup.

Understanding her point, Su Lin took the bowl and downed the content into his throat, after which he handed her back the bowl.

"Are we good?"

"Hmph!" Aris responded with annoyance on her face and left the room, closing the door with a backhand.

Only Garen and Su Lin were in the room now.

"So what happened?" Garen glowered at Su Lin. "With both your strengths, you shouldn’t be hurt this badly."

"You don’t need to worry about this. I can deal with it on my own." Su Lin didn’t elaborate, "It’s not the Poker, it’s some other people. I’ll deal with them." Mirroring Garen, he frowned. "I got careless. They are weaker than me, so I can’t ask you for help.

Garen stared at him straight in his eyes. Seeing the conviction in his eyes, Garen nodded.

"If you insist. What about Celine? How is she doing?"

"Much worse. She was buried alive in the avalanche and almost froze to death." Su Lin answered.

Coldness filled Garen’s eyes. "You are both my friends. If something happened, I wish to be there for you as your friends."

"Thanks," Su Lin nodded earnestly. "But like I said, we need to do this ourselves. I can’t bear the humiliation of having to ask people to avenge me…"

Even though he said that, he was still very grateful.

Among his friends, there were only two people who wouldn’t think twice to avenge him, and one of them was Garen.

Like this time, most of the dangers he and Celine was met with near the border was averted once they mentioned Garen being his friend. A huge number of forces treated them like they were important guests.

Even the riotous gangs dared not attack them due to Garen’s reputation of being Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate’s Sky Warrior.

"I’m really glad you visited." Su Lin patted Garen on his shoulder. "You’re in a different position now, the Sky Warrior of Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate, wait no, the Second Divine Warrior of Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate, the White Cloud Gate Master, the strongest Grandmaster of Combat of the Twelve Southern Sects, the Underground King of Galantia, Holy Mammoth Holy Fist… Your fame is all over the place! Tsk tsk… You’re a famous person now, even Black Mark Association had been absorbed by White Cloud Gate. You have three Grandmasters of Combat under you who are on par with Sky Warriors. You are dominating the whole of the South, you’re just like a cancer… I mean anti-hero!"

Speechless, Garen played along with his antics.

"You do look like you’re much better, you’re even well enough to tease me."

"It wasn’t that serious in the first place." Su Lin countered, "It’s just…" "Is Su Lin awake?" A young man knocked on the door, his voice giving away his calm, steadfast demeanor.

Su Lin immediately hid under his blanket.

"My elder brother is here!" He whispered and then used a louder voice. "I just got up."

With a click, the door was opened by a tall man in a black windbreaker.

He has short red hair, like Su Lin, but he also had red brows. His eyes were as sharp as an eagle’s, with only a glance, he could intimidate people.

He wore black leather gloves, accentuating the golden patterns on his cuffs.

Garen knew him as Harris, Su Lin’s biological brother. He was recently promoted to a senior official.

As for his impression of Harris, Garen could only remember Duskdune Shura had tried to assassinate him.

Duskdune Shura had tasked a former Royal General with the assassination. Obviously they’ve failed, indicating the complexity of his background.

"Your friend came to see you?" Harris nodded at Garen who stood up, giving out a subtle aura of authority. "Nice meeting you." He held out his hand.

Garen shook his hand.

"Nice meeting you too. I’m Garen."

"Garen?" Harris blanked for a little. He thought the name sounded familiar. But since he is a friend of his younger brother, he only nodded.

"I’ll be taking my leave then," Garen nodded politely. "Su Lin, get well soon." He turned around toward the door.

Laying on the bed, Su Lin thought his words sound loaded.

"Garen!" He called out. "Don’t butt in, I’m serious."

Garen kept his silence and smiled weakly.

"Fine. I’ll let it go this time. I’ll go visit Celine."

"Mm."

Harris listened to the conversation with a weird look on his face. This Garen seemed really influential, he didn’t know his brother had friends who had power over the situation at the border, this surprised him.

"Harris, Garen is my friend, I owed him my life. He’s not in the same circle as you." Su Lin noticed Harris’ expression and immediately understood his brother’s occupational habit of analyzing other people’s backgrounds, the links between different influences, and all those complicated mumbo jumbo.

His brother Harris was a pretty decent guy, but he’s always going off on conspiracy theories, as if the whole world was built on conspiracies alone. Because of that, he had not found someone to marry after all this time. The girls were scared as soon as they saw him with his strict face.

"Su Lin, you don’t understand, our family has a lot of connections with very influential backgrounds. If you don’t think in a deeper level, you may not even realize it after people have already cheated you. There are many people who wanted to use our family’s fame." Harris stated matter-o-factly.

"He’s not even in the same system you’re thinking about! To be honest, what he’s pursuing is totally different than what we are doing. The political situation in the Confederate at its current state, if Garen wanted to, he could’ve become a leader himself. He was so different from us it’s like comparing apples and oranges!" Su Lin rolled his eyes, "He’s one of those people you politicians fear the most. If you offended him, don’t count on a night of good sleep if you don’t have hundreds of special forces with artillery capabilities."

Harris smiled, not believing Su Lin. However, this really isn’t his business to butt in on. With their father and his vast political experience to protect Su Lin,this shouldn’t be an issue.

　　***************

After leaving Su Lin’s room, Garen turned into another room not far from Su Lin’s.

The door was open, a nurse in white came out with a slew of medication in the basin.

"Excuse me, is this Miss Celine’s room?"

"Yes sir. Mr. Garen, is it? Miss Aris told me it’s okay for you to go in."

"Thank you."

Garen entered through the open door. A bright white light illuminated the room.

Oil lamps filled every empty corners of the room. The outside of the glass of the oil lamps were painted white, so light from the fire was turned white and spilled into the room.

Celine leaned on the bed in the middle of the room. Like Su Lin, she leaned at the headboard, her face pale, eyes blank.

"You’re pretty quick." Celine forced a smile. "Thanks to you. If they didn’t know I’m your friend, I could’ve died out there."

Chapter 204: Preparation during the Eve 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"They knew of me, and they still hurt you guys so badly?" Garen squinted in spite of himself.

"It’s not their fault. They didn’t know initially. Let’s not talk about this. Su Lin and I will get back up where we fell. Let the two of us handle it. If you meddle with this, it’s just gonna add to our embarrassment." Celine shook her head in defeat. "I heard Andrela from the Celestial Circle Gate and you were working together?"

"You knew?"

"Oh please. Both of you were celebrities of the south. Behemoth Gate had it bad this time. With you and him together, the Red Sand Sword Gate will definitely follow your tracks. And with your connection with the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate, the whole of the Southern Martial Arts Community is basically your oyster farm." Celine sighed. "If anyone annoyed me in the future I’ll just call out your name and watch them quiver."

"Give it up." Garen sat on the bed, shaking his head.

"Oh yes, do you still want the rest of the Red Jade Palm?"

"Of course I do, the more the merrier. You’re finally willing to give it all to me?" Garen teased her.

"I already gave Su Lin the whole of his parts. Yours shouldn’t be delayed too. Besides, I’m not even sure if you still want the Red Jade Palm." Celine made a face as if she’s annoyed.

"Of course I do." Garen smiled. "Even if I don’t train in it, I can still collect it. White Cloud Gate needs to be stronger, but it lacks in that department when compared to the other sects. Also, talents between different disciples vary, if I can get more Secret Martial Arts, I may be able to fully develop a disciple’s talents."

"I’ll give it to you in a bit." Celine sighed as she scrutinized Garen, her gaze deep and full of admiration.

"Your Aura is so strong, it’s unbelievable. Have you had a breakthrough last trip?"

"That’s right. Where’s your mini-me? I don’t think I saw him in the manor.

"He ran away with our beloved Eight-Arm Dragon King. That twerp realized his immeasurable talent in the Gun Arts and followed Yoda to the military base to train his firing skills. It’s been about two months." Celine said helplessly. "He left me, his first teacher, for firearm, this is ridiculous."

Garen laughed softly.

"Right, if you’re ready we can start with the last part of Red Jade Palm. I have time now, but I need to leave in a few days."

"Fine."

The two of them sat together, one explaining, the other memorizing.

Celine only needed to say things once before Garen was able to memorize word by word. Celine who tried so hard to memorize everything when she learned it was so jealous for that.

The following two days, Garen stayed in the manor to help the two patients with blood circulation massages. After making sure they’re both alright, he told them about his long trip for them to be mentally prepared before leaving.

After that, he went to Red Sand Sword Gate to discuss things with the Gate Master and to visit Beo who had finally recovered from the coma. He also visited Seven Moon Gate and Circling Dance Gate.

Time flew like an arrow, it was soon the third month of the year.

Garen’s final destination was set to the be the headquarter of Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate at Wei Maen City. It was close to the Skylark Mountain Range and Skylark Mountain Waterfall.

White Bird Holy Fist Palosa hermitted there.

He decided to wait for Palosa to come out of his recluse before telling him about the Promise of March. If his departure to Smoke island was joined by Palosa, it would be a much safer option. With only the three of them, it would be hard to overpower IPA.

　　*******************

‘Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate’

An onyx tablet was erected with a tilt in front of a series of white buildings. The words were inscribed into the tablet with a strong calligraphy style.

Garen stood in front of the tablet with elites from the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate who came out to greet him around. He lightly touched the tablet, surprised by the skill.

"Who made the inscription?"

"The previous Gate Master." Sky Warrior Corbella explained with pride. "Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate was not a simple sect, it’s got a rich history on its own."

"I’ve heard about that." Garen nodded in understanding and glanced at the elites around him.

Behind him were two Elders who are pretty strong before breaking through to being a Grandmaster of Combat. If they went out on their own to found their own sect, they might even be stronger than Fei Baiyun.

Waiting in front were three middle-aged fighters who were infinitely close to being Grandmasters of Combat, even though they probably will not make it given their age, they’re still strong enough to keep up the appearance of a strong sect.

Slightly further, in front of the entrance, were two Grandmasters of Combat in different clothes. Judging from their Spirit, they’re probably only slightly weaker than Sky Warriors like Corbella.

Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate had three Sky Warriors, Garen had already been given the title Divine Warrior like Palosa, and was only second to Palosa. Hence he was called the Second Divine Warrior.

The extra slot for Sky Warrior was open for the Grandmasters of Combat in the sect to compete for.

As a sect with enough manpower to fight Black Mark Association, Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate naturally had more than just three Grandmasters of Combat, but the ones who managed to achieve the level of a King of Fist or Sky Warrior were still too rare. In that context, aside from Garen and Palosa, there were not more than five who qualified.

They weren’t around for as long as Red Sand Sword Gate and Celestial Circle Gate, but it’s already good enough that they managed to gather five Grandmasters of Combat.

Coincidentally, Garen was dropping by when they were holding the intrasectional championship for a new Sky Warrior.

Gate Master Bondi had decided to call anyone who’s a Grandmaster of Combat a Sky Warrior now that Black Mark Association has technically disbanded. Without an enemy, Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate gradually became lax, the title of a Sky Warrior became sort of a bragging right for the few Grandmasters of Combat to fight about.

Since everyone wanted it, it was decided that everyone will get it. Five Grandmasters of Combat, five Sky Warriors. Among these Sky Warriors, there exists conflicts of interest. To solve that issue, the intrasectional championship was born. Not only they can solve the issues they have with one another, it was also a way to showcase their power.

Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate was originally formed by multiple smaller sects, the outcome of this intrasectional championship would determine the advantage each group gets, heating up the competition even more.

Garen arrived at this point.

"Sir Garen, this way please." A middle-aged man greeted him and let Garen walk in the first.

"No need for such formalities." Garen smiled and marched in.

The bunch of people marched behind him, as if he’s a celebrity being followed by his fans.

On the other side of the entrance was a large field dissected into tiny rectangular fields like a chessboard. Within every rectangle, several disciples stood.

Some of them were only in their teenage, and some of them were at least 50 years old.

Cheering came from all sides of the field with energy and gusto.

With Corbella’s lead, Garen walked in from the side of the field with people following him, drawing gazes all around.

Soon, they arrived at a large conference hall. It was painted white, and the style was very reminiscent of the buildings for court trials of the past.

Outside the conference hall, Gate Master Bondi and other High Elders waited for Garen on top of the staircase.

"Welcome, Second Divine Warrior, Sir Garen."

"Anything but Holy Mammoth." Garen answered with a smile.

The bunch of people entered the hall and was greeted with the sight of two disciples in white in the middle of the hall, indicating the championship had already begun.

Garen’s seat was positioned higher than the Gate Master’s beside an empty one, which is Palosa’s.

After everyone was seated, the announcer proclaimed, "February 28th, Year 2088, Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate Intrasectional Championship, fifth match, begin!"

Ding!

The bell rang from one side of the room.

Hundreds of people sat in the hall, everyone of them were elites of the sect, some were competing disciples, some were their masters or family, most of them, however, were the core disciples of each branch, here to widen their horizon.

As the bell rang, the two disciples in the middle started getting anxious, they circled around each other, trying to look for each other’s weakness.

After a while, both of them were drenched in sweat due to the stress. Their masters, the Gate Master, and even the legendary Divine Warrior were all here. They were so worried about making basic mistakes, they were extra cautious with their movements.

A dozen minutes later, both of them finally charged at each other and started sparring.

In their over-cautiousness, they have lost their usual power and looked like they kept hesitating. People were getting bored with the match that was underwhelming.

After some time spent in a tie, the taller disciple finally ran out of stamina and was hit on his shoulders and sent out of the field. The judge who had ran out of patience hurried forward to announce the winner.

Gate Master who sat in front of Garen shook his head out of embarrassment.

"They’re too cautious and didn’t let go. Too much hesitation and without commitment to their movements. Maybe your presence stressed them out too much, Sir Garen. They were terrified of embarrassing themselves."

"Their foundation were still pretty good." Garen lightened the situation with a smile.

The same happened with the next match. After the match was over, Gate Master furiously left his seat to lecture contestants and their masters alike.

The following match was slightly better, two graceful female disciples fought against each other with ferocity and agility, letting people raise their hopes a little more.

The ninth match onward, the skill levels gradually raised within the fighters. Each of the disciples who went on had mastered the ability to use the Vibrating Fist technique. Below the level of Grandmasters of Combat, it was considered basic to have mastered the ability to Vibrate. Otherwise, they couldn’t even be considered a Martial Artist.

Anyone who was called Martial Artist must have complete control over the technique of Vibration. With that, they would be able to start teaching students in smaller places.

Chapter 205: Mediation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Sitting on the high seat, Garen looked like he was paying his utmost attention on the matches, but he was really casual about it.

Glancing at the matches below, he softly asked the Gate Master about situations at the Skylark Mountain waterfall.

"First Divine Warrior should be ending his solitary period in a few days. The herbal supplements he asked us to send had been increasing. Without his summons, no one was even allowed near the waterfall."

"Looks like he’s at his critical period." Garen nodded, "I will wait for him here for three days. When you’re sending people over, please relay the message."

"No problem." Gate Master Bondi nodded. This man is a descendant of Holy Fist Palosa who took care of him when he was a kid. His talent was pretty good, but it’s still ways to go before achieving the Holy Fist Realm, being a Grandmaster of Combat.

Bondi glanced at Garen before inquiring, "Do you have any opinions on the current situation in the Confederation, Divine Warrior?"

"Why do you ask?" Garen smiled.

"I heard you have a close relationship with the higher powers of the Confederation, and also that you have an important role." Bondi answered cautiously.

"Oh? This news had been travelling fast." Garen didn’t deny.

The winner’s announcement rang once more. "Aisha Freya of the east wins!"

Garen took a quick glance below and answered nonchalantly, "I do have a role in the Confederation, but I’ve only touched a tiny part of it. I don’t know most of how they run things."

"I only need some advice," Bondi asked seriously. "Now that Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate lost our enemy, we’ve became a little lax and disjointed. Without the stress of a common enemy, some of the original sects were thinking of separating from us." He scanned Garen’s facial expression before continuing. "Right now, the situation in the Confederation wasn’t stable, I don’t think you’ve managed to get wind about the current event?"

"What current event?" Garen paid a little more attention.

"Yesterday, Weisman struck Moshi City, the military port of the Confederation’s Special Forces. Three countries landed there and launched a massacre, killing more than two hundred thousand people. Only about a hundred people were spared to clean up the corpses." Bondi’s face fell as he described the situation. "The Confederation commenced a lockdown on the news. I only found out because my disciple’s family was there. The news should spread here soon."

"Two hundred thousand!" Garen’s face stiffened. "Three countries? Which three?"

"The empires Weisman, Crimson Crescent and Talitaan, Weisman lead the genocide." Bondi sounded somber.

"Are you sure? Two hundred thousand! Not a hundred or two, not a thousand or two, but two hundred thousand!" Garen was in disbelief. "In this age when several thousand deaths could cause an outrage, two hundred thousand deaths without even a sound?"

"Completely sure!" Bondi nodded,

Garen squinted as his heart suddenly sank. No matter what happened, disturbances in the Confederation is a threat to the safety of his family and White Cloud Gate. He could ask the Sirens for help in avoiding the war, but it’s not as calming as his own country.

"Let’s not be too hasty… We’ll see how the Confederation reacts, they are not so brittle to be easily defeated."

"I hope so…" Bondi went silent.

Garen’s put his arms on the armrest, thinking about something, the atmosphere becoming heavier by the second.

The next day, Cynthia got news from her contact confirming the authenticity of the news. It can be assumed to make its way through the whole Confederation, after all, it’s not a small amount of people who were killed.

The third day after the news, the championship had arrived at its final segment.

Garen didn’t go to audit the matches. Instead, with the arrangement of the Gate Master, he arrived at a secluded hall alone.

It looked like it used to be a small chapel. A bronze statue about eight meters tall was erected in the middle of it. The scent of incense permeated the air.

Garen entered. The disciple who lead him there closed the door and left, leaving him alone in the empty hall.

The statue looked down at him, his humanoid silhouette covered with a gray hood, spikes extended from his back, casting a shade of rusticness and savagery.

Standing in front of the statue, Garen waited without speaking.

Soon, a tall thin silhouette appeared from behind the statue. He had white hair and white beard, his face was calm and kind, and he wore a gray robe like the statue. It was Palosa.

"Been a long while, Garen."

"You’ve finally retired from your hermitary. Have you made up your mind? Join us." Garen asked calmly.

"I heard you got a Mirror of Secret Texts from the Immortal Palace in Picardi?" Palosa avoided the topic, bringing up another.

"If you join us, we’ll definitely share it with you. And not only that, we have other news." Regarding Smoke Island, there’s something that even the Immortal Palace was interested in, it must not be a normal treasure. It’s also why the King of Nightmare and Andrela decided to go together. If Palosa refused to join them, this news will not be shared with Palosa.

"Isn’t crossing the boundary the only dream we have at our level? Nothing to hesitate about." Palosa agreed without much thought. As one of the strongest fighters, he didn’t have to play tricks on them. Once he gave his word, there’s no need for them to doubt him.

After all, they are only teaming up for the benefits. They would naturally disband once they gotten the benefits.

Garen told Palosa about the Promise, in case he’s still hung up on the injury he suffered last time.

"Have you fully recovered?" Garen asked, "We’ve managed to get hold of the Argent Mirror last time, this time it’s possible there are more people from the Immortal Palace, be prepared."

"Don’t worry, if even I haven’t recover, Sylphalan could only be worse." Palosa answered confidently. "If there are other things to shout about, I won’t drag you down."

"Shall we go together?"

"No need, I still have things to arrange."

"That’s fine. See you at Hilda."

"See you there."

Garen turned around and left the hall, the door closing behind him.

Palosa stared at his leaving figure until his footsteps were no longer heard before a look of seriousness crossed his face.

"This boy… He’s even stronger now… Sylphalan, I’ve prepared something big for you!"

Having left the chapel-hall, Garen could tell Palosa had recovered to his previous state, but he’s also more confident than usual. Obviously he’s prepared a trump card, which is good, the stronger your allies are in this period of chaos, the better.

After reporting his current status, Garen tabulated the loose ends he want to wrap up.

"Two to go."

He left the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate at night in an prearranged car toward the capital of the Confederation Yangliu City.

Fenistine is there right now. According to Golden Hoop’s information, the leader of Behemoth Gate, General Black Orchid, had agreed to Garen’s private meeting request. The both of them will be meeting officially for the first time in this capital city.

Under Garen’s leadership, White Cloud Gate, Celestial Circle Gate, and Red Sand Sword Gate, as well as the whole of southern Martial Arts community have attacked Behemoth Gate countless times.

After killing Behemoth’s elite, Clark, Garen got his hands on the Blood of Eternal Life.

Furthermore, Celestial Circle Gate also utilized their sources to flush out one of the hiding places of Behemoth Gate. It is now safe to say Behemoth Gate no longer has any standing in the South.

Initially, Behemoth Gate wanted to have a formal meeting with Garen, to which Garen refused.

After that, the saga with the Argent Mirror happened in Picardi. As soon as this spread, the Behemoth Gate immediately contacted White Cloud Gate’s Intelligence department, hoping to meet with Garen.

After a few times, they even asked a high level Confederation official to be the mediator before Garen agreed to the meeting. Garen’s conditions were that it could only be a private meeting in Yangliu City and that Golden Hoop will arrange for heavy duty bodyguards surrounding the place.

Aside from the meeting with Behemoth Gate, he could also deal with Fenistine’s troubles at once.

After his return, Garen confirmed that Fenistine do need help with her situation. As a friend, he didn’t mind lending a hand, plus, it’s not that big of a deal to him.

　　**************

In the plane.

Under the starry night sky, blue starlights were reflected on the smooth fuselage, throwing a luster of gentle sheen like a mirror.

The four-winged military transport aircraft floated on top of a sea of cottony cloud like a black bird gliding slowly through the air. Strings of cloud zoomed past the windows occasionally, flying toward the full moon in the distance.

Garen sat in the cabin, quietly observing the blue-black sea of clouds. In the aircraft, it felt as if he’s in a world of endless cotton.

The aircraft slowly made its way through the cottony cloud. Above the aircraft was a canvas of black decorated with numerous amount of sapphires.

"Sir, your coffee." A pretty female soldier slowly handed Garen’s hot coffee to him.

"Thank you." Garen took the white ceramic cup and sniffed it. It wasn’t the best kind of coffee, but it’s already pretty lucky to be able to drink coffee in the air. "How far are we from the destination?"

"Another hour, sir!" The female soldier gave him a salute before answering.

"Can you please pass me today’s papers?"

"Please hold on."

She acquired a stack of newspaper and hung them on a hook beside Garen’s seat.

Garen casually flipped through the pages, and stopped all of a sudden as he picked out a page and started reading.

‘Military Port Massacre! Who’s Responsible?’

‘Surprise Attack at Navy Port! 200,000 Dead!"

‘Weisman Empire’s Declaration of War, "This is A War on The Systems, This is A Revolution!"

Chapter 206: Mediation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Headlines were flooded with the massacre.

Garen scanned through the other papers. Weisman defended their action, saying the number of deaths were grossly exaggerated, and that this was a response to the Confederation Army’s provocation. 99% of the deaths were soldiers, so they didn’t violate the international laws on human rights.

Garen picked some of the more trustworthy papers and perused them in greater details.

It was already a few days since the genocide. Protests were staged in various places to demand a strong military response, and at the same time to protest against the violence against helpless citizens displayed by the Weisman Empire.

After reading through the papers, Garen silently contemplated in his seat.

The aircraft was getting ready to land as it swiftly descended.

With some minor trembling, the aircraft landed safely.

Garen alighted the plane and took the pre-arranged car out of the airport and into the city center.

Half an hour later, within minutes of entering the city, noises came flooding in from the streets as if there were lots of people yelling. They don’t sound very practiced, bordering on disorderly, even.

Garen sat inside the black car, feeling the slowing of its speed. Pulling back the curtain, he took a peek outside. There was no one on the street, the noise seemed to be coming from afar.

"What’s happening?

The driver was a female soldier arranged by the army. She answered awkwardly.

"Sir, there may be protesters in front, maybe we should reroute?"

"Protesters?" Garen asked.

As the car crawled forward, the voices became clearer.

"No more imperialism!"

"No more imperialism!"

"Avenge Moshi Port!" "Avenge…"

Sounds of the protesters echoed from the front. Someone must have led the chants before people joined in.

"Sir, we can’t move anymore. They must have closed the road off." The soldier reminded Garen loudly.

"Let’s take a different route." Garen locked his brows together, "Does Yangliu have these frequently?"

"Yes, about once a week, at least ten thousand people each time." The soldier answered, "I heard many places have marches like that."

Garen exhaled and pulled the curtain back up.

"Wasn’t the army mobilized to keep them down?"

"Not yet, they’ve only mobilized the police to keep them orderly and jailed a few people who wanted to benefit from the chaos. Now that the protest snowballed, the higher ups didn’t dare to arrest anyone as well." The soldier answered helplessly.

Garen nodded with understanding.

The car turned into another street, slowly advancing behind other cars. Police were helping to direct the traffic on their motorbikes.

A dozen minutes later, the car slowed to a stop in front of a black-painted clubhouse.

Garen stepped out of the car and marched toward the entrance, accompanied by his bodyguards.

An obese, fair man in a lieutenant outfit stood in front of the entrance, smiling at him with his hands placed behind him and looking kind.

"Mr. Garen, I’m really glad to be the mediator for this meeting. It’s been a long trip, please, come in and have a little rest." His voice sounded shrill, a little like a duck’s voice quality, it’s a little funny to Garen. He didn’t feel like an official.

"Lieutenant Lycian, is she here?" Garen asked while following him.

"She arrived about ten minutes ago." Lieutenant Lycian was a friend of Su Lin’s father. When Behemoth Gate looked for him to mediate, Garen had to give face* to Su Lin’s father.

Of course, looking at the current situation, he might have wanted to mediate himself.

The hall was lit, the floor was lined with thick red woolen carpet. There were golden decorations all around, the wallpaper is of a faint yellow. There were special forces soldiers standing at a set distance from each other.

Garen could smell the faint scent of blood from these soldiers, it was apparent they had just finished a mission, and was directly ordered to cover this space.

After all, both the Behemoth Gate General and White Cloud Gate Master were ruthless. If they couldn’t reach a consensus and started fighting without the safety precautions, this mediator role may be dangerous to take on.

Noticing how Garen looked at the soldiers, Lycian smiled, "There’s a tent outside with artillery aiming here, keeping here as peaceful as possible so the meeting could go on. I think Mr Garen would appreciate that."

"Of course." Garen nodded, "The Confederation couldn’t sustain any more internal damage. This is why I’m willing to meet with him."

Lieutenant Lycian nodded in relief.

The two entered a quiet tea room.

The tea room wall was lined with black wood. A very detailed Eastern ancient drawing hanged on the wall facing the door. It’s rectangular, and was set on the wall in a horizontal fashion. It’s about 5 meters wide, accentuating its exquisiteness.

Tens of birds were drawn on the canvas. Some were soaring, some landing, some charging ahead, and some waiting to be fed.

There were red birds, blue birds, white birds, black birds and birds with all sort of colors and sizes, highlighting its magnificence.

"Such a good picture!" Garen doesn’t know how to paint, even then, he could tell the painting must have a really high value.

On the right of the painting sat a tiny lady in black clothing. The lady was slowly pouring a cup of tea. The jade-colored tea flowed smoothly into the white jade teacup, stunning Garen a little bit before calming him.

The lady had a pretty face and looked as if she’s only in her twenties. She moved with grace and a smoothness highlighted by her fair porcelain skin.

Garen approached her with the lieutenant, and noticed she wasn’t wearing any simple black clothing, but a black silk dress with a long, floor-sweeping skirt that shone with mystery and silky smoothness.

Black hair, porcelain skin, pretty face, and a pair of soul-catching slanted eyes.

For a moment, Garen felt as if he was back in China, and the lady sitting in front of him was a classic oriental beauty, gently pouring him his tea.

The two sat down slowly with Garen facing the lady as he watched the lady handing him his tea in appreciation.

"I’m a crude guy, I don’t know the simplest things about culture, so I will be frank. You’re General Black Orchid from Behemoth Gate?" He didn’t explain much, instead admitted himself straightforwardly.

"I heard Gate Master Garen was barely twenty years old, but it seems like you’re more mature than that. Unbelievable." The lady smiled. "Yes, I am Black Orchid. General is just a title, it couldn’t compare to yours."

"My time is running out and I have other matters to attend to, so let’s not beat around the bush. The situation in the country no longer have room for infighting. About your sect, you must know, I was not the one who started the feud. You were the one who incited my senior sister’s betrayal." Garen stated expressionlessly.

"This was our fault, but White Cloud Gate was not one of our concern at that point. It was only after your ascension that this happened. Strength equals dominion, it was the law of nature. Now that you’re strong enough, we no longer have reasons to fight against each other." The lady paused, "This was also one the reason I requested Lieutenant Lycian to mediate. Only the Strong Ones may earn respect."

"And by that you mean…"

"We’ll give up on the South and will retreat completely." Black Orchid sipped her tea, "We will also abdicate from avenging Clark, that way we’ll be even."

"Even if you struggle, you won’t be able to do anything else in the South." Garen smirked. "This outcome was already in my grasp, your offer lacks sincerity."

"Kid, don’t be too arrogant…" Cold fury flashed through her face. "You are strong, but don’t you assume what you saw was the entirety of our power."

"Me? Arrogant? You were the one who initiated the mediation, but you didn’t even want to show any sincerity, and you dare to call me arrogant?" Garen responded with the same fury. "Don’t assume I don’t know that your headquarters is in the North. I wouldn’t mind a war between your sect and I, at least then I can find out whether you sect is stronger or the Immortal Palace Alliance!"

"Let’s not jump to conclusion so soon. Since both of you willingly participate in this mediation, it’s obvious both side were sincere about this. Let’s back up a little for my sake." Lycian interjected, reminding them of his presence with his kind face.

"Let’s agree to this, for my sake, Behemoth Gate will retreat from the South and will discuss with White Cloud Gate when their future operations involving the South. Likewise, White Cloud Gate will discuss with Behemoth Gate in the future whenever they need to move to the North. What do you think?

"What if the discussion didn’t happen?" General Black Orchid sneered.

"Then it’s not my fault if I kill them." Garen recomposed himself. "For Lieutenant Lycian’s honor’s sake, I agree."

"Likewise!" Clenching her jaw, Black Orchid echoed Garen.

To be honest, if it weren’t for Garen and his companions’ victory against Immortal Palace Alliance in Picardi, the Behemoth Gate wouldn’t request for a truce so readily.

Garen and Andrela were still somewhat easier to handle, at least they were more straightforward.

The difficulty lies with King of Nightmares. This person can shapeshift into any identity they choose, be it male or female, young or old. More horrifyingly, they are proficient in hypnosis and have the title of King of Hypnosis. With an enemy like this, it wasn’t their true power that was hard to manage, but their tracking and anti-tracking abilities.

With a character like this, no organizations would be able to conceal themselves completely. If a war breaks out, with King of Nightmares’ help, Garen will have the entire Behemoth Gate thrown into disarray in no time…

Black Orchid didn’t even dare to imagine when that happens.

Because of Behemoth Gate’s deviant initiation method, they have made enemies out of everyone. If they were exposed…

This was also why they requested General Black Orchid to call for a truce.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. Chinese idiomatic phrase meaning to pay respects to an elder or to give honor.

Chapter 207: Meeting 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A verbal agreement was one thing, but concrete action was another altogether.

Black Orchid observed Garen through narrowed eyes for a moment, and then lightly took a sip from her cup of tea.

"I heard that Gate Master Garen managed to stop the people from Immortal Palace at Picardi. It’s making quite the uproar through the world of martial arts." Black Orchid put down her teacup, and patted her hands lightly. "When they heard that Gate Master Garen had agreed to meet here, the elite warriors of our Behemoth Gate fought each other for the chance to experience your ultimate Body Hardening Technique."

Garen’s expression didn’t change. The elite fighters of the Behemoth Gate wouldn’t stop at anything less than a personal experience of his powers. They were obviously here to scout out his abilities.

"I have also long heard that the Behemoth Gate likes to recruit potential geniuses from all walks of life and disciplines. In that case, the fighters you have raised must be extraordinary. Allow me to widen my horizons."

"Since you have agreed, Gate Master, then I shall ask the General to arrange an arena." Black Orchid smiled slightly, and slowly stood. "Other than the leader of the Behemoth Gate, there are two of our strongest fighters. I believe they won’t disappoint you, Gate Master."

"I hope so." Garen stood, and fell silent.

Lieutenant General Lycian had guessed this would happen, so he stood at the same time and led the two of them out through a small door on the left.

Passing through a narrow wooden corridor, the three of them quickly arrived at a spacious concrete area behind the meeting place.

The arena was oval-shaped and surrounded on all sides by almost a thousand soldiers, all armed to the teeth. And on the right end of the arena, there were already two people waiting.

One of the two had been standing while the other crouched, but upon seeing the other three enter, both of them instantly stood at attention.

Garen observed the duo, one man and one woman, closely. The man had his hair falling over his shoulders and stubble all over his face, wearing a long white robe that looked like a bathrobe. Only his eyes were a strange blue-green, just like those of a cat or wolf.

The woman had a slender but healthy figure, and was wearing skintight leather like Cynthia, except hers was all red. Her waist and limbs swayed gently, her arms twisting flexibly like snakes. In contrast, her skin was shockingly white, like someone who just recovered from a horrible illness.

A pair of red eyes fixed tightly onto Garen, with a vague flash of cruelty in them.

"Red, White. Gate Master Garen wants to see the true essence of our Behemoth Gate martial arts. Which of you would like to demonstrate first?"

"Me first." The long-haired man was probably the one Black Orchid called White. He took one step forward, standing in the middle of the arena. With a wave of his right palm, there were suddenly five transparent crystal blades in between his fingers, each as thin as a cicada’s wing.

"Top level fighters who can stand their own against the Immortal Palace only come once every few decades. I would like to experience Gate Master Garen’s mystical powers for myself." The man chuckled coldly. "Please."

Be it Black Orchid, Red, or White, none of them actually mentioned the issue of key importance.

It was the fact that the two fighters here who had been brought out of the Behemoth Gate, together with Black Orchid herself, were in fact the three strongest members of the Behemoth Gate. Most importantly, the three of them had faced the Imperial Palace head-on before, and likewise managed to get out of the encounter intact.

If Sylphalan wasn’t so ridiculously over-powered, the Imperial Palace might not have been able to suppress the Behemoth Gate.

The Behemoth Gate had had their way for several decades. Butterfly Blade Barcrand, from the same generation as Sylphalan, was a top-tier fighter who had escaped over the sea from the Azure Continent. The Blue-eyed Butterfly Assassination Group that was founded in and terrorized the Azure Continent had later been destroyed by the Imperial Palace over a dispute in profits.

Garen gripped his fists lightly, and slowly stepped forward.

"Blue-eyed Butterfly, Barcrand? To think you were still alive, and you even joined the Behemoth Gate."

"You know me?" Barcrand was rather taken aback, but he immediately laughed nonchalantly, "Compared to how you, the White Cloud Gate Master, had your reputation spread across the entire Confederation within a few short years, I am still far from your match."

"You, sir, are a legendary senior." Garen smiled, "Since you’ve already retired into the shadows, why do you still come out to look for a beating? Old guys should stay in their wheelchairs and live the rest of their few remaining days quietly."

"You got an impressive mouth on you! I wonder if your hands are as impressive," Barcrand’s expression didn’t change as he said calmly.

"Won’t you know as soon as you start the attack?" Garen stood with his hands behind his back, his eyes slowly narrowing.

Neither of them won an advantage in the war of words, so they decided to abandon speaking altogether, and just observed each other closely.

Phiuw…

A cold breeze blew past them.

Barcrand instantly vanished, quietly, without a trace, as though he had completely disappeared.

Garen was slightly taken aback, and carefully felt for the movements around him. But he couldn’t find any trace of this person whatsoever.

Swish!

He cocked his head, and sparks flew instantly on his left cheek. Something transparent and sharp had sliced across his face.

"Interesting. Assassination Knife Techniques, is it?" It was Garen’s first time facing this strange field of martial arts. Even though Palosa’s moves from back then were called the Assassination Fist Technique, the truth was he used his fists so openly and honorably that they could no longer be considered an Assassination Fist Technique.

Psst!

Another row of sparks appeared on Garen’s right arm. That piercing sound of friction, sharp enough to make one’s teeth ache, continued to linger in the air.

As for those watching from the sidelines, Black Orchid’s and the Red woman’s eyelids kept twitching. They knew very well how much damage White could inflict with his slices. Even Duskdune Shura wouldn’t dare stand still like this when facing White. But when faced with Garen…

Lieutenant General Lycian’s scalp had gone numb.

"Unbelievable… To think the human body could reach such a high level of hardness!!" He murmured under his breath non-stop, looking at Garen as though the latter was a monster.

Psst!!

More sparks exploded from Garen’s chest. Garen suddenly laughed, just once, and threw his left arm backwards. The air was smacked loudly, producing a piercing sound.

In that moment, a shadow staggered before disappearing into the air. It was obvious he had been scraped by that split-second attack.

"Never let it be said that I don’t know how to respect my elders." Garen pulled back his left hand, looking at the faint traces of blood on his fingertips.

Slowly, he started walking forth. Rows after rows of sparks kept erupting on his body, but after every bout of sparks, he would casually brush past Barcrand’s shadow without fail.

Psst!

Another shadow aimed a strike at his left ear hole without mercy. This was also the only place on Garen’s body where the defense was slightly weaker.

Barcrand held his breath, all the power in his body focussed on the sharp blade in his hand. His body twirled in mid-air, his arm similarly spinning at high speed, like the tip of an electric drill.

"It’s over." Suddenly, Garen’s voice spoke into his ear.

A powerful force struck his waist fiercely from the side.

Barcrand’s expression shifted slightly, the tip of the knife in his hand slipping downwards instantly to act as a shield in front of his waist. At the same time, his body curved upwards like a butterfly amongst flowers, and he actually managed to evade the brunt of the attack.

Barroom!!

His whole body was struck away by Garen’s whip kick, and he flew into a nearby wall with all the impact of a bullet.

Eerily, the wall split into an infinite number of small pieces without a sound. Barcrand’s figure stood on the collapsed wall, looking ever so slightly worse for the wear, as he stared at Garen with a serious expression. His right hand hung loosely at his side, evidently dislocated.

"What fast reflexes," White sighed sincerely.

At the last moment, Garen did hold back a little. Although they fought fiercely with their words, neither side was willing to bring the conflict one step higher, both opting to leave some space to maneuver. According to legends, Butterfly Blade could control five Butterfly Blades at once, but he had used just one earlier. It was obviously just a test.

With the familiarity of an old hand, Barcrand lightly pressed his dislocated arm together, and it fell back in place with a ‘crack’.

"Next one." Garen looked at the woman in red by the side.

Red took a step forward, her whole body emitting a faint aroma. A slight breeze blew past, and the smell entered Garen’s nostrils, relaxing his body and mind. The woman had eyes as sharp as a hawk’s, her whole person radiating an aura that contained a hint of coldness and cruelty. Her long chestnut hair was tied into a ponytail that hung behind her. After seeing that short test between Garen and White, the tinge of easygoingness on her face had also gradually vanished. In its place was the careful wariness of a beast before the hunt.

With a swoosh, she pulled out two identical fiery-red guns from goodness knows where. The barrels were thick and large, with spiders engraved onto them.

"My martial arts is a new trend, a mix of guns and Secret Techniques, so watch out."

Without waiting for Garen’s reply, she fired her first shot with a ‘bang’.

Strangely, the bullet from that shot wasn’t particularly fast, but it left a clear trail of white smoke in the air.

Garen tilted his body slightly, the bullet brushing past his shoulder.

Bang!!

There was the sound of a muffled explosion from behind him, the burning red flames coloring Garen’s face crimson.

That bullet had hit the wall behind him, and immediately exploded like a grenade.

"A custom-made explosive bullet, is it?" Garen instantly took three more steps back.

Bang-bang-bang!!

Three more explosions, and three more clouds of red flames on the wall behind him.

Even he wouldn’t want to test explosive shells like this with his own body. Who knows how strong the explosive power inside was. If it was powerful enough to overcome his defenses, and if it contained poisons at that, he would surely fall where he least expected it.

The only thing he was still vaguely wary of at this point, was high temperature weapons like these.

Just as he steadied his footing from his retreat, a red shadow flashed past his eyes.

Red actually began fighting at close distance. Two long reverse-hooks extended from the grips of her guns, piercing through the air at Garen like a pair of fangs.

The two were so close, their bodies were almost plastered together. Standing in the middle of the arena, they emitted a continuous barrage of metal clanging sounds.

Directly in front of Garen, Red had completely morphed into a flurry of flames, her movements strange and unpredictable like an eight-legged crimson spider. Her attacking patterns were completely unlike regular martial artists, as she used those sharp thorns to aim at the vital spots on the lower body. But at the same time, her speed was extraordinarily fast, her angles hard to catch.

Garen had never before encountered such a vulgar manner of attacking, and couldn’t adjust in that moment. As such, he was forced into retreating repeatedly.

Psst!

His belt was hooked and cut, making Garen reach for his belt in a hurry to prevent his pants from falling off. As the Master of a Gate, as the strongest fighter in the South, his reputation and image were an important trademark for the entire power.

And as a man, if he were forced to run buck-naked by this woman here, even an eventual victory would count as a loss.

Red chuckled sweetly, easily did a backflip, and fired two shots in mid-air.

Bang, bang! Two clouds of red flames erupted on either side of Garen at the same time, the kickback making him retreat backwards the entire time.

Hearing Red’s laughter, Garen started to grow rather angry. She was either aiming for his lower body, or his butt, all her attacks honed in on his fatal spots. Although his Body Hardening Technique was unrivalled, he couldn’t hold up to such a vulgar fighting style.

As soon as he stood steady, he immediately saw Red pouncing at him again while upside down. The two reverse-hooks whistled sharply through the air, aiming straight between his legs.

Chapter 208: Meeting 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Hmph!" Garen finally stopped holding back, and stomped down his right foot.

Boom!!

Large swathes of concrete shards instantly flew into the air, shooting away in all directions like a bomb.

Smack!

A piece of concrete accurately hit Red’s large, perky breasts.

"Ahh~~" This woman actually moaned seductively, somersaulting before landing slowly on the ground not too far away. Her right hand cupped her chest tightly as she stared at Garen resentfully.

Garen’s heart skipped a beat, and he suddenly found his mouth thirsty and his tongue dry.

"Why don’t we end the sparring here." Black Orchid’s voice came from above, "We, the Behemoth Gate, have understood your strength, Gate Master. As expected of the White Cloud Gate Master, the man who could fight against Sylphalan…"

Before he realized it, Black Orchid had soundlessly walked up behind Garen, her soft arms like white jade as they lightly caressed Garen’s chest. There was a hint of seduction on her face, her lips moist and glossy like peaches.

"What are you lot trying to pull?" Garen carefully worked his Blood Qi throughout his body, but didn’t find anything amiss. Having successfully perfected the Divine Statue Technique, and add that to his maxed-out vitality, he should have been completely immune to all diseases. Most poisons also only had a tiny effect on him. Right now, his Blood Qi was shockingly thick, about equal to the blood and flesh essence of a few elephants compressed.

Turning his eye to the side of the arena, Garen abruptly discovered that General Lycian had disappeared without him knowing, and the surrounding soldiers were also retreating non-stop.

Black Orchid’s soft and slender arms held Garen’s face lightly. For some reason, Garen had no intention of rejecting her whatsoever. The places where his skin was in contact with Black Orchid were radiating a bone-numbing sensation.

The fragrance of Black Orchid’s body kept assaulting his nostrils, further agitating his already quickening Blood Qi.

Black Orchid’s cherry lips hung by Garen’s ear as she said softly, "There is only one medicine in this world… that can get past even peak-level Body Hardening Technique…" She grabbed Garen’s hand lightly, and placed them on her own towering breasts.

Whoosh!

The black gown flew upwards, covering the two of them like a black veil.

"Let me bear you a child…" Black Orchid’s voice said softly from underneath the black veil.

All the Blood Qi in Garen’s body erupted in an instant, like black powder set alight. He no longer held back, and no longer wanted to hold back. Although he had no idea what the Behemoth Gate was planning, his natural-born special power was indicating that his current condition wasn’t negative, but positive. Besides, this primal instinct gushing up from deep within his body made him unable to resist it.

Beside them, Red stood up from the floor, her gaze complicated as she looked at the man and woman tangled behind the black veil.

"The world’s strongest woman and the world’s most talented man… A combination like this…"

　　******************

After an unknown period of time.

There was abruptly a loud moan from within the black veil.

Soon after, the black veil started to twirl and rise, enveloping a slim and perfect female body, as it floated directly to land on top of a wall.

At the end, Black Orchid turned back to glance at Garen.

"The world’s most talented man, a child like this would definitely complete our dream!" She felt the intense, tearing pain from her lower body, her gaze complicated.

Red landed softly beside her, and was similarly wordless.

"Go!" Black Orchid lifted her black dress, obscuring both of them from view. Once the dress vanished, the two of them also disappeared without a trace.

Garen lay face-up, the clothes on his body once more tidy and presentable. There were still traces of Black Orchid’s soft fragrance on his body. That water-like feeling and surrounding had him slightly dazed even now.

"The Behemoth Gate…" he chanted lowly, as he slowly stood and glanced towards the direction Black Orchid had left. He lowered his head to look at the bloodied scratches across his chest. It was the first time someone had managed to break his skin with their fingernails since he perfected the Divine Statue Technique.

"To think it would be under these circumstances…" Garen smiled wryly.

He did not know why Black Orchid, as the leader of the Behemoth Gate, would do something like that. But as his first woman in this world, Black Orchid’s body was just like a water current, soft and supple, clear as jade. That faint fragrance, those perfect, slender curves. Every image was imprinted deep into his brain.

Inhaling deeply, Garen tried to chase the lingering temptation and pleasure out of his mind.

He understood what the medicine Black Orchid used was. It was a medicine that could work against peak-level Body Hardening Technique, and it was even an irresistible aphrodisiac.

It was the Heaven Match Powder, from the East. This kind of nearly-extinct aphrodisiac should have been exhausted several centuries ago. To think the Behemoth Gate managed to find a portion.

"Now the relationship’s gotten complicated." Looking at the virgin blood on the floor, Garen suddenly felt a headache coming on. At first, his relationship with the Behemoth Gate was crystal clear. Because of First Senior Sister, both sides had a considerable grudge against the other. Great, now their highest leader had even given him her body’s first night. The previously simple relationship instantly became ambiguous and complicated.

It was obvious to see that Black Orchid had all this planned in advance. She used the intervention as a chance to get closer to him, and drugged him when they were testing him one-on-one. In the end, they achieved their motive.

Helplessly, he turned around and walked towards the exit to the arena. He had no idea since when Lieutenant General Lycian had been standing outside the door, but presently the man smiled at him suggestively.

"How was it? That was the strongest leader of the Behemoth Gate, y’know. Such a strong woman, beautiful, with good skin, strong enough abilities, and wielding considerable power as well. She even took the initiative to drug you and gave herself to you. And you’re still sighing like it’s the end of the world, you chump?"

"Looks like I hadn’t taken the training to build an immunity towards drugs seriously… This time they got me with an aphrodisiac, but next time it could be a poison." Garen shook his head, "And besides, if it weren’t for you, Lieutenant General Lycian, pulling some strings in the middle, their chances of success wouldn’t be that high, would it? Don’t you think you should bear some of the responsibility?"

Lycian chuckled, looking rather awkward. "You already got all the benefits, can’t you leave a little for others? When that woman Black Orchid found me and mentioned about borrowing some seed, even I was shocked. But I still agreed in the end. You know how it is, in the South of the Confederation now, the main conflict is the problem between you and the Behemoth Gate. As long as the two of you have this sort of relationship, when faced with an outside threat, you won’t have to worry about the other side deliberately holding you back."

"Besides, you can relax, the agreement you had with the Behemoth Gate before this still stands. That woman, Black Orchid, is deathly decisive, so once she has made a promise, she will definitely fulfill it." Lycian said with a straight face, "As for my compensation… If I gave you the military position of Upper Major General, would you take it?"

"Sure. Why not?" Garen knew that Lycian represented the higher-ups in the Confederation, and did not hesitate. He understood what the Confederation had in mind as well.

The higher-ups had already discovered the fact that Governor Grant wanted independence. Perhaps they thought that since they couldn’t do anything about that right now, rather than letting a governor who wasn’t close to the higher-ups gain independence, they might as well give the authority to a power who was closer to the government.

"I’ll exert some influence on the governor’s office, don’t worry. Didn’t you give me a military position so I can set camp against that guy?"

"You sure see through things clearly," Lycian said with a nod, somewhat surprised. "It’s very hard to imagine that you are only slightly over twenty this year."

"Alright, now that things are settled on this said, I should get back now. There are still things I need to handle." Garen found this trip to meet and discuss with the Behemoth Gate utterly mystifying.

He carefully observed the attribute pane at the bottom of his field of vision.

To his great surprise, the vitality pane had increased a little again.

From 2.65 to 2.76.

It had obviously increased suddenly after he did that with Black Orchid.

After exiting the hall, Garen got onto a military vehicle and immediately checked into a luxurious hotel according to prior arrangement.

At the same time, Cynthia and Jack, who had been trailing behind, also arrived at the hotel.

Due to his complicated feelings towards Black Orchid, Garen asked the two of them to investigate Black Orchid’s background, while at the same time calling a temporary halt on some of the actions he had been taking to raid the Behemoth Gate.

But in truth, up until now, the Behemoth Gate’s bases in the South had already been pulled up by the roots under the joint attack of various powers such as the King of Nightmares’ Sirens, the Celestial Circle Gate, the Crimson Sand Sword, and the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate. They had lost almost a hundred members. This may well be the Behemoth Gate’s worst loss in recent decades.

So even if Garen asked them to temporarily cease action for now, it was already meaningless.

Reining in his good mood from before, Garen stayed at the hotel for two days. Cynthia also obtained Fenistine’s current home and company addresses.

Following these addresses, Garen searched.

　　　******************

In the Yang Liu city area, in front of a dilapidated office building.

Garen slowly walked up to the entrance of the office building and stood firm, frowning slightly as he looked at the building.

It was all crooked and twisted, like a grey plastic box about to fall into pieces. There were graffitied swear words all over the walls, and there was even a pile of steaming hot dog shit on the ground by the metal door.

The people who walked past him were mostly peasants wearing simple clothes. Some of them had green tattoos peeking out from their necks, acting like hooligans.

Meow~~~

A filthy stray cat walked slowly past Garen’s feet. Most of its black fur had fallen off, the rest of it lay in patches just like a leper.

"Cynthia, are you sure Fenistine’s company is in a place like this?" Garen turned around to ask Cynthia very suspiciously.

His pretty subordinate was currently wrapped up in thick cotton clothes, wearing a hat and gloves. Even so, she kept on attracting some nearby hooligans’ filthy gazes.

"I’m sure it’s here, yesterday Miss Fenistine just beat up a hooligan here."

Garen shook his head. He never thought Fenistine’s situation would be so bad.

"Never mind, let’s just go in and see."

"Yes."

The two of them walked into the office building, one after the other. As soon as they got in, they saw a fat man with a large beard swaying as he walked down.

The fat man was wearing a wool shirt and black-rimmed glasses. Seeing Garen and Cynthia, he immediately pushed up his glasses and carefully considered the two of them.

"May I ask who you’re looking for?"

"Is this the Green Pine Auction House?" Cynthia stepped forward and asked.

"Yes, you two are here for General Manager Fenistine, aren’t you? Plrease come in, the manager is upstairs." The fat man took out a dirty handkerchief to wipe his forehead. "Actually, no matter how you rush us, we can’t give you any more money. As you can see, we have even sold the building that was the company’s headquarters, and sold a large majority of the merchandise…" He turned around and led the two of them downstairs, all the while explaining the poor misfortune of Green Pine with an expression of pain.

The more Garen and Cynthia, the less they had to say. This fatty didn’t even bother to ask why they were here, which obviously meant that too many people had been demanding debts here recently, to the point where he had gotten numb to it.

Chapter 209: Reason 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"If memory serves me correctly, Green Pine should have been a larger auction company, right?" Garen asked, perplexed. "How did it end up like this?"

The fatty glanced at him and nodded in affirmation. "True, Green Pine was very famous before, with fixed customer bases both inside and outside the country. The only thing is recently, the company’s source of liquid funds were all frozen, so we couldn’t make ends meet for a while. Our previous competitors also piled on the pressure, and then there were multiple serious mistakes with the purchase of merchandise, so we lost a considerable sum there as well. In other words, it was like all our misfortune from before befell us all at once, and everything that could go wrong did go wrong. My god…" Speaking of what happened in the past, the fatty’s face was presently still unhappy and depressed.

He led Garen and Cynthia into an office on the third floor and knocked the door. "Big Sis, there are more people here."

"Bring them in… One more won’t make a difference." A tired voice came from within.

The door was pushed open, and the two of them walked in while the fatty stayed behind to close the door.

The room was empty, with only a large, long table in the middle. A young woman was sprawled on it, writing something on the table and looking deeply exhausted.

The woman was very young. Even her gold-rimmed glasses and black professional lady’s outfit could not hide her air of childish youth. Her blonde hair was tied into a bundle, and her dark blue eyes showed a deep-seated weariness.

She raised her head and pushed up her glasses, looking at Garen and Cynthia carefully. Her expression was first of confusion, and then she frowned. She looked obviously hesitant.

"May I ask, you are…?"

Garen couldn’t help but laugh. "You don’t recognize even me anymore?" His voice hadn’t changed at all from before.

As soon as he spoke, Fenistine’s eyes widened, and she stood abruptly. "You!! You’re Garen!! Why are you suddenly here, why didn’t you tell me beforehand?!!"

Garen shook his head. "I just had something to see you for, but it seems that you’ve hit a wall yourself."

Fenistine smiled wryly. "It’s just a small matter, didn’t you go to university? Why do you have time to come here?"

Garen casually pulled a bench to the table and sat down. "Forget about me, what about you? What on earth are you doing now? How did you end up like this?"

Fenistine wiped her face, sitting down as she said helplessly, "I don’t know either. Starting from three months ago, it’s like I fell into a run of bad luck, and nothing good at all happened to me. Even good things ended up becoming bad. By the time I realized it, things have become like this."

Garen frowned as he said, "Explain it to me in detail."

He already had a hunch at this point. He could vaguely sense a thick air of Antique of Tragedy on Fenistine. It was highly likely that this thing was causing her run of bad luck.

As Fenistine slowly described the events leading up to this, he also gradually understood what had been happening.Navici

The root cause of it all was going to Navici, in the Jade Mountain Province near the border.

Fenistine waited but never got Garen to agree to go with her, so she decided to go alone and excavate clues about the mysterious incident from that secret underground vault they had found.

He still remembered the message on that paper slip.

"Navici Tsunami Mountain, number 174, the third tree, six feet under. I left the item there. --Charlie."

According to Fenistine’s story, she had gone alone to find the object mentioned in that message. In the end, she brought it back and kept it in a secret vault.

"What is it? What made you so nervous?" Garen asked in confusion.

Fenistine glanced at Cynthia, who was standing behind Garen.

"Cynthia, leave for now." Garen waved at her.

Cynthia nodded, turned around and left the room, closing the door behind her. With that, only Garen and Fenistine were left in the room.

"Who knew? You’re doing pretty well yourself, huh?" Fenistine looked rather surprised to see that. "I thought she was your girlfriend. To think, she’s your lackey?"

"I’m not particularly well, it is what it is." Garen was still sorting out what he had just heard. "Do you still have the item you excavated?"

"No, I sold it long ago. At first I suspected it was due to an Antique of Tragedy as well, but I’m still the same after selling it." She bent her body down a little, lowering her voice, "I’m telling you… The thing I found was a tiny, really small wooden carving. According to my deductions, that thing is definitely a very formidable Antique of Tragedy!"

Garen watched Fenistine and her expression of mystery in exasperation. He really wanted to say that he had discovered that a long time ago, but seeing how Fenistine was trying so hard to build up the suspense, he couldn’t bring himself to interrupt her.

There was a thick air of potential misfortune from the Antique of Tragedy surrounding Fenistine. It had evidently accumulated after she spent too much time with the Antique of Tragedy, and it would take at least a few months of bad luck for it to dissipate. Garen mused it over, but decided to immediately reach out his hand anyway.

With a ‘smack’, he accurately grabbed Fenistine’s wrist.

"Don’t panic, I’ll check your condition. I know some Eastern medicine."

Fenistine’s face reddened in an instant, and she opened her mouth to say something, but she never did say it. In the end, she just let Garen hold her wrist.

As soon as the two of them touched, that thick air of misfortune was quickly absorbed by Garen until there was not a trace left.

"Alright, it’s fine now." Garen released Fenistine’s hand, and smiled as though nothing happened. "Your condition now isn’t that great, do you need my help?"

"Can you?" Fenistine recovered in an instant, looking at Garen half-believingly. "You have to know, I need a substantial amount of money right now."

"It’s fine, just tell me."

Fenistine knew that Garen had inherited the White Cloud Gate, but the White Cloud Gate was merely a trifle. How much money could a local gate like that fork out?

"I need at least two hundred million in liquid assets, to have a proper turnover," she said in a low voice.

"Two hundred million, no problem." Garen had thought it would be a huge sum, and didn’t expect it to be so little. All else aside, just the Black Mark Association that he recently merged with alone could squeeze out the money for Fenistine to use. That wasn’t counting the White Cloud Gate’s power and assets that, in total, had enough financial power to match a provincial government.

To him right now, two hundred million was merely the tip of the iceberg.

But Fenistine was slightly dazed. Her little mouth hung open, her eyes widened, and she looked at Garen dumbly.

"Hey hey hey, you’re not kidding, are you? That’s two hundred million! Not two hundred! I know you inherited the White Cloud Gate, but even if it’s the White Cloud Gate… that’s still too much, right? Why does your expression tell me that two hundred million is two hundred!"

"I’m not kidding." Garen shook his head. "I’ll transfer it over to you in a moment, how about using a Confederal bank account?"

Fenistine stood up, and walked a circle around Garen.

"You little punk… Not bad!"

"Alright, stop fooling around." Garen was speechless. "It’s just that you weren’t aware of it. The truth is regular martial arts sects aren’t all that meets the eye, you just didn’t know about it."

"Fine, I didn’t know anything. But are you sure you’re not kidding?" Fenistine still couldn’t quite believe it.

"No, no," Garen replied helplessly. "Oh, yeah, your family has local connections. Do you know about a woman called Black Orchid? She has a lot of power, and is a martial artist herself."

"Black Orchid, huh. If you didn’t get the name wrong, there is a woman with a lot of power here and a name like that in Yang Liu City. Just the one. She’s the mastermind behind the private rose-colored places here in Yang Liu City." Unsurprisingly, Fenistine did know.

According to the information Garen had gathered, Black Orchid had a decent influence and reputation among Yang Liu City locals, which was why she could convince the Lieutenant General into putting a word in for the Behemoth Gate. So it was very normal for him to get such an answer from Fenistine, who had some base work here.

"How well do you know her?" Garen was still rather unhappy about having a woman take his first night. And he had another layer of concerns behind that.

"That woman, Black Orchid, is very mysterious." Fenistine thought back with a gaze of concentration. "I first saw her at a banquet. She was very beautiful, with a great aura. Back then, she was standing next to the leader of a powerful clan, and they had a great presence. I heard Father say that this woman had methods, and a fierce determination to achieve whatever she set her sights on, together with a lot of hidden power and influences."

"How much do you know about her as a person?"

"Personally? Her?" Fenistine wasn’t stupid, and she immediately sensed something amiss. "Did you offend her?!"

"Mind your own business, just tell me." Garen shook his head.

Fenistine glanced at Garen half-believingly.

"Black Orchid is a powerful woman, and has perfected her martial arts to an amazing degree. She once demonstrated catching a bullet with her bare hands, she’s basically a humanoid monster! And she’s cruel and cold, very decisive. It’s just that previously she took a trip to the Fourth Military Hospital, and apparently fell ill.

"One of my older brothers mentioned that she was injured by someone, though. After escaping with a grievous injury, she nearly died on the road."

"Injured?" Garen frowned. "How do you know such a secret? For elite fighters like Black Orchid, she would definitely hide the fact that she was hurt."

"She got hurt and nearly died, but the captain of the special forces team that protected her was my older brother’s best friend. It was a secret back then, but a lot of time has passed since then, so it’s a secret no more. Any limitations had also been removed." Fenistine replied simply.

"Do you know who injured her?"

"Not sure."

Garen tried to make some inferences.

The largest possibility was that Black Orchid’s injury had affected her abilities, so she wasn’t strong enough to hold up the huge Behemoth Gate on her own anymore. That was why she used the conflict with the White Cloud Gate to retreat, hiding the fact that her own condition was far from great.

And his concerns were related to his own natural-born special powers.

He hadn’t realized it yesterday, but after calming down, he noticed it immediately. Were those natural-born powers hereditary or were they unique to only him?

Judging by Black Orchid’s personality, even if she did have his child, the child’s education would have nothing to do with him. God forbid there one day be appear a monstrous enemy with the same powers as himself, now wouldn’t that be fun.

After obtaining some relevant information from Fenistine’s side, Garen asked Cynthia to send a telegram, informing the White Cloud Gate headquarters to transfer two million over to Fenistine’s company accounts.

As for himself, he returned to the hotel they had decided on.

Chapter 210: Reason 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

While he was chatting with Fenistine, he thought about the source of his special powers and had a vague feeling, as though his powers were sending him a signal.

The attribute and skill panes at the bottom of his field of vision had both started shimmering slightly. It was like countless ripples on the water surface.

At night, he sat cross-legged in his hotel room. On the surface, there weren’t any changes in his body, but his spirit kept trying to catch that little flash of inspiration in his heart.

It was just like a piece of paper flashing through his mind. He could see the words and pictures, but he just couldn’t recall them.

Garen tried his best to catch those traces, or rather, those memories.

As he kept concentrating, the ripples in his attribute pane kept getting larger and larger. Until finally.

Boom!!!

There was an ear-splitting noise, and Garen’s mind was a complete muddle as he descended into oblivion.

After some time, a series of mystifying images appeared in his heart.

In the middle of the endless starry sky.

A red shard sliced past the galaxies at high speed, eventually being pulled in by the Earth’s gravity and crashing into a certain place on Earth.

As the shard burst past the atmosphere, most of it was oxidized, and at the same time it turned into countless tinier pieces, scattering like rain across Earth’s sky.

The rain-like shards entered many living beings without a sound or trace, invisible to the eye. Most of these living beings self-combusted, and were burnt to ashes.

A few of them survived, but were greatly weakened. After contracting all sorts of diseases, they died an early death.

And then there were the ones amongst ten millions, those who were hit but continued with life as usual. The shards had no effect on these people.

Garen quickly noticed his past incarnation. He had also been one of those hit, and was one of the lucky few who were unscathed. At the time, he was a mere teenager.

In the blink of an eye, many years passed. He grew up, started working, all the way until he died of electrocution.

Just as he was electrocuted into a pile of charcoal, a translucent figure slowly rose from his body. It was about to be torn into shreds by the unseen rays radiating through the air, when suddenly the figure glowed with a faint red light from deep within. This light was the unique life of every individual, that little bit of sizable energy born from their bodies, memories, and souls.

It wrapped the figure’s head, blinking continuously, until the head slowly merged with the red light. Finally, both vanished without a trace, while the remaining body that was left behind was directly torn to pieces by the rays.

Strangely, Garen also saw the other people who had lived after being struck by the red shard at the same time.

Those people either died of illnesses, or ended their lives peacefully. Some of them were also killed.

But of all those who died, only three managed to awaken that dot of red light that lay dormant within them. The rest were torn to smithereens.

He was one of these three with the blinking lights. Although the other two managed to awaken the red light, the places they merged with the red light were different. And in the final process of merging, the red light had gradually faded, meaning the merging had failed.

Therefore, of all the countless Earth humans who had been awoken by the red shards, he was the only one who successfully merged with it, and he had merged his head as well.

The red shard was like a stimulant to the DNA of the soul. Some of the creatures succeeded and lived, while others failed and died.

The ones who lived were one in hundreds of millions. And of those who lived, there was another tiny, miniscule chance that they could successfully awaken the red shard.

Of the ones who were activated, they still needed to merge with red light. And the parts that merged were all different.

After Garen absorbed the red light, the soul in his head that was wrapped up in the red light floated slowly through the universe. It sporadically blinked into different unknown universes, before finally being swept up in a space tornado and ended up swept onto this planet. It was then that it was incorporated into a young man named Garen.

As he wandered through the starry sky, Garen gradually began to understand what this sort of red shard was for.

It was a natural mutagen for soul, and only worked on souls. The activated souls would present all sorts of different effects, some useful and others useless. Some were very powerful, while others were extremely weak.

And the difference in the part that was merged also manifested in different results. He was very lucky to have merged his head, and even more fortunately, he was able to find a planet with sentient life and a proper body before his consciousness was ultimately destroyed after aimlessly wandering the starry sky.

The starry universe was limitless. If he wandered for too long under those circumstances, even the strongest would end up grounded into nothing.

If it weren’t for this round of quiet reflection, and his natural-born power having merged with his head, he truly wouldn’t have been able to see so many of these memories.

He didn’t know how it was like for the other creatures awoken by the red shards, but it certainly wasn’t like his situation. After all, every creature’s experiences, lives, and memories were distinct. These differences decided that the red light they had nurtured would also be different, and the special powers developed as a result of the final merging would also be certainly different.

And his special powers, were this body’s attribution abilities. Perhaps his ability to transmigrate was part of that as well.

Sitting cross-legged on his bed, Garen slowly opened his eyes. There was a thin sheen of sweat on his brow.

"So this was the truth of my beginnings…"

He had always wondered where his special powers came from, even though there wasn’t any doubt deep within his memories. But he had never really seen the whole process.

He wasn’t sure what that shard was, but after it activated the red light, it burned itself out completely. That must mean it was some sort of medicine.

He was lucky to have that light merged with his head, so he could retain all of his memories. He was lucky to have found a planet with humans and successfully merged before his consciousness disappeared completely.

"This was basically the lucky result of countless coincidences."

Garen completely understood the source for his natural-born powers.

To put it bluntly, his body on Earth had nurtured a mutated soul. After the body hosting it perished, this one-of-a-kind soul transmigrated through space and time, and was lucky enough to meet a new sentient planet before dying, finding a new merger, and took over someone else’s body.

It was a miraculous process. Without the physical body on Earth, without these memories and experiences from before he was even born, without these countless coincidences, there wouldn’t have been someone as naturally talented as Garen.

And this most basic idea lifted the heavy concerns from Garen’s heart.

This was different from hereditary powers, his were natural powers born from the mutation of his soul. The source was the very quality of his soul, that had changed after being awoken back then.

A hereditary power came from the blood and genes. These were two fundamentally different things.

One was the body, the other was the soul.

The blood was gone once you change a body, but it wasn’t the same for the soul. A power that followed the soul was purely nurture, not nature. So the hereditary powers could be inherited, but the powers of the soul could not…

"It’s fine as long as they can’t be copied. Or else, if there’s someone else with the same powers as me…" Garen knew exactly how strong his powers were. With enough potential, no matter how untalented that person was, as long as they weren’t too unlucky, they could still be pushed to the very top.

But these memories he had just excavated made him realize that souls did indeed exist on Earth. At the very least, he was an example of someone whose soul had mutated.

"In that case, as for the Behemoth Gate…" When Garen imagined the other side discovering the truth, he couldn’t help but relish in their misery. Black Orchid would surely throw a tantrum of crazy proportions.

　　******************

In a hidden underground base somewhere in the Confederation.

Black Orchid’s face was pale as she looked at the white crystal rock in front of her. Her hands dug deeply into the surface of the stone, leaving deep scratch marks.

"How can it be!!?? How is it possible!! How can the essence of such a strong man produce a life reading of only white quality!!" Her eyes were about to spit fire.

"There’s nothing impossible about that." A man with long black hair reaching his chest stood behind her, and replied mildly, "That person didn’t make love to you willingly, but was forced to by drugs. And even normal people could have imperfect descendants, the same goes for strong fighters. The only difference is that the chances would be smaller."

He glanced at Black Orchid. "Alright, time to decide, are you going to have the child or not? Essence Stones aren’t that easily wasted according to your whims."

"I…!" Black Orchid gritted her teeth, her heart suddenly a mess. She had no idea how to respond.

Within the underground chamber, both of them fell silent.

Finally, Black Orchid forced the words out of clenched teeth.

"I’ll have it!! Even if it’s just a normal person, it’s still his son! That man, he won’t be able to leave it alone!"

The long-haired man was about to reply when suddenly, the white crystal that was as tall as a man was dyed a faint wisp of red.

His expression changed, his gaze turned disbelieving.

"How could it be!!"

"What happened!!?" Black Orchid instinctively sensed something amiss, and asked hastily.

The long-haired man’s expression was torn between laughing and crying. He turned his gaze away, his expression as he looked at Black Orchid holding just a hint of pity.

"In the testing process, that man’s essence weakened and died because its life force was too weak… To put it professionally, its chances of living were too low. So you can’t have it even if you wanted to."

Black Orchid froze.

"Then… Then I…" Her voice began to tremble.

"Congratulations, you were f*cked for no reason." The long-haired man looked at her with pity.

Black Orchid stood there, staring.

She wasn’t even aware of when the long-haired man left the room. She just stood in front of the crystal blankly, watching as the stone gradually returned to its original colorless state. It reflected her pale, colorless face,

"Garen!!" She finally spat out those words through gritted teeth.

Just then, Garen was sitting on a plane headed towards the seaside city. He could imagine the ugly expression on Black Orchid’s expression upon discovering the truth. But no matter what, he still had some special feelings for his first woman.

"If we are to come into conflict again, I’ll make her death easier," he told himself. Without that mental burden on him, his relationship with the Behemoth Gate was simplified once more.

At the same time, he finally understood the source of his powers. He was no longer worried about hereditary powers, and so that lifted a heavy weight from his chest.

Chapter 211: Gathering 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After all, the Behemoth Gate provoked First Sister Senior, killed Second Senior Brother, and killed Great Elder. Back then when the White Cloud Gate nearly fell apart, they had also played quite a role in that.

If he really did end up adding another layer of that nature to their relationship, he wouldn’t be able to get over the roadblock in his own heart.

Sitting in the plane, Garen rearranged all the relationships in his head from ground up. At the same time, he twiddled with with a dainty gold-colored seal in his hand. This was the Antique of Tragedy that was causing Fenistine all that bad luck. With his current level of power and influence, all he needed were a few words to get it back.

The seal itself was just a very simple Antique of Tragedy. He absorbed all its potential points in one go, and it gave him 4 points of potential in stock. However, since the Golden Sword Throne was becoming extremely slow, this was still a considerable reward.

Now he had 15 potential points in store. Too bad his body had reached its limit, so he couldn’t use those points.

Even this thing had been relegated to nothing more than a toy in his hands.

With this trip, he had more or less dealt with the Behemoth Gate. No matter how forceful Black Orchid was, she could no longer come out to muddle things up when her condition was so bad. Although there was a storm blowing through the country right now, as long as he had the help of the Nightmare’s group of Sirens, he could find an escape route overseas even if something went terribly wrong.

Now there were the Celestial Circle Gate, the White Cloud Gate, and the Sirens. The three gates had practically become a coalition in both attack and defense, their combined power expanding to almost ridiculous levels. They had more or less become a large-scale martial group that transcended countries.

Even if he wasn’t getting sufficient input, it was still more than enough for him to protect himself.

"Everything is prepared and ready. This might be the final fight." Garen tilted his face towards the airplane window, a hint of anticipation and excitement in his heart.

Perhaps he himself didn’t know why he wasn’t the slightest bit worried about the upcoming conflict, but that feeling of relief that he would soon understand it all was already filling his entire body up to the brim.

　　　　************

Brrr…

Outside the glass window of the wide airplane lounge, a blue military plane with stripes gradually lowered onto the ground and landed steadily on the runway, rapidly decelerating.

In front of the huge floor-to-ceiling glass window, two extremely eye-catching men were watching the landing plane through the glass.

Of these two men, one was wearing a black suit with a pitch black tie, holding a sword in his hand wrapped in black cloth. His long hair fell over his shoulders, and he was even wearing a black eyepatch over one eye. It was Andrela, who had rushed over here long ago.

The other person had a seductive looks and an enchanting figure, wearing long white androgynous sleeves and pants, with long hair tied into a ponytail. If it weren’t for that flat chest, no one would think he was a man.

Nightmare leaned their whole body onto Andrela’s shoulder, their beautiful eyes watching the decelerating plane lazily.

"Garen’s so slow, and he arrived so late."

"He had more things to handle than we did, it’s perfectly normal," Andrela replied calmly. "With this trip, I’m the weakest one here. This might be my biggest challenge. If I can get past it, I will surely be able to improve further, and attain the same level as you guys."

"And then?" Nightmare played with their companion’s hair, their interest piqued. "Then you can take the captain’s seat in bed? True, I was always the one on top, it’d be good to change it up once in a while."

Andrela was speechless.

"Don’t you have anything to do? Is it okay for you to be hanging around my place all the time?"

"I got it all arranged nicely." Nightmare smiled. "Oh my, Palosa’s here too."

Before they even finished their sentence, a regular little old man walked soundlessly out of the crowd nearby. He looked just like the old men selling lunch boxes on the street, with his white-grey robes and dusty face. He held a cane in his hand, and slowly limped over to them.

Palosa walked slowly until he was within ten paces of the two, and stopped. He narrowed his eyes and stared at Nightmare, surprise flashing through his eyes.

"I’m not late, am I?"

"No, the last one will arrive in a moment." Nightmare straightened up, holding a golden pocket-watch in their hand to check the time. "It’s 3.14 pm. The weather now is pretty suitable for going out to sea too, so we can leave today."

"That’s good."

Palosa walked up to the rows of seats and sat down, then proceeded to close his eyes and rest while steadfastly ignoring everyone.

For a moment, all three of them fell silent.

Most of the people in the airport weren’t regular people. The ones walking to and fro were either military officials, millionaires, or other even more powerful people. There were only a few people here and there, but once in a while there would be someone hurrying past, surrounded by a group of bodyguards.

The three of them were actually pretty inconspicuous compared to the rest. They didn’t have policemen, guards, or even a female companion. They were no different from other regular citizens.

"Since we’re going there this time, there should be quite a few people arriving, right?" Andrela asked Nightmare softly.

"Not quite a few, there are a ton. Some people want that secret treasure no matter what, while we’re partly in it out of curiosity, and partly in it for the revenge. There are others too, who probably want reduce the Confederation’s power. There are surely many elites heading there." Derision flashed across Nightmare’s face. "I bet many countries will send their elites over. That secret treasure, huh… If it really is that useful, then any person, group, or country would find unimaginable uses and research values in it. No power would be willing to let it go."

"True."

As the two were talking, a man with short purple hair and red eyes walked out of a distant entrance. He was wearing a black suit and a large wool coat, looking just like any regular rich leader. He even had two fully-armed female soldiers in black uniforms next to him.

"Here he is, with two female soldiers to boot. What a textbook example of a military general, tsk-tsk," Nightmare exclaimed.

"We’re all here, so let’s go. The ship’s ready, too," Andrela said softly. "This time we have to get our revenge and our treasure. We can finally end it all."

Palosa seemed to sense something too, opening his eyes to look at Garen calmly. He stood up, and walked to Nightmare’s and Palosa’s sides.

The three of them watched Garen striding towards them.

　　******************

A few thousand nautical miles off Smoke Island, on a deserted patch of sea.

The deep blue seawater roiled under the blue sky and white clouds as a large white ship sailed slowly towards Smoke Island.

The ship was fully armored, with a sharp spike on the helm. There were swathes of navy soldiers in white uniforms running across the deck sporadically, hurrying to adjust the ship’s direction.

On the helm, a stout man with white skin was stepping on the banister with one foot, staring into the distance.

The large man wore the white navy uniform with two white-gold medals on his shoulders. His chest and nipples were bared, revealing a large tuft of black chest hair.

How long more to that What’s Island?" he asked, his words garbled by the toothpick in his mouth.

"We can reach by nighttime. Probably…" a solemn-looking blonde female adjutant said hesitantly beside him.

"How many people are coming this time? Anything worth notice?" the large man asked, spitting out his toothpick.

"This time we’ve confirmed the validity of the secret treasure, and all the countries think it’s very valuable. No fewer than thirty powers are joining in this hunt. The ones we should watch out for are Fivestar Continent’s King of the North Pole, Gyard, and Mare, the Spearmaster. There’s White Peacock from Stonecliff Continent, and King of the Gun, Nikon. Then there’s the Card Clown, and the Three Great Generals from our Weisman. That, and the legendary Immortal Palace." The female adjutant finished explaining, and added, "Seven powers in total, but we can’t be sure if any of them will join forces. After all, we don’t have any skilled telekinesis users, so we can’t find any traces."

"Seven powers? That many?" The large man rubbed the stubbles on his chin. "They all look like formidable fellows…"

"They are indeed. These people and powers coming here are almost all the strongest characters from their respective countries or continents. They don’t usually come into contact with each other, so they’re the apex fighters of their respective areas, dominating without opposition. But this time they’re gathered in one place, or rather, all the elites from around the whole world have basically gathered here," the female adjutant said calmly. "Those who dare to alight on this island all have absolute confidence in themselves. This is no longer a fight between a single country or continent."

"Isn’t that even better?" The large man’s smile was excited. "With all these delicious fellas gathered in one place, would our three generals still have to fight each other? Opponents as far as the eye can see!"

"General Milo, please beware. These aren’t people you can take lightly, they’re all people who can conquer a country or even a continent. They’re the cream of the crop, chosen from countless others. If it weren’t for the appearance of the Black Smoke Pot, there’s no way so many of them would show up. After all, contacting the dead is a small thing, but being able to transcend life and death, to achieve immortality, that’s the real deal!" The adjutant reminded him exasperatedly.

"Relax, do I seem so reckless?" Milo chuckled.

　　　***************

At the same time, far away at the shore of Fivestar Continent, Port Bolivia.

A huge black cruise ship was advancing slowly, spitting out a long column of white smoke that reached for the sky. The cruise was a few hundred meters long, and a few hundred meters wide. At the entrance to the ship, many passengers were neatly lined up to board the ship.

"Don’t worry, I’ll be back in no time. This is an international meeting held by the company, it’s just a little longer than usual, otherwise it’s the same business as usual."

A man in a white overcoat hugged his wife, and then kissed his daughter’s little face, his own smile warm and gentle.

"Papa, you gotta bring Yawen back a toy, okay." The little girl was just five, with red lips, white teeth and fair skin that made her look unbelievably innocent and adorable.

"I’ll remember for sure." The man pinched his daughter’s face fondly. "Alright, I’m off."

"Be careful on the road, give way should you get in trouble, don’t pick any more fights than you have to. Your safety comes first," the wife advised him worriedly. Her complexion was unnaturally pale, her beautiful face like white-jade porcelain, without even a hint of color.

She stepped up to kiss her husband’s lips lightly, and then put a large white fox fur coat onto his shoulders.

"I know, I know," the man repeated. "Don’t worry, I’ll be back soon."

He stepped onto the boarding plank, squeezing into the crowd flowing into the ship. He turned around occasionally to look at his wife on the shore, holding their daughter’s hand and waving non-stop.

"Go home!" he yelled loudly.

The wife nodded hard, but had no intention of turning around.

Looking at the wife’s figure, for some reason, the man’s eyes suddenly grew moist.

"Allie… I won’t let you die before I do…" he murmured under his breath.

In that moment, unwavering determination flashed past his eyes. He turned around and disappeared into the crowd, striding towards the ship.

"I will survive and return to you… For I am the God of Spear, Mare!"

Chapter 212: Gathering 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

From the northern sky of Smoke Island, groups of tiny black dots in the distance congealed to a massive group, slowly moving inland.

The group of dots resembled flocks of black birds soaring against the blue sky, completely uniform, lacking differentiation.

Every single black dot was a fighter aircraft. Not regular aircraft, but strange pieces of machinery with odd shapes. From the bottom of their fuselages spouted two additional boat-like long boards, which betrayed their identity as a next-generation seaplane.

The aircraft flew past the airspace swiftly and, after a while, was trailed by a small plane.

Behind this aircraft following closely was a black hot air balloon with a black, rectangular wooden boat dangling below.

There were a group of men in black scattered in the boat. All of them were equipped with thick black leather shirts, goggles, hats and scarfs.

"Boss, is it true that the Black Smoke Pot is able to increase a human’s life span? And we can even use it to communicate with the dead?"

One of the men in black shouted as he asked the men in black who stood at the very front.

No one would be able to be heard clearly under such a windy conditions without shouting.

"They said that it has been proven! I’ve sent people to verify it’s validity. The Black Smoke Pots that appeared in the past did indeed have such an ability!" The man in the lead answer loudly. No one could see his face as it was hidden under the thick shirt. Only his strong body figure could be made out with that get up.

"Have you prepared the bear skin and fox skin that will be traded later?" The leader asked loudly.

"All done! You won’t be humiliated!" The underling replied loudly as well.

"Donze! Is it true that your mum has given birth again recently?" The leader shouted.

"Yeah. It’s the sixth child! How about your mum!" Donze shouted back.

"My mum isn’t as great as yours!"

"No no! My mum is definitely no match to yours!"

"Don’t say that. My mum definitely can’t give birth…"

"Back in the days, my mum…"

A group of people were standing behind feeling helpless. How embarrassing! They had seen people one-upping one another with everything except their mothers’ ability to give birth...

Fortunately they were in the sky. If they were at the ground…

They might have embarrassed the whole northern community!

"Is this the legendary King of North Pole?" The young guy and girl from the very back of the hot air balloon were staring at the people who were at the front.

"It’s him… That two doofuses are the strongest in the North Pole…" Another girl replied as she sighed. "Although I really don’t want to admit it, only the two of them are qualified to participate in this battle."

"I have a bad feeling about this…"

"You’ll get used to it." The girl patted on the guy’s shoulder.

Below the balloon, on the patch of ocean.

Similar to the white fish swimming in the sea, there were multiple white yachts cutting across the water on the blue sea at high speed, leaving white trail wakes behind them.

The wake created by the yachts cutting the blue sea was clear and obvious.

"Hoo~~~!"

A person on the yacht who had a loose hair and naked from the top of his waist shouted very loudly, and strangely as well.

"Haha! It’s those idiots from the North Pole!" There was a wretched man, dressed like a clown standing on one of the yachts. He was also naked from the top to the waist and there were strange lines of patterns of red, blue and green painted onto his black skin. His makeup was no different than the jokers on a poker card.

The joker raised his head and looked up at the hot air balloon at the top of his head. His virid eyes glowing with the intent to kill.

"Prince! Let’s give them a big present!’

"Roger!"

On the yacht, a golden hair girl with a twisted smile took out a rocket launcher out of nowhere aimed at the sky.

Pew!!

The rocket flew soared upward and went after the hot air balloon, leaving a trail of white smoke and bright light.

"Big fireworks! Big fireworks!! Hehehe~~~" The prince was licking his wet lips as he looked at the sky with anticipation.

Kaboom!

The rocket suddenly self destructed as it flew half way in the air.

The prince was stunned as he looked at the pieces of steel debris falling from the sky.

"It’s raining! It’s raining!!" She started shouting in a high pitch. Her naked upper body was continuously burnt. She motioned her hand so fast that it became blur as she swatted off all of the debris to the other yachts nearby.

"You’re so bad Prince. Haha!" The joker laughed loudly as he drove the yacht away to avoid the debris sent in their direction.

As the members on the yachts did not want to be outdone by each other, they started to use the powerful steel balls as a toy and shoot at each other.

Bam!

One of the steel balls hit the yacht’s bow and punched a hole through the sturdy steel plate.

*************

Smoke Island.

The small, green island was like a piece of jade sitting quietly on the blue ocean.

The island was surrounded by white smoke as if there was a white blanket covering the whole island. The island could only be seen faintly under the blanket of smoke.

The evening sun radiated its faint red light and dyed the whole sea in red.

A black shadow slowly came up to the surface of the sea near the rocky beach on the Northern part of Smoke Island.

With the splash of water, the figure emerged from the water.

It was an oddly black colored, giant submarine. The circular cover on the top of the fuselage cracked open and four human figures emerged, landing firmly onto the rocky beach.

"This is it." One of the black figures said. "The full moon is tomorrow, and I wonder how many top fighters from each country are coming. How exciting…"

"As long as it doesn’t affect our main objective." An old man’s voice came from another black figure. "We must obtain the Black Smoke Pot at all cost! I will let you do the arrangement, Flamingo."

"Sure." The third black figure nodded his head. "Sylphalan is acting up again. We are likely to be attacked since the reputation of the Immortal Palace is too well known. Hence, according to the layout of the island, I suggest we head out to the southern territory of the island first."

"Southern territory?" The man with an old voice asked curiously. "This small island is separated into two territories?"

"The Smoke Island is much larger than you think. It’s very unlikely for anyone to run across the whole island with full speed within a day. We couldn’t determine its size because of the smoke." Flamingo explained." The island is separated in the southern territory and northern territory. Crossing between each is only doable at 11.40pm as the smoke is too thick to navigate in. Furthermore, there are too many unknown dangers ahead of us as well."

The first black figure nodded in agreement: "This means that the war will be separated into two places and we won’t be in a lot of pressure. However, how would you know that they won’t pass through the smoke?"

"No one would take a risk in a fight among equals since the most dangerous thing is not of natural conditions but humans." Flamingo calmly replied. "We have made a name for ourselves, the Immortal Palace on the Smoke Island 50 years ago and became the world’s strongest and mysterious terrorist group. It’s a burden for being so well known, especially in this circumstance.

"How should we divide the Black Smoke Pot when we got it?" The old voice asked again.

"Free for all," Flamingo replied.

"Alright."

"You have no problem with this right, Sylphalan?" Flamingo looked at the last black figure.

"Can’t die from this…" Sylphalan replied with a coarse voice. He took down his hood and revealed a face filled with scars.

"Alright then. Let’s move out."

As soon as Flamingo finished his sentence, four of them instantly disappeared from the beach and formed 4 black lines, moving inland.

**************

"The Smoke Island has a forest terrain, a rocky terrain and a lot of other complicated terrains that have yet to be explored." Andrela was noting down on a small notebook as he spoke eloquently.

The four of them were on a big military ship heading towards the Smoke Island.

The military ship was surrounded by a large amount of smaller battleships. All of them were blue with a stamp of the Federation’s military insignia.

Andrela looked at the remaining four people and said with a smile on his face: "It seems like the terrain in Smoke Island can change at any time. It’s constantly surrounded by smoke, vision is ineffective, compasses have no effect and other signal instruments are unable to send out any signals as well. Hence, we can only rely on our sense of direction. This environment suits a certain someone to unleash his true strength so we have to be extra careful."

"Assassination? I am a practitioner of Assassination Fist Technique. Let’s talk about other things." Palosa sat on the deck with his knees as he said calmly. "What should we take note of the most?"

Andrela started smiling again.

"Alright, I will talk about what we should take note of the most." He stopped as he saw Garen and the King of Nightmares attracted by his topic.

"The King of the gun, Nikon, who is that old man we saw previously, is most likely the best gunner. There is also the King of North Pole…" He started to give out the intel of the strongest people.

"Then who is the most dangerous?" Garen asked as he lean against the guardrail. "Excluding Sylphalan of the Immortal Palace."

"It’s me." Andrela started to smile crazily.

"?"

The few of them were stunned as they looked at Andrela in confusion. He was not an arrogant person so it was rather weird for him to say so.

"I have brought along the latest highly explosive purple bomb. I have brought 15kg of them and could blow this ship we’re currently on up into the sky."

"You don’t have to be so determined." Garen stared at him as he frowned. "I have a grudge against Sylphalan and the King of Nightmares has a grudge against Flamingo. In addition, all of us have an interest to the Black Smoke Pot. This is the reason why we are here. You don’t need to bet your own life on this."

"No no no…" Andrela waved his hand. "I know my own situation. I am different from you. I can feel that I have already reached my peak and improving my current self is nothing but a dream. I can only break my limit and achieve a greater strength if I risk my life! Life? A life without pursuit is meaningless to me."

"You have reached your extreme limit." Palosa sighed.

"Perhaps. However, I am still currently not qualified to go into the extreme limit." Andrela smiled as he replied back.

Chapter 213: Gathering 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen sighed and silently walked to the side of the ship.

He knew that Andrela was gentle on the outside but crazy on the inside from the first time he interacted with him

"It all depends on you since you have already made the decision." The King of Nightmares shrugged. She was currently in a young and cute teenage girl form, which looked exactly like Andrela’s younger sister Aisis. "Alright let’s not talk about these. Drela, do you like my current form? Do you want to do something exciting tonight?" she held her purple skirt as she turned around in a circle. "It’s your biological sister~~"

Andrela didn’t react at all and said. "Regrettably I do not have such a fetish."

"Don’t you feel that it’s very exciting?"

"Not in the least."

"Do you want me to transform into…"

"You do not need to transform into my mother…"

Both of them were flirting with each other as if no one was watching them.

Palosa went to his room to rest, leaving Garen alone on the deck as he looked far to the distance.

As the body of the boat rocked with the motion of the waves, it gave off a sense of insecurity.

Far away at the horizon of the blue sea, there were a group of grey shiny dolphins occasionally jumping out of the ocean as they cut open the sea at high speed, leaving a trail wake behind.

He placed his hands onto the cold black handrail as he gently touched the surface of the rough paint which was somewhat worn and torn.

The cool and salty sea breeze blew on his face and entered his neck.

"Sylphalan…" He murmured. Ever since he met the real Sylphalan which was during the Argent Mirror incident, he no longer had the desire to know the truth about the old man.

"What happened? What are you thinking about?" An unfamiliar voice came from behind.

"Nothing, just feeling a little bit emotional," Garen replied calmly.

The person who stood on his left was a middle aged man with a curly moustache and a cigarette in his mouth. His overall image looked like an old aristocrat in Europe on Earth.

His hair was combed to the point where it was shining. In a black tuxedo, he was fiddling a small and unique silver pistol in his hand as it kept producing a clicking sound.

"Major General Nikon. We all have our reasons. What’s yours? Why did you participate in this operation?" Garen looked at the famed master who was known as the King of the Gun.

"About that… It’s just a small matter. I’ve been wanting to visit the Smoke Island because I heard that it has a very good scenery."

Garen laughed as he knew he had wanted to avoid the topic.

"Let’s change the question then. How do you view this operation? What are the odds of us winning?"

"The odds? That depends on the objective." Nikon had his mouth shut tight. "Each objective has their own chance of success."

Garen shrugged and stopped asking questions as it was a waste of time.

The fleet was slowly and firmly heading towards the Smoke Island. As the sky turned black, the surface of the ocean started to turn into dark blue and the sparkling reflections of the moon could be seen on the ocean’s surface.

After gathering on the deck, the five of them went back to their respective rooms and did not see each other again as they were preparing their minds for what was to come. The big battle was the next day and it could be a life or death situation if there was any slight negative impact on their state of mind.

The fleet took the opportunity to speed up during the night and soon, the highly dense white smoke of the Smoke Island could be seen with the naked eye.

Poof!!

The gas kept discharging from the Chimney.

Garen stood still in his room and could faintly see the highly dense white smoke of the Smoke Island through the ship’s window.

He could not see more than two meters ahead of the ocean’s surface with his naked eye.

Woo!!~~~

An ear piercing alarm suddenly rang.

"What’s going on?!" A man asked loudly as rushing footsteps could be constantly heard from the corridor.

"The ship had collided with something!"

Boom!!

An explosion was heard as the body of the ship started to vibrate.

Garen knew the situation was dire and quickly pack the necessities such as food and water and opened the door.

Boom Boom!!

Another two explosions and vibrations occurred as a strong burning smell filled the air.

Sailor after sailor zoomed past him towards the deck as he opened the door.

"What’s going on?!" Garen simply grabbed one and questioned him.

"Captain! The ship has collided with a mine! We are currently fixing it!" The sailor’s face was filled with black mechanical oil as he sweated profusely.

Garen let go of the sailor and shoved everyone out of his way as he made way to the deck.

As there were already fire on some part of the deck, the sailors were already trying to put it off with a fire hose.

Palosa was already on the deck whereas Andrela and the King of Nightmares just came out from behind him.

The four of them grouped together and as Garen was about to open his mouth, he saw a red flare flying to his direction.

His face changed and without thinking any further, he jumped out of the boat and into the water.

Boom!!!

The ship that ah spanned at least a hundred meters across exploded. The ship’s body broke into half from the middle like a paper boat torn into half and sank into the sea in a matter of seconds.

Boom boom boom boom!!!

The constant bombardment incessantly created fountains of displaced water from the sea. The white water spurted up high above and poured down drizzling noisily.

Garen was floating in the cold sea. As he swam for a few meters, he felt a numbing sensation at the top of his head, as if something had pierced onto his skin.

"Not good!" He kicked the water with all his might and jumped up to at least ten meters above the sea.

Kaboom!!

A huge amount of water spurted upwards from where he originally was in the water.

Bright red lights strobed from the black ships on the pitch black sea. They were either flashes of returning fire with their canons, or otherwise light from fires still burning on the deck.

The Federation’s fleet was ambushed by an unknown fleet.

At the other side of the sea in the distance, another fleet lit up a countless amount of red strobes; they had opened fire.

Garen swam quickly in the ocean as his shirt had been torn to pieces due to the shock. The suitcase in his hand was mushed as it had been hit by the shells.

He quickly swam towards a life buoy that had been thrown into the sea and hung himself by the life buoy with his shoulders.

The water splashed as he jumped out of the water from the life buoy and gently landed onto an undamaged ship.

"Return Fire!!" Nikon was roaring nearby. "Fucking return fire!! Kill all of them!! These fucking Weisman Bastards! Sooner or later I will cut you all up and feed you to the dogs!!"

Boom!!

Before he finished his sentence, this ship had taken damage.

A bright light flashed in front of Garen’s eyes and both his ears starting ringing loudly. It was as if there was an alarm clock ringing continuously beside his ears. In a blink of an eye, the fire in front of him had covered his whole vision.

A fire broke from the deck nearby him and exploded, releasing a torrent of flame similar to a red lotus.

The deck’s explosion ruthlessly tossed into the ocean again.

"F*ck!!" Garen quickly pointed his toes and ran on the surface of the ocean for at least ten meters before landing on debris left behind by a sunken ship.

He couldn’t hear anything and he could see a piece of bright red afterimage in his vision and he couldn’t see anything clearly at all. Garen knew that he was powerless as this was a battle between two fleets. He had no choice but to sit and wait for it to play out.

After some time, His eyes and ears started to recover. Garen rubbed his temples as he scanned his surrounding.

The whole ocean was disastrous as the Federation’s large fleet had completely disappeared as it had turned into millions of pieces of debris floating on the surface of the ocean.

A few lucky surviving sailors were holding onto the life buoys as they gathered at larger pieces of debris. However, only a few people could find their sense of direction due to the pitch black conditions during night time. To make things worse, there were waves that would topple over the debris and some would occasionally drown into the cold sea.

"Augustus!! I will kill you no matter what!!" The King of the Gun, Nikon’s roar could be heard from a distance.

Chirp!!!

Suddenly, a sharp chirp that sounded like a bird could be heard from the Smoke Island which was far away. It was as if it was a response towards Nikon’s anger. The chirp obviously sounded provocative and contemptuous.

"Everyone get to the island!!" Palosa’s voice suddenly popped out from the middle of the sea and everyone could hear it clearly.

Swoosh!!

Four streams of water rose together at the same time as four human figures jumped up and sprinted on the water and headed towards the Smoke Island.

As Garen was about to head out, he realized that his hand was rather light. The suitcase was no longer there. His shirt was ragged and the left side of his shirt was completely torn apart.

He quickly reached in his hand and fumbled.

"My Golden Sword Throne!!" His facial expression changed slightly. The Antique of Tragedy, which were Golden Sword Throne and the Golden Seal, were placed in this very pocket. He brought them anywhere so that he could absorb the potential at all times. He didn’t expect to lose them from the series of explosions.

"Garen!" Palosa’s voice came from the distance.

Although Garen was slightly unhappy about it, he still got up and stepped onto the surface of the sea and sprinted towards the Smoke Island.

The Smoke Island’s Southern Coast.

There were three figures in white fur overcoats looking at the five people that were sprinting towards the Smoke Island.

"It’s Flamingo. That damn clown. How dare he push the blame onto us when he’s the one who had sunk our ship!" The tall man with pointy hair said angrily.

"Let’s leave here immediately. Flamingo’s underling had assumed that we were the ones who did this. The Clown Queen had perfectly copied my Bombardment Technique." Another black figure said calmly.

"Isn’t that good? They can have a good match with Flamingo’s underling! They had just formed a team and now they wanted to be the very best? We definitely need to make them suffer more." The last man laughed.

"It’s time to leave." The man in charge turned around and walked into the island. The other man followed suit, leaving behind the last man who was yelling here and there and being ignored.

************

On the other side of the hidden rocky spot.

A team of clowns that were dressed up strangely were looking at the five figures sprinting towards the island.

These clowns were all wearing thick attire and hats and all of them looked the same on the outside. No one could differentiate who’s who as their body figures were hidden within the thick dress up as well.

"Hehe… Let’s move out." The clown who stood at the front said in such a way that it was impossible to differentiate whether they were a male or a female.

"Hehe…!" The remaining clowns started laughing strangely as well. Their voices were so similar to the first one it was impossible to make out the differences.

All of them brought out a long black rocket launcher from behind and set them up skillfully as they aimed at the five figures who were sprinting towards their directions.

Pew pew pew!!!

The rockets flew towards the five figures and left a trail of white smoke behind.

Chapter 214: Gathering 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom Boom Boom!!

The rockets exploded on the sea. The fireworks were extraordinarily beautiful during night time.

Garen flicked his toe and fired off a water arrow to hit the rocket launcher.

The explosion occurred just right in front of him and he had no choice but to defend himself with one of his hand until the debris stopped flying around.

"How are we going to tackle this?!" He looked at the others and realized that the King of Gun, Nikon had already taken out his small pistol and aimed at where the projectile came from.

Pew!

A red light flashed from the pistol as it produced a faint sound and was completely silent after.

At the same time, a sharp silver ball landed on one of the clowns who were on the hill. They immediately reached out their hands on attempted to grab the ball.

Pew!!

The small ball exploded into countless thin needles in every direction.

Silently, the whole group of clowns collapsed into the ground, pierced by the thin needles.

"Let’s go. Their grand performance is no match for my mere shot." Nikon blew the gun’s muzzle with a calm expression.

Two of them sprinted out as everything settled down.

After striding on the surface of the ocean for awhile, he finally reached the beach. Technically, he was stepping on the water instead of pedalling with his legs as he ejected himself away from the surface of the water by stepping on the water with enormous power.

He was not an expert in QingGong as he was already drenched from head to toe the moment he reached the beach. He looked very pathetic with his torn shirt drenched with cold water.

As he landed, he saw that Palosa, the King of Nightmares and the others were already waiting for him. It was obvious that he was the slowest on the water.

"You look pathetic!" The King of Nightmares said helplessly. "It’s such a pity for the new shirt that I just bought. I had taken a long time to pick out these shirts and it’s already ruined."

It wasn’t just him. Andrela and Nikon’s shirts were more or less the same. On the other hand, Palosa was the only one whose shirt was perfectly clean. He even had the two briefcases with him on his hand. He looked like an old tourist who was about to travel around.

"It’s the Three Major Generals from Weisman! They have already arrived!" Nikon gripped his teeth. "This time I will kill all of them myself!!"

"Do you want to move out on your own or join us in our venture?" Palosa asked coldly.

"I have other things to attend to, I won’t be going with you." Nikon shook his head. "We shall part ways here."

"Alright."

As Nikon finished his sentence, he sprinted back to the sea and started helping the soldiers to get onto land.

"Let’s go as well." Palosa turned around and went deeper into the island.

Garen didn’t say a word and followed Palosa behind. Four of them were completely silent throughout the whole journey as they explored the island.

The surface was completely deserted, filled with nothing but black rubble and stone. The smoke that kept coming out from between the stones had reduced visibility to only a few meters.

The four of them left the beach and went into the inner part of the island. It was just like a normal road, save for the mist.

The mists that surrounded them stretched across the horizon, and everything was covered in white.

Palosa found a big stone, squatted down and opened his suitcases to reveal some food and drinks.

"Let’s eat something. We’re probably going to be staying here for the night."

Andrela and the King of Nightmares sat down separately and took a fried biscuit and mixed it with milk.

Garen took a fried biscuit as well. He surveyed the surrounding environment as he nibbled on his snack..

The surroundings and the sky were completely white, whereas the surface was filled with black rubble. On top of this they could only see three meters ahead of them, as if the four were stranded on a deserted island out at sea.

He grabbed some pebbles off the ground and pinched them gently.

Crack.

The stones were squished into black powder and revealed a honeycomb shaped structure within the stones. The inside of the stones were very hot; about thirty of forty degree celsius.

"The landscape here is very strange and the geothermal temperature is unusually high. The smoke seems to contain some sulfur in them." He whispered.

"Although the Smoke Island has plenty of secrets, we won’t be in in danger as long as we don’t enter the ancient ruins. I heard that there were tourists who got lost in the mist and died falling off a cliff, even though the number of these cases were rare." Andrela explained. "We should be fine as long as we take extra care for the enemies on this island."

He took out a leather paper from his shirt and opened it slowly to reveal a map.

"This is the general layout of the Smoke Island mapped by the older generations. It’s not very useful but it can be used as a reference."

They gathered and examined the map carefully.

The map pictured a very long island and was separated into Southern Territories and Northern Territories. These two territories even had locations that were annotated with a small dot and names by the side.

"There are a few popular scenery spots that were marked from one to nine and all of them are different types of statue forests. Which one should we pick?" Andrela asked. "Tomorrow will be the full moon and we need to fulfill the two requirements if we want to enter the ancient ruins."

"The first requirement is to have a telekinesis expert, which is me." The King of Nightmares replied lazily."

"The second requirement is the key." Garen continued the conversation. "The question is, where is the key?"

"It’s most likely located at the statue forests. The Three Major General from Weisman who ambushed us just a while ago will most likely head there as well." The King of Nightmares said casually. "I will have them pay for destroying the brand new shirt that I had just bought."

Garen was unhappy as well as he lost the Golden Seal and Golden Sword Throne for no reason. These were Antiques of Tragedy that had valuable potential points embedded in them and they disappeared for good because of the enemy’s actions.

‘Hehe…"

A playful laughter emerged from the mist, not too far away from them.

"Who’s there!" Andrela sharpened his gaze as his hand started to glow silver in color.

WIth a clank a clown in a red and green shirt slowly emerged from the mist. He wore a red mask and his cheeks were ripped opened from the mouth to the ears, as if he had a very huge, bloody mouth. He approached closer as he threw the knife which he was holding away from his hand.

"It’s very fortunate to meet someone who had been ambushed by the same people." The clown spoke with a very hideous voice. "We were attacked by Weisman’s Three Major Generals as well. Our fleet has been destroyed and we are going to take revenge."

"Oh? Do you know where they are?" The King of NIghtmare took out a white pear out of thin air and gently bit into it.

"Of course. Those people are about to obtain the key. Their intel is too accurate." The clown’s obvious emphasis was strangely warped. The key was obviously the most crucial item to enter the ancient ruins but he seemed to be celebrating this disadvantageous moment. "What do you say? Do you want to go?"

"You have informed quite a few people, right?" Garen asked softly.

"Of course. How dare they attack people who want to board the island? The Weisman’s Government would think that they are unstoppable if no one teaches them a lesson." The clown replied with a sharp tone.

"How many people do you have?" Garen continued his questioning.

"Do you think I would answer that question of yours?" The clown laughed.

"That’s true. However, what makes you think that we will trust you?"

"Because you have to. Whoever wants to obtain the key would not miss this opportunity. They are in the North. Walk this way and I will be your guide." The clown smirked as he said. "We all have a common enemy. We will deal with the key after we deal with them."

He lead the way and walked in the direction he spoke of earlier.

Palosa was motionless and no one could make out what he’s thinking with that poker face of his.

The remaining two had a smile on their face and did not seem to be moving as well.

On the other hand, Garen squinted his eyes as if he smelled something fishy going on. He started walking in the other direction the clown was leading.

"You’re going in the wrong directions." The clown turned his head around and looked at him. "Follow me. It’s over there."

"Should I ask you where I should go?" Garen furrowed his eyebrows and continue walking forward.

Shoosh!

The clown rushed back and stood in front of Garen to block his path.

"You can’t walk over here. You should follow me instead…"

"What do you mean?" Garen started to become serious. "You better move out of my way."

"Little fella… This road must not be taken… Or else… I will be very angry~~~" The clown in the mask started to laugh strangely.

"Are you going to move away?" Garen started to smell something faint from this directions and his tone immediately went cold.

"If you want to be killed by me, I’m fine with that." The clown’s tone started to change as well.

"To die by your hand? Hehe, let me see how do you plan to kill me!!" Garen said furiously and attempted to capture the enemy with his expanded hand.

Boom!!

An invisible aura started to shroud the clown like a greenish black iron claw latching onto his face. The invisible wind pushed the surrounding white mists as it moved towards the sides like a wave.

Hngh!!

The clown screamed in a high pitch. As he attempted to avoid being caught via moving quickly in a strange manner, his sleeves were loosened and revealed a lot of black hand grenades in them.

Kaboom!

Both of them retreated and the fiery explosion exploded in between them as the bright explosion pushed away from the surrounding white mists.

"Divine Statue - East King Hand!!"

Garen’s gaze sharpened, became a black figure and instantly rushed out to capture the clown with both of his hands. High pitched noises were screeched from the air as his palms brushed across the air.

A transparent wall was formed in front of him. The wall was created by multiple layers of air vortices and it headed towards the clown like a giant boulder.

The clown screamed as he turned away, attempting to escape.

Splat!!

The clown’s body was separated into half and his blood rained down on the surrounding.

Garen’s hand was still 2 meters away from his body.

"Couldn’t even last one attack." He sighed as he walked slowly towards the clown’s head and stepped onto the useless clown’s brain.

As he flicked his leg, a silver card flew into his hand.

The card was made of metal and it had a picture of black and white ghost printed onto it.

"It’s the clown’s card." The King of the Nightmare approached him slowly with a hand covering his nose. "The Clown King had ten underlings with different personalities and each of them has as a different nickname. You must be one of them. I heard the clowns’ body were either filled with poison or traps and they’re all proficient in poisoning others. It’s unfortunate that you’d been torn into 2 pieces before we can see your skill."

He looked at Garen.

"Killing people with airflow through space. Have you reached that realm, Garen?"

Chapter 215: Southern Territory 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen passed the card to King of Nightmares and did not answer his question. "Let’s go. It looks like there’s something over here." He walked towards the direction that he had determined earlier.

The King of Nightmares and Andrela looked at Palosa.

The latter shook his head and said: "We needn’t make this unnecessarily complicated."

"I think it’s best for you to follow along. That might turn out to be necessary." Garen turned his head around and said.

Palosa closed his eyes and stayed silent.

"Hmph." Garen didn’t want to speak further either and proceeded to walk into the mist.

Andrela and the King of Nightmare were speechless as they looked at the both of them. They ultimately followed Garen.

"Although we’ve already expected to have different opinions and be separated because of it, I didn’t think it would be so soon," Andrela said helplessly. "However, everyone has their own objective, opinions, and style of operation. Since Palosa and Garen both stand at the pinnacle of the martial arts world, it is normal to have a different modus operandi."

"I don’t really care." The King of Nightmares said as he hung onto Andrela’s shoulder lazily as he leaned against him. "It’s very boring lately… Drela, I have a suggestion."

"Forget about it." Andrela suddenly stopped.

"Drela, how about we have a wild war when everyone gathers at the middle of the island? Didn’t you want to be famous? If we do that you’ll be famous internationally~" The King of Nightmare suggested lazily. "I don’t care how you want to do it~~"

"Of course you don’t care…" Andrela was speechless. "You can just morph into another person. What about me?!" He knew that the King of Nightmares would do it if he wanted to. It’s completely normal of the King of Nightmares to knock Andrela unconscious and act in his place during the war if he got excited.

"Furthermore, I don’t want to be famous, I just want to… sigh, nevermind. I just can’t get through you!"

The trio walked into the thick mist and soon disappeared.

Palosa was still sitting in the same spot with his eyes closed.

************

Garen kept walked towards where the smell was coming from in the mist and soon arrived the place where there were blood stains on the rocks. The blood was dark red, betraying the fact that it had been shed some time ago.

He kept walking on and suddenly heard a faint sizzling noise in front of him. It sounded like someone was boiling oil or some sort.

Soon, a bonfire appeared in front of Garen. Within the fire were a pile of corpses, green and red. Black dense smoke kept oozing from the still burning flame.

Garen stood in front of the bonfire and examined the corpses.

"They’re the clowns."

The King of Nightmares walked forward, looked and said, "They died pierced by steel needles. It’s very similar to Nikon’s technique."

"Looks like the clowns were most likely the ones who ambushed us when we were in the sea." Garen squinted his eyes and whispered. "Perhaps they were trying to push the blame\onto the Weisman?"

"Let’s forget this and go to where the key is. We have to go to the statue forests, be it to open the ancient ruins tomorrow or battling for the keys. We should go there further and see who’s in the Southern Territory."

"The Southern Territory and Northern Territory have their own respective keys?"

"Of course," Andrela answered. "One on each side. Hence there are only four people qualified to battle for the Black Smoke Pot."

"I recall from the map that we need to pass by two important places right?" With Garen’s memory being photographic, he had already memorized the map he had seen earlier. "They were the gap between the canyon and the edge of the cliffs. These two locations seem to the best spot for an ambush."

"A map is a map. Do you have any idea how to differentiate the locations within this mist?" The King of Nightmares frowned.

"How did they differentiate the directions here?" Garen squatted down and examined the clown’s corpse that was in the bonfire.

The King of Nightmares squatted down and looked at the surface’s striations.

"We should just follow the usual method. This surface has a consistent striations. We should be fine as long as we follow the direction that these are going. We should be good if we can find a living person."

"We will just have to deal with it." Garen frowned. "Let’s go there as soon as possible. We will interrogate him or her if we find someone."

He looked at the surface’s striation and walked along it. The remaining two followed tightly from behind.

The rocks in front of them were getting higher and higher. Some of them even had a deep gorge in between and they had no choice but to jump across the gap. The mist between the gaps were getting more and more dense as soon they could not see more than 2 meters ahead of them. The trio could only communicate via smell and hearing to prevent getting lost.

Soon a pile of corpses appeared on the floor. They were soldiers in white clothes without any emblems or indication of nationality. They examined the corpses and couldn’t identify any traits from it.

They kept moving forward. Explosions could occasionally be heard from far away, along with faint roars and the occasional gun shot.

The mist had perfectly enveloped the whole area.

"Has the battle to obtain the key started?" Garen looked at the directions where the explosions occurred.

"The key has been out for some time. We just don’t know who’s holding it. I heard that the keys were brought in from the outside, and the Southern Territory and Northern Territory have two keys each for two entrances to their ancient ruins. However, the ancient ruins are small and hard to find, and no one knows which the Black Smoke Pot is in." Andrela explained.

Garen stopped the conversation and kept marching forward as they moved past the pile of corpses.

*************

Among the white mist, a group of human figures in clown attire quietly gathered beside the clown’s corpse. The corpses were torn into pieces and blood was spilled everywhere. It was a sight of horror.

The lighted torches in their hands faintly reflected the masks on their face.

"White ghost was dead right after he sent us the intel." The clown leader’s voice trembled as he spoke, in a weird tone.

"We have underestimated Flamingo."

"We will give up on attacking them and change our target. The deal between us and the Immortal Palace is to reduce the amount of participants that were not qualified to enter the ruins. Since they are qualified to enter, we shall ignore them." The clown leader whispered.

"My queen, do you have any confidence to retreat without harm?" He suddenly turned his head to the right and asked the clown.

"I’m not sure."

"Does that mean you’re not confident?" The clown leader paused for a while. "Nevermind. Let’s go ahead. All of you separate out and explore the other roads."

"Yes."

All the clowns moved out, and the clown leader was left alone.

He walked slowly to the corpse, squatted down and pinched the corpse’s skin.

"What powerful strength… A very cruel technique…" His playful gaze started to become more and more serious.

****************

Boom!

Garen slammed his palms onto a man in black’s waist, and the opponent flew away like a canon and crashed onto a rock not far away. The sound of multiple bones breaking could be heard and the man died instantly. It was unknown how many bones were broken.

He stood still and scanned his surrounding.

There were a lot of corpses in black shirts on the ground, and all of them had a picture of a white clown on their bodies.

Andrela and the King of Nightmares came from different directions.

Andrela cleaned his blood-stained sword

"These people are the clowns. What use do they have stationing here? To die without a purpose?"

"Perhaps they are trying to obtain the right to participate." The King of Nightmares yawned." This is meaningless. They are slightly stronger commoners die with the slightest attack. This is not fun at all."

The trio were standing in a narrow gap. There was a tunnel carved in the mountains face in front of them that was only wide enough to allow one person to pass through at a time. The tunnels seemed to be endless, shrouded by mist.

"Shall we go?" The King of Nightmares asked casually.

"Of course." Garen took a big step and entered the tunnel. Suddenly, his facial expression changed and immediately retreated.

Kaboom!!!

A loud deafening sound rang from within the tunnel.

The rage of fire accompanied rubble crashing came down from above and threatened to crush.

Clank clank clank clank!!!

Andrela appeared in front of Garen/ The sword on his hand instantly transformed into a mirror and turned all of the rubbles into pebbles. Even the fire was stopped in its track.

The trio was forced back by the explosion for ten meters or so. The floor clearly had a few scorch marks from the friction created when they were pushed back.

From above, there was a red mushroom like cloud slowly ascending in the area. Strong winds were gusting and blew away the mist in the surrounding to reveal a big land of deserted place filled with black rocks.

"Clown King!" Garen was very angry. He had been stomaching his anger from losing his Golden Sword Throne and Golden Seal earlier. Now he had been attacked by the clowns again and was almost caught in the explosion hidden in the tunnel.

He could have been injured by the explosion if he hadn’t realized that the place seemed strange as if someone had set a trap in it.

Although he was not afraid of bullets, it didn’t mean he wasn’t afraid of being caught by a big amount of explosives.

The King of Nightmares and Andrela were unhappy with it as well and no longer have a relaxed expression.

"Let’s go!" Garen pushed away a stone that was flying towards him and continued walking. He started feeling impatient as he was continuously attacked and had to react constantly.

"My make up!!" The King of Nightmares started crying and started to bring out his comb and mirror to attempt to fix his make up. As he reached into his pocket, he realized that his combs and mirror had been utterly destroyed, "Damn you clown king! Don’t let me meet you!!"

On the other hand, Andrela was quietly patting away the dust was on his body.

The trio formed a line and sped up as they followed the surface’s striations and travelled to the first location.

************

At the center of the Southern Territories laid a strange place where mist was absent.

There were black statues arranged here. They were either standing, sitting down, or posing in weird postures. They were arranged in such a manner that it formed a dense forest of statues.

At the center of the statue forest was an empty space of land that was surrounded by the forest of statues.

A group of men in black coats were treading with care on this empty land. They stayed close to the stone statues and kept walking and jumping into inconvenient paths and were extremely wary of empty space.

"This is the place guys. Be extra careful. Dale, are you alright?" The golden haired woman who was leading the expedition turned her head around and looked at him with a worried look.

"I’m alright. Let’s keep moving. Stop treating me like a fragile flower that’s placed in the living room." The middle aged man who was at the very back replied. He was holding a black pipe in his mouth and occasionally took a puff.

"Oh right. What’s the situation on the items that we found? Has the result been released?" He looked at a fat bearded man who was just beside him.

Chapter 216: Southern Territory 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"No. I have never seen these items before. It looks like something from Ancient Endor, but I couldn’t match it with anything from that time period." The big bearded man said helplessly.

"White Eagle, do you feel better?" Dale Quicksilver turned her head around and looked at the last person in the team. He was no other than the closest partner and assistant, White Eagle.

At this point in time White Eagle had seemed like a drunk person. His face was pale, his eye sockets deep and his usual bright golden hair was unreflective. The only thing that remained positive was his sharp gaze.

He raised his head and looked at his old friend Dale Quicksilver. "I’m still alright." His voice was unbelievably coarse. "It’s just that I may have spent too much energy. The few men in black previously were rather troublesome."

Dale Quicksilver nodded her head and didn’t say anything further.

The group kept walking forward and soon the detective pulled out a small metal piece out of the human stone statue and passed it to the big bearded fat man.

"Have a look at this."

"The big bearded fat man took it and examined it in detail for a long time. Ultimately he shook his head helplessly.

"I’m sorry… This is way beyond my knowledge."

Lady Si Lan looked at the big bearded fat man helplessly. He was an identification expert that they specially hired. However, the items they encountered along the road was unknown to him and only a small portion of items that he identified were vaguely described.

Whenever they encountered something the first thing he would do was apologize.

If this kept on, no one would know when they would be able to find the opponent’s trail. One must realize that these stone pieces were clues left by the people who kidnapped the two children.

These clues were purposely left behind. If we couldn’t find the remaining clues, I’m afraid Silvica and Eve…

"If only Sir Kelly was here. There’s too little research going on in the Ancient Endor’s culture." She sighed.

"Yes. If only Kelly was here…" Dale Quicksilver stopped her sentence midway as she lowered her voice.

This trip to the island was actually baited by a mysterious man. Detective Dale’s daughter Eve and White Eagle’s son Silvica were kidnapped by a mysterious man. If they wanted to save them, they had to go on the island.

The enemy obviously had an unspeakable motive so they had no choice but to follow his demands.

In addition, the clues that would guide them forward were those black small rocks that were placed there beforehand.

"They purposely come up with a riddle for us to guess." Dale Quicksilver stopped walking with a calm expression. "This may be a game, a game where we don’t have any choice. The opponent’s strength far surpasses ours, so they get to set the rules. We have no choice but to follow them. Do not panic. If we do, we won’t have any chance to win anymore."

"But Eve and Silvica…"

"Relax. The kids will eventually go through some rough training as well." Dale smiled as she tried her best to not sound worried.

"Don’t worry Dale. I have a sword here so we still have the ability to protect ourselves." White Eagle comforted.

"That’s true…" Dale nodded.

"Let’s rest for a bit." The detective sat on a stone statue’s leg.

Everyone started sitting down without paying much attention to their surroundings.

"NIneteen years ago, my parents were burnt to death on this island…" The White eagle sat down as he took out a small exquisite copper necklace out of his shirt.

The pendant had the same style as a pocket watch. He opened the pendant to reveal a black and white picture.

"This is my father." he gentle stroked the surface of the glass that was protecting the picture. "Never in my dreams would I think of a time I would be stepping on this island again…" He had a complicated expression on his face as he grabbed the white sword tightly in his hand.

Pew pew!!

Suddenly, two ear deafening gunshots rang from afar.

"Let’s move!"

The team quickly got up and moved towards the source of the gunshots.

They passed through the stone statues and soon arrived at another empty field that was multitudes larger than the previous one.

There were already a few teams standing in the empty field. Each of them stood at the corners. There were a pile of corpses in black shirts, obviously the receiver of the gunshots that had pierced the air earlier.

Dale looked closely and saw that there were a total of three teams on the empty field, and they stood tall and clear.

Two of the three teams were confronting each other and the atmosphere was getting tense by the second.

There were two teams on the left comprised of werewolves, whereas there were three tall men with white coats standing on the right.

The werewolves looked unhappy as they stared at the three men in front of them. Although the werewolves outnumbered them, they were obviously holding caution.

"The leader of the werewolf clan sir Bedega secretly came to the island. Looks like you have brought quite a number of clan members as well? Are you guys trying to get your hands on the Black Smoke Pot?" One of the strong and tall men covering himself with a white shirt laughed. His black chest here was moving about with the wind and it looked strangely funny.

"The Weisman’s Major Generals had also secretly come to the island? If you can come here, why can’t we?" The black werewolf who seemed to be the leader replied with a cold shoulder. "Furthermore, even the clown king from the poker organization has come here himself. The grand occasion this time is much more stronger than the last time. Do you want us to give you a hand?"

"Capturing the clown king is the Weisman’s Major Generals’ mission, so you don’t need to concern yourself with it." The leader of the Three Major Generals said calmly. "We will also take this opportunity to kill that traitor Ghette.

"I don’t think you can fully understand the overall situation even if you, The Glorious Chancer are the one who’s going to face it, right?" The leader of the werewolf clan said. "The clown king and the Immortal Palace have formed an alliance, and he is now considered as one of the Immortal Palace. It won’t be easy for you guys to deal with him."

"Is that right?" The Glorious Chancer’s face slightly twitched and didn’t say another word anymore as if he was in deep thought.

Dale Quicksilver and her team had entered the area without drawing anyone’s attention. These people were obviously the calefares on the island so it wasn’t worth people taking precaution against them.

This meant that those experts who were very cautious would measure their strengths. They would simply ignore them if they were no threat to them.

Soon after their arrival, more and more people started to gradually gather here.

This was the entrance of the ancient ruins in the Southern Territory. To open the ancient ruin entrance, one must slot in the key into one of the stone statues. Even if you had obtained the key, you had to come to this place if you wanted to enter the ancient ruin.

Waves of powerful figures started to enter the empty field. There were elites from the Federation, special forces from the Tulip and a few unknown groups with unknown backgrounds. What was strange was that these people were injured and came in small numbers. Furthermore, they didn’t seem to be in good shape as well.

"Looks like they have been ambushed as well." Dale Quicksilver whispered to Si Lan and White Eagle. "The Weisman’s Three Major Generals and the leader of the werewolf clan are currently on the field. The clown king shouldn’t have the guts to appear. Even if he is one of the Immortal Palace, he won’t come out without any forces. Although the situation looks very tense, this is the safest place to be at the moment."

"The Weisman’s Three Major Generals have been open towards their actions. As the strongest team in the field, they should be able to control the situation." Si Lan nodded in agreement. "White Eagle, are you still able to hold up?"

"I’m fine…" White Eagle’s veins started to become visible on his face, as he held the white sword tightly in his hand. There were black runes flashing faintly on the sword’s body. "I still can resist it…" He grit his teeth as he whispered.

The three of them looked at White Eagle.with concern as he might not be able to suppress his negative emotions.

This sword is the legendary Rune Blade that had a mysteriously terrifying power. They wouldn’t have been able to arrive on this island without this sword. However, enough strength and will is required to be able to hold the Rune Blade.

White Eagle made up his lack of strength with his unfaltering will. If not for this, he would have not been able to sustain it at all.

"So we will just camp here? Until tomorrow?" The fat Identification Expert whispered.

"There’s no need for that. The key should be here by now, with the Three Major Generals or the leader of the werewolf clan. From now on until the next full moon, everything depends on the participants’ skills. However, to be able to obtain the key from the Three Major Generals and the leader of the werewolf clan…" Dale Quicksilver shook his head. "When they appear here in the flesh, they are also sending a message to the clown king that if he wants to the key, they are right over here. You’ll have to come and get it yourself if you’re brave enough!" She paused for a while. "At the same time it’s also an announcement to the others. The key is with them, and as long as if you’re not afraid of death, you’re free to try and get it from us!"

"That’s crazy!" Lady Si Lan gasped. "This place is filled with elites from all over the world. Even the special forces from Tulip have arrived."

"This is the behavior of the Weisman. They are able to behaved so because they are trying to take over the world." Dale Quicksilver nodded. "Now we just have to see if there’s anyone brave enough to attack. We don’t know who was the one who kidnapped Eve and Silvica so everyone please observe carefully."

At this moment, a group of men and women with red shawls over their heads quickly entered the district. A woman with red eyes, who seemed to be the leader, glanced around and finally set her attention onto the Weisman’s Three Major Generals.

"The Glorious Chancer, it’s good to see you again." The girl placed her right fist on her chest and greeted him with a bow.

"Elysha, are you here for there key as well?" The Glorious Chancer asked calmly. His had a small black moustache just above his lips which gave him a rather stern look.

"The real battle starts after the entrance of the ancient ruin is opened. It’s too early to say that yet." The red eyed girl replied.

"That depends. Only those who have the key on their hand has the right to use the Black Smoke Pot. Even if you’re the first to arrive to the Black Smoke Pot, you will not be able to use it." The leader of the werewolf clan butted in. "Elysha, has the Demon Hunters Alliance decided to participate in this fight?"

"You should consider yourself lucky to be in the White Lion Camp. I will kill you without any hesitation if you were from the Black Lion Camp." The lady said with a calm tone.

"You can always try." The werewolf leader couldn’t help but to laugh.

The situation had gotten more and more intertwined. The Demon Hunters Alliance, Werewolf Clan, Weisman’s Government and the clown king were four power houses and obviously the current major players. Each of them has the strength to annihilate all of the others present.

Some had decided to retreat after witnessing such a dire situation.

Chapter 217: Southern Territory 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

[Trigger Warning: This chapter may include minimal sexually abusive narration. Please exercise caution when reading or skip the chapter.]

Carefully, Dale Quicksilver and the others retreated from the immediate area to avoid being noticed.

From afar, leaders from the Three Major Generals, the Werewolves, and the Demon Hunters negotiated for a while, all becoming increasingly tense as time goes by.

The Werewolves and the Demon Hunters drew their weapons facing each other.

Phewwweee!

With the sound of a whistle, all the werewolves charged at the Demon Hunters in a fan-shaped formation.

Bullets wheezing, growls, howls, and other sounds mixed into one another, forming an orchestra of bloodshed and severed limbs as the Demon Hunters and the Werewolves fought.

The Werewolves were ferocious and brutal. In their fury, they can enlarge themselves by more than half of their original size. Coupled with their accelerated healing factor and their astonishing defense, killing them would prove to be difficult unless their heads were lopped off.

On the other hand, the Demon Hunters were aggressive as well. Their weapons were so sharp they were able to slice the limbs off of werewolves easily. Even though they lack power, they made up with their immense experience, establishing them to be well matched with the Werewolves.

One after another, the other parties retreated. Unlike the usual tactics the Demon Hunters used, this team was able to fight the Werewolves one-on-one, demonstrating their elite status among the usual teams.

The red-eyed lady brandished her metallic arm and faced off against the leader of the Werewolf pack. Her red cape darted around him like scarlet fire surrounding him.

Arooooo!

The leader howled wildly.

"Enough, Bedega!" Among the Three Major Generals, a tall, lean man beside the Glorious Chancer yelled. "There were other elites on this island, do you want all of us to die?"

Unfortunately, it was a little too late.

With the leader’s howl, the eyes of all the werewolves flashed red, increasing their speed remarkably.

"Slay them!" The Demon Hunters yelled, procuring a syringe each and injecting a pale red liquid.

The situation soon descended into disarray.

Due to the conflict between the main forces, the Three Major Generals were not able to control the situation, considering their lack of manpower. Some other forces who were nemeses started attacking each other as well.

Dale Quicksilver and his team kept retreating when suddenly a flying machete cut through the air and flew toward them.

"Dodge!"

White Eagle swung his blade at it.

Clank!

The machete split into two parts and fell into the ground near the human statue behind them. At the same time, the main fight had shifted closer, forcing the group into two sides, Si Lan and the appraisal expert were on one side, Dale Quicksilver and White Eagle on another.

In the turmoil, Dale Quicksilver kept trying to follow Si Lan with his gaze, but there were seven or eight people fighting between them. As he turned his gaze upward, a bullet hit a stone statue on top of him.

He could only hear weapons clashing, screaming, robes flipping, and the wind swooshing. Other than that, nothing.

After White Eagle parried several other machetes, he was immediately treated as the enemy and was pulled into the fight. He tried his best to defend Dale Quicksilver while worriedly glanced at Si Lan and the appraisal expert.

"What now!"

"We need to get closer! Otherwise, Si Lan will be in trouble!" Dale Quicksilver clenched his jaw.

Unwittingly, they were forced farther and farther from their original spot, to the point that they have lost sight of the other two.

Dale Quicksilver tried to calm down.

"Need to find a way! I… must!" He stood behind White Eagle with his back against a stone statue, squinting.

The difference between their strength is too huge. Anyone from this bunch of people would be considered elites of the world, even though they look like they were struggling, every one of them could watch out for their own. At most they’ll be injured, not dead.

"Something weird!" Dale Quicksilver realized something. Even though the people seem brutal, the movements they employ were mysterious, separating the group as well as blocking them from meeting up.

"They’re doing it on purpose!" He realized with a start. " White Eagle! Charge!" He roared.

"Follow me!"

White Eagle rippled his sword.

Zing!

Black runes lit up from the rune blade, vibrating as if they were made of ink.

It sounded like an uncountable amount of people chanting together.

The blade was soon illuminating with black radiance. Three other rune blade shadows appeared out of thin air, circling White Eagle and Dale with increasing momentum, like a fan at its maximum speed.

Two sparring ‘opponents’ didn’t react in time and got slashed by the spinning blades, stumbling back awkwardly.

"Where are you going?"

A strange piercing voice came from straight ahead.

A levitating red figure came into sight, colliding with White Eagle forcefully.

Poof!

The shadows vanished as White Eagle grunted and retaliated with the red figure.

"You again!" He groaned and tried to disengage to no avail.

It was then that Dale Quicksilver realized the red figure was the weird clown who intercepted them before.

"The red clown!"

The clown had two bright red daggers on his hands and stabbed at White Eagle furiously, but his face was wearing the eerily calm grin the whole time, as if this was all an intricate dance routine he was used to*.

"Spiralling Smog."

He shrieked as green haze burst out of his body, covering a huge area centering him.

White Eagle and Dale Quicksilver were immediately enclosed by the haze, choking them both.

"We need to meet up with Si Lan!" Dale Quicksilver screamed at White Eagle.

"No! He’s still here!" White Eagle paused to regain his equilibrium, but a red silhouette dashed on his left, leaving a burning wound on his arm.

Psst!

Dale Quicksilver was cut on his back as well.

"What can we do? Dammit!" White Eagle tried to suppress the anger in him. The situation is getting worse and more dangerous than ever. If even they were so badly hurt, then where Si Lan is… unimaginable!

　　**************

"Gah!"

Si Lan yelped and stumbled backward, clutching her chest. Her black outershirt was sliced open, revealing the white corset she was wearing underneath.

The opponent’s attacks were so unnaturally accurate, it was obvious that it was planned.

Right now, she’s trying to hide next to Yoke the appraisal expert in the crevice between two statues at the same time the clown in red costume was closing in on her.

"Yoke, I’ll hold him off, run when you can!" Si Lan whispered as calmly as she could. Her usual politeness and seriousness was slightly shaky, as she herself had worried written in her eyes.

"What about you?" Yoke wasn’t so sure about the plan. "I can’t leave you here!"

"Just go, I have my own way to escape." Si Lan pretended to be confident in her plan, but she knew, it would be over for her.

Since working with her most admired Detective Dale Quicksilver, this was the first time she was in such a pinch.

The enemy in front of her wasn’t just a normal criminal. He was from the top assassin syndicate in the world, the Joker Squad of Poker Organization.

What she couldn’t believe was the clown in front of her slowly took off his mask, and revealed a badly scarred face of a woman.

"Si Lan Reybier, it’s been so long, you’re grown up to be such a pretty girl…" The woman’s voice was dangerous and shrieky, "It’s been what, twelve years since Dale Quicksilver and White Eagle forced me into desperation by the Nile River…"

Si Lan felt her throat went dry.

"You! You’re Kassidan!" How could she forget? Twelve years ago, when she was just a little girl, she was kidnapped. A huge amount of money were asked. The proprietor of the incident? Scarlet Spider Kassidan.

If it weren’t for Dale Quicksilver and White Eagle who passed by and saved her, her weed on her grave would’ve been as tall as an adult.

"You’re still alive!" Biting her lip, Si Lan spat out, "And you even joined the Poker as the Joker!"

"Because of you… I didn’t die, I’m stronger than ever…" Kassidan’s eyes were wild, "Do you know why I split you guys up?"

She chuckled and clapped her hands twice.

Soon, a dozen strong men waddled in from the hazy surrounding, all of them wearing the Joker mask.

"Unexpected, after chasing Dale Quicksilver’s tail for so many years, you’re still a virgin? What a shame… dying from this brutality at such a young age. You haven’t turned 25, have you? So young… tsk tsk tsk…"

The Scarlet Spider giggled, which soon turned into a nefarious shriek. Her right hand flicked, and a flying knife sliced a large hole into Si Lan’s shirt at her waist.

Another flick, the flying knife returned to her hand. Another, the knife darted between Si Lan’s legs and nailed itself on the stone statue behind her. Her fair thigh was exposed at the cut on her pants.

"Agh!" Si Lan staggered backward, her back pressing against the statue.

"Such smooth skin… Ah! Ah!" Scarlet Spider started moaning, reveling in her torture. "Now! Deflower her to death! Don’t leave any holes undefiled!"

Hurr hurr…

The dozen of men approached Si Lan, rubbing their palms together and surrounding her.

"Si Lan, run!" The appraisal expert, Yoke barged into the circle, blocking in front of Si Lan.

Thud.

He was sent flying and fainted after having rolled on the ground.

"Yoke!" Si Lan’s face was white as ash.

　　*************

Garen, King of Nightmare and Andrela marched up to the central area of the fog and looked darkly into it.

"Blow it away!" Garen ordered.

"I’ll do it!" Andrela stepped forward and brandished his sword.

Shwoop!

Three silver mirrors appeared in front of him. Wind started blasting away at the green haze, unveiling the scene inside the chaotic area.

"Listen up!" King of Nightmare projected his voice. "Give us the Jokers in ten seconds!" His voice boomed at everyone who were inside the green mist.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. Alternately “as if this was all a game to him”. Choose your preference between literal/poetic translation.

Chapter 218: Southern Territory 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Or else…"

He gestured with his right arm, causing an invisible force to shoot out, slightly bending the space around it. Rocks and boulders levitated and flew about in circles screeching, forming a Telekinetic Tornado about three meters tall and four meters in diameter.

"It’s Telekinesis! Please stop!" A deep voice echoed from the central area. "We are the Major Generals from Weisman, the Clown King you were looking for is not here!"

"Why do we even bother talking to these savages! Let’s show them who’s boss!" A deep female voice came from in there somewhere.

Shrk!

With a glint of red light, a boomerang sliced through the air toward the three newcomers, aiming at Andrela.

The edge of the boomerang had a glaze of toxic blue. In the air, it looked like a red-colored moon, as dangerous as it is beautiful, the air around it became a gust of strong wind.

Andrela parried it with his sword easily.

The boomerang was destroyed instantly, its pieces splintered everywhere. Andrela’s movements were relaxed, as if he was just brandishing it for fun.

After his intense training to better himself, he finally reached a level where he can safely say he’s one of the top fighters in the world. Even though he still has ways to go before he could compete with the best few, he could already hold himself against these fighters.

In terms of ranking, he’s probably one of the top 30.

It was only because King of Nightmares, Garen, Palosa who were all monsters in a race to the top that he looked weak. In comparison, if he decides to join any other organizations, he would be considered their best fighter.

King of Nightmares beside him didn’t think too much. His face was dark with fury as he pointed toward where the boomerang came from. "Hmph!"

Fwoosh!

A huge Telekinetic Tornado shot out.

As the green mist had yet to fully disperse, the Tornado quickly disappeared behind it.

A deafening silence, and a sudden detonation.

Boom! Woo woo woo!

A piercing sound of the explosion accompanied by a tempestuous blast spread out from the center of the explosion.

The ground shook, even the stone statues visibly trembled.

Sounds of screaming and shrieking echoed from inside, obviously hit by the attack.

"Let’s go in!" Garen marched into the stony maze.

King of Nightmares and Andrela followed closely.

　　****************

Boom!

The Scarlet Spider and the other clowns stopped in front of Si Lan. Everyone looked unsettled.

"What do we do now, boss?" One of them asked in a hushed tone.

"They are specifically looking for us, and they still made such a huge fuss, they must not be some normal goons! Now that the Clown King wasn’t here, we won’t be able to stop them! Abort! Abort now!" Scarlet Spider quickly muttered.

"Bring this harpy along!" She looked at Si Lan, who was laid down, unmoving, on the ground.

Two of the clowns approached her to grab her.

Thud!

Si Lan flipped, kicking the two in their lower abdomen region. They yelped and staggered backward.

"You b*tch!" They tried to grab her again.

Woo woo woo!

A sudden blast of wind hit them.

The violent gale brought bullet-like stones and debris, piercing them in their backs. Ironically, Si Lan and Yoke were spared due to being in the shade of their pursuers.

Most of them were down. At least four of them had blood oozing out of all the seven openings of their heads, they were as good as dead.

The green haze finally cleared up due to that gust of wind.

"Kill her!" Kassidan shrieked.

Thud!

Before she could do anything else, a foot appeared on her abdomen and had her sent flying to a stone statue not far away.

A tall and strong silhouette slowly walked beside the Scarlet Spider and stamped his foot on her torso.

The silhouette was of a hulking man, his wore an earring on his left ear, his short purplish black hair moving with the wind. His eyes were red as he looked down at the people.

"Tell me, where is the Clown King?" His leather boots lightly treaded on Scarlet Spider’s head, only putting minimal pressure on it.

"This voice!" Si Lan suddenly felt goosebumps running down her spine, and it shocked her out of her spacey state. She stared at the man.

"You! You’re Mr. Kelly!" She yelled out of surprise.

The man took a double take and slightly turned his head toward Si Lan.

"Miss Si Lan?"

Stunned, Garen stared at Si Lan and her torn outfit. Mr. Kelly, that name reminded him of the time with Dale Quicksilver when he pretended to be an appraisal expert.

"What is it Garen?" A tall, handsome man appeared beside Garen, and frowned as he cast his gaze on Si Lan.

"It’s nothing, I know her." Garen replied calmly.

"No use trying to run!" King of Nightmares shrieked in the distance. "Get rekt Clown King! I'll let everyone have a go at you for a hundred times each! I'll make you go through it until you begged to die!"

Garen and Andrela’s mouths twitched.

"His hobby is still… weird."

"You’ll get used to it… Let’s go see what’s happening." Andrela turned and headed off toward the source of the voice.

Garen turned.

"Miss Si Lan, care to follow?"

"O… Of course!" Si Lan stood up in a hurry, but still instinctively pressed her legs together as her thighs showed slightly where it was sliced off.

Garen smiled and approached her and Yoke. Carrying them one on each side, he followed after Andrela speedily.

As Garen dashed through the field, Si Lan’s eyes were shut tight due to the wind, she asked loudly.

"Mr. Kelly, why have you come to this island?"

"I have some things to do here. I’m looking for something." Garen answered casually. "What about you? Dale Quicksilver is here too, isn’t he?"

"Y-yes. We lost touch a little while ago." Si Lan clenched her teeth. "Was the one chasing after the Clown King your teammate?"

"I don’t know him." Garen denied without hesitation. If he admitted to knowing King of Nightmares, that’d be embarrassing.

As they spoke, they have arrived at the central area where the smog had completely cleared up.

There were bodies lying haphazardly on the ground, three people were attacking a lady on a small clearing in the center.

The lady wore sharp golden claws on both her hands. Wherever she scratched at, the person in that direction would evade as soon as possible.

It was then that Si Lan noticed, among the ones attacking the girl, there were one of the Three Major Generals of Weisman, the red-eyed woman leading Demon Hunter, and a strange figure with the clown costume.

"Hmph!" Andrela huffed. "Night, you need help?"

"Nope!" The lady with sharp claws giggled, and scratched furiously, leaving lasting marks in the air. As the three stepped back, she twirled around.

"Got ‘em!"

The golden marks left in the air slowly dissipated according to a mysterious pattern, but everyone who watched this scene fell into a trance, feeling drowsy, as if their mind is filled to the brim. Suddenly alert, most of them turned away.

The three attacking King of Nightmares pulled back in aghast, but right then, the clown stumbled and fell backward.

"Run!" Smoke screen burst out of the other two as they transformed back into two clowns. They ran in two different directions.

King of Nightmares grabbed the clown who fell.

"Queen!"

The other two clowns screamed worriedly.

At the same time, the smog cleared up, the Three Major Generals of Weisman had already landed their killing strike and congregated. They also saw the fight in the middle with King of Nightmares and the clowns.

"It is the Clown King’s people! They dare show themselves!" The Glorious Chancer scowled. "Who’s that being attacked?"

"I think it’s King of Nightmares from the White Peacock!"

Gasp!

As the speaker finished his sentence, silence fell after a collective gasp.

King of Nightmares, the person who claimed to not be the strongest, but was said to be the most terrifying. He could manipulate at least 90% of the people to do anything they wouldn’t have done otherwise.

It didn’t only happen once or twice, but many, many times. Some had been hypnotized to streak, some were even hypnotized to lick the ground in the toilet while propping their buttocks up…

Or hypnotized to see the septic tank as a swimming pool…

The stories are so outlandish, but it always managed to throw people into bouts of goosebumps.

Hearing it was King of Nightmares, not only the normal people, the Demon Hunters, the Werewolves all took several steps back quietly. Even the Glorious Chancer himself frowned.

Because of that, King of Nightmares had numerous enemies and myths about him.

The Archbishop of the Holy Church, Archbishop Hester, who has had very positive public image, had been pursuing King of Nightmares when he was hit with a hypnotic suggestion, causing him to stop mid-fight and jerked off in public.

An old man, eighty-seven years of age… masturbating in front of hundreds of audience…

The old man killed himself after it ended, and King of Nightmares’ fame spread around the world yet again.

"Do we need to explain to them about the Jokers pretending to be us…" General Milo asked.

"What is there to explain? Don’t disgrace the Weisman Empire!" The Glorious Chancer persisted.

"King of Nightmares, the Clown King is our enemy as well. If you’re willing, we’ll definitely help in their extermination!" Werewolf pack leader declared.

"The Demon Hunters too!" The red-eyed lady shuddered as she recalled the event with the Archbishop.

Other powers quickly followed suit, as if scared about repercussions if they are the last.

"Who attacked us on the beach?" King of Nightmares clutched the head of the clown, restraining him, and stared at the crowd.

The clearing was messed up. King of Nightmares stood in the center of the crowd and glared without any signs of fear.

No one answered. The leader of the Demon Hunter, Elysha looked antsy.

Garen approached King of Nightmares with Si Lan in his arm, followed by Andrela.

"Maybe we can get information from this joker," Garen glanced at the clown held down by King of Nightmares. "The others called him Queen, so he must be pretty high-ranking."

"Kill me if you can! You can kill me, but you’ll never kill the Queen! Hahahahaha…" The clown laughed maniacally.

"Kill you?" King of Nightmares smirked, "There’s nothing easier than killing! You won’t die so easily in my hands!"

"Tomorrow, before this time, we have one day to find and kill the Clown King." Andrela peeked at his wristwatch and stated.

Chapter 219: The Wait 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"We were attacked by them as soon as we came ashore, and it looks like everyone who entered the island had been attacked. Poker Organization was definitely scheming something in secret. We were all here for the key, the Black Smoke Pot." Garen raised his voice, "I think everyone here wanted the Black Smoke Pot or witness its abilities. No matter what your intentions are, the ruins doesn’t seem to be opening yet, so we don’t really have conflict of interest here. Killing is unnecessary. I think, Clown King wants us to fight."

"It’s true, Clown King’s followers have the ability to disguise as other people, it’s easy for them to pick a fight as another person." Someone agreed.

Garen stood in the center with the others, surrounded by all the rest of the people.

These parties knew their power is not enough, so they only came to try their luck. Furthermore, these were the ones who managed to breakthrough Clown King’s trap through their willpower. Some of them were nameless people who powered on, some others were not necessarily unknown where they came from.

It didn’t matter who it was. Anyone who stood there have their own desire - the Black Smoke Pot.

It’s the same for the Three Major Generals. They were officially here to capture the Clown King, but in reality they were there for the Black Smoke Pot.

There were rumors of the Black Smoke Pot establishing the connection between this world and the Underworld.

The scene was in a slight confusion. No one party knows what the other parties think, so they were all being extra cautious at each other.

Most people were focusing on the three from White Peacocks in the center. Even if King of Nightmares was intimidating, who would really give up the opportunity to obtain the Black Smoke Pot, having come this far?

Those who were here had already made up their minds to breakthrough every single obstacle to get to it. If there were people who could settle for less, they already had and wouldn’t even make it to the island.

"What do you White Peacocks think?" The leader of the Three Major Generals, The Glorious Chancer spoke. "The Clown King had given up on the Black Smoke Pot and plead allegiance to the Immortal Palace. He’s here to get it for them. What about you?" He paused, "If I remembered correctly, the White Peacocks hadn’t been around for too long, but all of you seem to have unsettled business with the Immortal Palace?"

The three had already silently agreed for Garen to be the leader and the face for the group. Andrela had admitted to be inferior to Garen in fighting ability, King of Nightmares was not even considering to lead.

Garen stepped forward, staring at The Glorious Chancer.

"Black Smoke Pot is not our primary objective. Just as you said, our main focus is Immortal Palace."

The Glorious Chancer nodded. "What if we form an alliance with each other? Our mission was to capture Clown King, this aligns with your focus, I presume you and him also have a score to settle. Our other mission was for the Black Smoke Pot, that was our real mission."

"Alliance?" Garen didn’t think the Three Major Generals from Weisman would suggest such an idea, but seeing the sincerity on his face, Garen at least knew The Glorious Chancer really wants an alliance.

King of Nightmares muttered under his breath, "He was trying to soothe the sour relationship between you when Weisman sent the Killer Hunters Squad after you. I think they were even trying to recruit us."

Garen nodded subtly to indicate his understanding. The Red Sand Sword Gate saga wasn’t a huge thing now, but it was still something they had to settle.

"What’s in it for us in this alliance?" He hollered.

"If you help us get the Black Smoke Pot, and we’ll help you when you face off with the Immortal Palace. They are also the scourge to our organization." The Glorious Chancer proclaimed.

"How can I trust you?"

"I have been on this job for twenty five years. I have yet to make a promise I couldn’t keep." The Glorious Chancer stated calmly.

Between the back-and-forth of these two, some other teams around them started to shift. White Peacock and Weisman was already difficult by themselves, if they allied, no other teams would even be in the race to the prize anymore.

Some weaker groups started to leave the crowd. They were very aware of their abilities. Now that the situation had gone beyond their control. They might as well pull out before it was too late, after damages had been done.

The rest of the stronger groups which still had some confidence in themselves congregated, becoming larger temporary groups.

Garen and the Three Major Generals all noticed the behavior changes.

"The Northern Territory should be under Immortal Palace’s control, the King of the North Pole and God of the Spear have probably allied to resist the Immortal Palace," The Glorious Chancer continued, "If we join in the fight, Immortal Alliance will have no chance of succeeding."

He stared at Garen’s face. This young man is only twenty years of age, but the intelligence pointed out he’s a rising star who monopolized a whole province. He didn’t pay much attention before, but he didn’t realize the young man may be even stronger than what they had expected.

He immediately tried to recruit him.

"Weisman welcomes all talents and intellectuals. Top fighters like you three, you can get the best receptions and a position only second to us. Please give it some thought. Right now, the Confederation is not in a good spot, even normal citizen were able to see how bad the situation is. Three elites like you don’t need to waste your lives away on a dying tree, why not choose a bigger stage and a better environment?"

Garen and the other two didn’t reply directly. After King of Nightmares hypnotized the Queen clown, they already found out it was one of the clowns who originally disguised as the fighters from Weisman to attack them. Knowing that, their hatred for the Joker Squad deepened.

"Let’s not talk about this first. Our main objective here is still sussing out the Clown King." Garen steered the conversation away from recruitment. "I don’t know why the Clown King sent out so many cannon fodders to attack everyone. But since they’ve started the attack, they will need to face the consequences." He’s extremely upset with the Clown King for the loss of his Golden Sword Throne and Golden Seal. Since that was sorted out, vanquishing him is, of course, the main focus. With a pest chasing after them constantly will definitely be a discomfort.

The Glorious Chancer looked at his watch. "It is currently 7.35 in the evening, almost night time, but this blanket of mist is everywhere so we won’t notice the difference in our surrounding. If we want to exterminate the clowns, we still have 24 hours."

He looked around.

"I reckon the Clown King is among us."

"Do we need to clear the space?" Another Major General murmured. "With us and the White Peacocks, we’ve got the power to exterminate everyone else here."

"We’re not in a hurry." The Glorious Chancer shook his head.

Garen temporarily agreed to the alliance proposal, so he approached the Major Generals with Andrela and King of Nightmares. King of Nightmares was training the Queen clown absent-mindedly.

"Repeat after me, ‘I am a pig.’"

"I am a pig…" The clown was spaced out.

"‘I like to eat shit.’"

"I like to eat shit…"

"‘I love freshly baked ones.’"

"I love freshly baked ones..."

Garen and Andrela watched as King of Nightmares trained the clown and felt slightly sick. They know King of Nightmares enough to know they wouldn’t say something they were not going to do. They were preparing to really let the clown do the deed.

Si Lan also shuddered, but her priorities lie in finding Dale Quicksilver.

"Mr. Kelly, if you want to look for the Clown King, there’s a person who may be useful." She suppressed the urge to continue watching and managed to compose herself.

"You mean Detective Dale?" Garen had a slight frown.

"No need," King of Nightmares stood up, "I already found out the gist." They had a smirk on their face. "How dare he spring the bombs on us! And seeked refuge with the Immortal Palace!"

"We’ll still be here for the rest of our time, it may be beneficial to find Dale Quicksilver." Andrela have heard of his fame. "Even though we’re forming a temporary alliance with the Weisman’s, we’ll probably still need to fight them when we open the ruins’ entrance. Who wouldn’t want the Black Smoke Pot that can grant them breakthrough? The truce we’re having right now is temporary, it would be dangerous if they’ve gone all out in attacking us."

Garen nodded in agreement.

"Too bad we don’t know Palosa’s plan. If he’s here, we would have a bigger chance."

"The old guy had different persona at different time, none of us know what state he was in during this recluse. Don’t get careless…" Andrela spoke hushedly. "The Black Smoke Pot can only be used by one person, if we got to the end, I wouldn’t hold back even if it’s you I’m facing!"

"Let’s do our best." Garen smiled. A one-use item such as Black Smoke Pot that can communicate with the underworld, as well as help people ascend to higher peaks. Even if Andrela and him were best friends, it would be foolish to give up his path and dreams just because of that relationship.

They are partners, as well as rivals.

Even if he said he doesn’t want the Black Smoke Pot, but given the chance, he would not let that chance go either.

The truce they were having, was in fact the calm before the storm.

Garen looked around. "Let’s go look for Detective Dale." He took Si Lan in his arm, and stepped lightly on the ground, charging out without a sound.

Everyone else only saw a blur before Garen and Si Lan disappeared. Being reminded of the canyon between their abilities, more elites have almost given up.

The pillar jungle was full of thick stone pillars, each pillar was as tall as a tree with the bottom half carved straight up to the top half which was carved into statues of different poses.

Some of them sad, some happy, some in enjoyment, some in fury. All the statues were doing different actions than the others.

The stone pillars were placed far apart, about three to four meters. Between all the pillars, they formed a maze extending into every direction.

Chapter 220: The Wait 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

With Si Lan in his arm, Garen dashed through the field with increasing speed, looking for Dale Quicksilver following anywhere that had any signs of fighting.

Four encounters, plenty of followers of the Clown King, but no sign of Dale Quicksilver and White Eagle. They ran for another few hundred meters in the fog, and finally heard some grunting coming from the front.

They approached the sound and greeted with the sight of White Eagle fighting with a clown in red.

White Eagle held a white blade that was glowing some quivering black runes. His face was tense, veins popped, he basically looked like a savage. Even with that, he was quickly losing his ground against the clown.

Dale Quicksilver aimed his gun at the ones fighting but didn’t dare to shoot. They were both so quick in their movements it was impossible to aim.

White Eagle and the clown were both agility-type fighters, the light from the sword and the red clown’s claw kept finding ways to attack each other, but there were only swishing sound of the wind but not from one for clashing.

Srrt! A slash wound appeared on White Eagle’s right arm, but as his eyes were red with fury, he didn’t care.

"Mr. Kelly!" Seeing White Eagle in danger, Si Lan looked at Garen anxiously.

Garen nodded and stepped between the two in an instant, his arms outstretched toward the both of them.

Thud! Thud!

White Eagle and the clown got pushed back simultaneously.

Seeing Garen, the clown turned and ran without a word.

Garen squinted and grabbed at the clown’s head. His hand was as fast as lightning, only a white silhouette was visible.

"Stop butting in!"

A sudden killing intent came from behind Garen. White Eagle roared at him, charging.

Wielding the blade, White Eagle’s eyes were filled with hatred. A slicing air burst out of the white rune blade toward Garen’s back.

White Eagle didn’t expect to find his parents’ killer a dozen years after in the same place! The red clown was the killer who murdered his parents in cold blood! Even though he was being subdued earlier, he was planning to unleash his strongest attack the whole time until Garen interrupted the fight, forcing him to unleash the power earlier than he wanted.

The red clown also repocketed a small ball unwillingly. This ball is an item built specifically to defeat the rune blade. He was waiting for White Eagle to unleash the true power of the rune blade so he could reflect it back with the ball.

"Dammit! If he didn’t cut in so early!" The clown glared at Garen for a bit. "Just a little more, I would have killed White Eagle and tie up my loose ends!"

Seeing White Eagle stabbing at Garen, he felt a rush of schadenfreude.

The white rune blade pierced Garen on his back. Black light glowed on the runes on the blade, emitting a mysterious air.

Different from Flamingo’s sword, the most distinct feature of this rune blade was its sharpness. Whatever it stabbed, a pierce mark would appear, whatever it hacked at, they would be cut in half.

This is Garen’s first sense of crisis since mastering the Divine Statue Technique.

"Ten Thousand Mammoth Retrograde!"

Garen rippled his arm, pushing an invisible force outward.

Boom!

A transparent ripple formed in the air from Garen’s arms.

The ripple spread, hitting both White Eagle and the clown, causing them to fall backward onto the ground and slid some distance before stopping.

Garen flexed his back, the tiny pierce wound quickly closed and disappeared.

He turned back to look at White Eagle.

"What are you doing! Mr. Kelly saved you, and you want to stab him!" Si Lan ran over and propped White Eagle up. At that point the veins on White Eagle’s face had subsided.

Blood rushed to his mouth, which he spat out immediately. He looked exhausted.

"You’re not even a Grandmaster of Combat, and you dared to come to the Smoke Island." Garen shook his head in disbelief. "You guys are too reckless."

"I…" White Eagle didn’t know what to say. He had hurt Garen in his excited state. "I’m sorry… I was influenced by the blade."

Garen shook his head, ignoring White Eagle, and turned toward the approaching Dale Quicksilver.

Dale Quicksilver recognized him and withdrew his gun, flashing him a wry smile.

"Mr. Kelly, I didn’t think we would meet like this."

"Yeah, same here." Garen shrugged, "Were you here for the Black Smoke Pot?"

"Of course not, we are self-aware people." Dale Quicksilver said. "It may sound a little sudden, but I hope to get your help. To be honest, my daughter and White Eagle’s son were both kidnapped onto this island, we were looking for a long time, but we haven’t been able to locate them…"

"You want me to help you find the kids?"

"If there’s anything I could help you with, please tell me." Dale Quicksilver added readily.

Garen hesitated. Dale Quicksilver was an old friend, it wouldn’t be too hard to help him. However, with the time he had left…

Si Lan tied the unconscious clown up and came over. "The one who kidnapped the kids was Clown King. We need to find him, just like Mr. Kelly. So our goal aligns."

"So…" Dale Quicksilver looked relieved. "What do you think?"

Garen thought silently.

"We can’t delay here for too long. If we can’t figure this out by tomorrow, we’ll need to abort."

Dale Quicksilver dropped his head in deep thought, and looked up almost immediately, "Three hours. I can find him in three hours."

"Oh?" Garen stared at him, slightly surprised. "You sure?"

"Of course!"

Garen kept his quiet and led the detective group back, dragging the unconscious clown along. White Eagle kept having the urge to finish the clown off on the way, but he persevered.

In the middle of the pillar jungle was an oval black stone tile, a massive black stone statue was erected in the center of it.

The statue is about a dozen meters in height, posed like a humanoid Lucky Cat*. Its head was large with a kind facial features, but it wasn’t clear whether it’s a male or a female. White smoke continually billowed out of its nostrils, ears, and mouth. Wisps of smoke hung around the air, adding to the mysterious calmness the scene brings.

The Three Major Generals of Weisman Empire, as well as the Werewolf Bedega had already arrived and were resting against the statue, planning to wait until the next day in that position.

Andrela and King of Nightmares stood beside the three generals, and made space as soon as they saw Garen with a number of people following him.

Garen didn’t speak. He led Dale Quicksilver and the others there and sat down, not caring about anything else. Dale Quicksilver and Si Lan couldn’t stay still, they started wandering around.

Some of the other parties had already left, the rest were just people who were trying their luck. With Garen’s fame, Dale Quicksilver had no trouble talking to people. There wasn’t much info, but he finally understood Garen’s influence.

Dale Quicksilver kept his eyes low to cover up his surprise.

"Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate Second Divine Warrior… White Cloud Gate Master? Mr. Kelly had us fooled for so long!"

"What is a ‘Divine Warrior’? What level is he?" Si Lan wasn’t too familiar with the Martial Arts community, and even Yoke and White Eagle was curiously staring at Dale. They weren’t people from that circle, so they didn’t know how intrepid he actually is.

"Is he as strong as the people from Golden Hoop?" White Eagle asked after having a thought.

Dale Quicksilver wasn’t sure whether he should laugh or cry. "He is one of the strongest leaders of Golden Hoop. Under his management, White Cloud Gate was getting so much attention from the government, a province was basically given to him! What do you think?"

Gasp.

It was then that Si Lan and White Eagle finally understand what ‘Divine Warrior’ entails.

"Will he, you know…" White Eagle asked worriedly. "There were tons of people who wanted my sword…"

"If he wanted to target us, it would have been as easy as killing an ant… Your blade is powerful, but I don’t think he wants it. When he saw your blade just now, he wasn’t very surprised, that means he has seen similar things before." Dale Quicksilver analyzed. "Let’s not talk about this. We need to focus on finding the Clown King."

"Isn’t three hours a little tight?" Si Lan asked, concerned.

"It’s alright, I already have some thoughts." Dale Quicksilver replied confidently.

Garen leaned against the foot of the giant statue, watching Dale Quicksilver and the others walk about the area and occasionally stop to check the marks on the ground.

"You think they really can suss out the Clown King?" King of Nightmares asked boredly. "I’ve already hypnotized those clowns, nothing."

"Let’s give it a shot, it doesn’t cost us anything, at least we got someone to help." Garen stated.

"When do you want to get the key?" King of Nightmares continued asking, "The key on the Werewolves are easier to get than the ones on those three from Weisman. If we want it, we can get it easily."

"Don’t worry. Let’s look for the Clown King first." Garen wasn’t in a hurry, "Between the Southern and the Northern Territories, only one side could win the qualification to use the item. We’ll have to fight at the end anyway. If we’ve got the keys but were killed by the people from the North, it’d be pointless. At the end, only one person is deserving of the Black Smoke Pot."

"To break limits… I didn’t think I’d be interested at first, but now I feel like I wanna fight for it." Andrela muttered.

The three stopped chattering and sat quietly on the ground.

The fog started to become darker. Whatever they can see of the sky was turning gray, and the fog had become thicker.

Some people tried to light a torch, but torches were dampened by the fog, they just won’t light up. It got colder, weaker people were starting to feel the chill.

Dale Quicksilver strutted about for a while and stopped. He walked to somewhere quiet and started thinking deeply.

Garen ignored him. He only needed an answer, how Dale Quicksilver came up with that answer wasn’t important. His attention was on the white rune blade in White Eagle’s hands.

The blade is impressive even though it could only break his skin, but it was much more powerful than the one Flamingo had. However it doesn’t seem to have a great range, obviously the makers focused on different aspects of their blades.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. Lit. Wealth-beckoning cat. A Japanese cat figurine that has one paw up by its face. Usually mistaken for Chinese in origin due to its popularity in the Chinese community. Look up maneki-neko.

Chapter 221: Clarity 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen noticed that the runes on the rune blade moves on their own. Flamingo’s was the same, his sword having red runes. It’s not something logic can explain.

Even though the rune blade wasn’t able to deal enough damage to seriously hurt him, it was enough to break his skin. With just that, he didn’t dare to underestimate the white blade.

"White Eagle, can I have a look at your sword?" Garen asked calmly.

White Eagle flinched and looked at Garen, at the same time, he stole a look at Dale Quicksilver and hesitated.

"Sure."

He handed over his blade to Garen.

Holding it, Garen started to scrutinize the blade.

　　******************

Northern Territory

Somewhere deep within the fog

In the middle of the jungle formed with black statues.

Sylphalan half-kneeled on the ground, breathing heavily, one of his hands pressed on the ground while the other on his heart.

Lub-dub! Lub-dub!

His heartbeat, as loud as drums, echoed throughout the jungle of stone statues.

Sylphalan bit his lower lip, the hand on his heart clutching at his shirt and his chest. The drilling heart ache he had was impacting his ability to focus, even his vision started to blur.

"Still okay?" Flamingo walked out from behind a black statue. He wore a set of red clothing, the Sword of the Sprite sheathed by his side. He looked clean, like a ball of pure fire, not even his feet seemed to have any dust on them.

"Yeah…" Sylphalan struggled while standing up, but he managed a murmur. "Leave if the time comes, I suspect I wouldn’t be able to control myself."

Flamingo kept quiet.

"Don’t force yourself."

"I know. But after suppressing it for so long, I really need to let it loose once in awhile." Sylphalan answered.

"I really can’t tell if your choices then were right or wrong." Flamingo sighed helplessly then slowly stepped backward into the thick fog until his silhouette was completely gone.

Somewhere out there, footsteps approached hurried.

"He was hiding in here! Sylphalan, this time I will make sure you die!"

"Murderer! I finally can avenge my father today!" "Be careful of the others from Immortal Palace! Ace, tell everyone to be alert!" "Yessir!"

Sounds of people were approaching Sylphalan quickly. Numerous valiant auras surrounded Sylphalan.

All these people were elites, among them, at least four to five were able to unleash their Auras that were as strong as some of the top level Grandmasters of Combat, weaker to Duskdune Shura by a little. They were all here to seek revenge from Immortal Palace. Because of his strength, some of them were also trying to eliminate Sylphalan so they can have a chance of grabbing the Black Smoke Pot for themselves.

Lub-dub!

Sylphalan palpitated once more. His brows were slowly knitting together, veins popped up on his skin, congregating toward the center of his brows.

Hoof…

Sylphalan stood up, two bumps appearing on his armpits.

　　***************

Garen examined the blade carefully. The rune blade in his hands were not very different from normal swords. No flowing runes, no special powers, as if it really was a normal longsword.

"Incredible…" He returned the rune blade to White Eagle. He wasn’t able to see anything, but some of the patterns on the sword was really fascinating.

The sky had already darkened by this point, moonlight spilled down from above, its shape blurred by the layer of fog.

"Mr. Garen." Dale Quicksilver finally returned to Garen’s side. "I think I know where the Clown King is."

"Oh?" Garen looked at him with interest. "Are you sure?"

"Yes." Dale Quicksilver nodded.

"Tell me, where is he hiding?" Garen stared at him attentively. He tried sensing everyone here including the Three Major Generals, everyone seemed normal to him.

"Clown King didn’t hide, he disguised." Dale Quicksilver answered with confidence.

"Disguised?" Si Lan and King of Nightmares moved close to listen to the analysis.

"Yes, his disguise is pretty flawless, normal people wouldn’t be able to tell." Dale Quicksilver stated calmly. "Don’t you think the situation here feels a little odd?"

"Oh?" Garen was finally aware, about an hour ago, all the parties looked a little weird, something in them looked strange.

He looked around, focusing on each group as his gaze passed.

The Werewolves gathered around, talking about something inaudible.

The three Weisman Major Generals sat together not far away, eyes closed.

The Demon Hunters were fixing up something, looking busy.

The other smaller teams were also doing their own thing in their corner.

"Can you point him out directly?" Garen turned his attention back to Garen.

"Of course."

Dale scanned at the other people around, his gaze steady and calm. "The real Clown King was hiding among the obscure group over there." He looked at the crowd of unknown people in the corner. "Gate Master Garen, please take my signal when approaching him, or else he would be able to run away again!"

"Of course." Garen nodded.

"Good." Dale Quicksilver stared at the unknown group and raised his arm, as if to point out the target. "The real Clown King is… Seize White Eagle!"

He yelled and rushed behind Garen.

No one was able to react in that instant.

White Eagle paled, his rune blade slashed at Dale Quicksilver, creating a fan-shaped aura.

Phoosh!

A strong draft toward the blade made him miss his aim.

The draft was Garen’s misty breath!

He leaped up, grabbing at the rune blade with one hand and at White Eagle’s neck with the other. His stance was like a fierce tiger hunting a sheep, bringing about chilly wind.

White Eagle yelped and retreated as he sheathed his sword. His lightly-stepping toes were even faster than Garen. He somersaulted in the air, evading Garen’s pounce.

"You again! Dale Quicksilver! I wanted to give you a chance, you deathseeker! I will kill you today!"

"Let’s see how you kill someone who’s under my protection!" Garen said coolly.

"No one had ever survived Clown King’s assassination!" The Clown King landed and pulled at his own face, tearing off a mask and revealing a man with strange makeup on his face.

Garen was going to attack when he suddenly heard Dale Quicksilver grunt. He turned back.

Detective Dale was pressing on his right arm, his face slightly green. That’s an obvious indication he was poisoned. The scarlet wound on his arm was definitely inflicted right before.

"Damn you!" Garen roared with fury.

Crack!

His stomp made a hole on the ground as he shot himself toward the Clown King like an arrow. His right hand aimed at Clown King’s throat, pushing an invisible force to arrive before he did.

As the invisible force closed into Clown King’s throat, another force shot out from the side, bumping into Garen’s arm, making him miss his mark.

Boom!

Garen’s attack hit a stone statue, crushing it like a bean curd and slicing a huge chunk off it. Pieces of stone hit the ground, creating tiny craters all over.

Even the pieces were so loaded with power from the missed attack, giving everyone else who witnessed it a chill.

Clown King shuddered. If it wasn’t for his savior, he would’ve been sliced in half with that attack.

Garen was furious. That attack could have killed the Clown King before he figured out his style of combat. Catching him by surprise and killing him would’ve rendered him unable to use any of his tricks, like the clowns before.

If it wasn’t for the third person who bumped into his arm.

He glared at the Clown King as he escaped like a threatened bunny. Feeling dissatisfied, he turned toward the one who parried his attack.

"You!" His eyes went wide, shocked.

Not only him, Andrela and King of Nightmares also felt surprised by the turn of events. They thought Garen would be able to finish the Clown King by himself. After all, however strong the Clown King was, he was still weaker than Duskdune Shura. Fighting him face-to-face would be easy, they weren’t expecting this turn of tides.

"We’ll go after him…" Andrela stood up with his hand on his sword, but he couldn’t finish his sentence.

King of Nightmares also looked serious as they looked around.

The Werewolves, the Demon Hunters, and the Three Major Generals of Weisman were all standing up, facing them, slowly encircling them.

Clown King laughed shrilly, looking at them from afar.

"Weisman’s Generals had already planned from the start to eliminate you elites from the Confederation. Temporary alliance? Talking terms and conditions? You idiots!"

The Glorious Chancer crossed his arms in front of his chest, standing still.

"White Peacock, if you agree to join the Weisman, then I won’t have to ruin my reputation after all these years building it for you."

Garen turned a deaf ear to him, his gaze slowly becoming mild as he looked at the one blocking him.

"I only thought you’ll make a move later, I didn’t expect you to carry it out so soon…"

He had already expected this situation. The Weisman’s were never trustworthy, he only thought they would carry it out so early.

The person in front looked at Garen calmly.

"To me, you were the biggest threat in this race. Give up, you no longer have any chance of getting it."

"Palosa, do you really think you can stop me?" Garen ripped off his shirt readily, revealing his fair sculpted upper body.

"Don’t forget, I’m the First Divine Warrior." Palosa also ripped off his shirt, revealing his skin tight black martial arts clothes.

The one blocking Garen from pursuing was Palosa who separated with them earlier. Garen didn’t know what agreement he had with Clown King, compelling him to save Clown King.

"Boring."

Garen slowly clasped his hands together as if praying to a Buddha statue. As his palms met, a transparent bubble of air slowly circulated around him.

"Since my mastery of the Divine Statue Technique, I haven't been using my full strength. Palosa… don't let me down."

His eyes widened, and his hands stabbed forward.

"Divine Statue, West Phoenix Fist!"

Caw!

As Garen punched, a set of large wings appeared on his back. Those were wings as large as a Phoenix's. Shapeless and colorless, the wings extended out toward Palosa in synchrony with Garen's piercing hands.

Chapter 222: Clarity 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This was the fighting style he had come up after gathering all sorts of secret techniques and merging them with the physical fighting style of the Golden Statue Technique, a style that was most suitable for him. East King Hand and West Phoenix Fist were among the most essential moves.

Garen understood that regular attacks were meaningless when facing an opponent like Palosa, so he decided to just use his strongest moves.

Putting his palms together, piercing straight ahead.

The huge phoenix wings behind him were formed from aura, pressing down on the opponent’s acupressure points from both sides as it created a huge impact in at instant, forcing the opponent to take the hit head-on. This was an ultra-powerful lethal attack combining acupressure, aura, and killing moves!

Garen’s hands were straight as an arrow as he rushed forth, like the sharpest drill, aiming for Palosa’s chest.

If this move made contact, he just had to split his palms apart and the victim would be instantly torn into two. It was the same result as the East King Hand.

If the East King Hand used great speed and power to compress invisible air currents into killing a person, then the West Phoenix Fist was the essence of all of Garen’s skills.

Palosa’s right arm grabbed forth, while his left hand quickly touched a few points on his body.

With a tearing sound, his arm suddenly expanded greatly. It was surrounded by a swarm of countless currents of black aura, crawling around his arm like bugs.

"Secret technique, Snake Scale Arm!"

In a split second, those transparent phoenix wings collided abruptly into the black aura. A huge aura current erupted in all directions at the same time.

Boom!

The earth gave a mighty tremor, making everyone’s feet and the rest of their bodies numb.

Some of the stone statues that had been knocked around in the previous fighting fell to the ground with a crash, stone shards going everywhere.

　　********

Andrela took a few large strides forward, and was black by the general from Weisman with the black chest hair.

"Looking like you guys really do plan to help the Clown King stop us." Andrela casually slices with his sword a few times, his eyes staring intently at the general before him.

"Unfortunately, compared to the Clown King, you guys are the bigger threat. After we’re done with you, we’ll naturally go settle the clown." The general chuckled.

"Settle us? With just you guys?" Andrela laughed coldly. "Although I don’t know how the Clown King got you guys together, Garen’s power is not something you lot can imagine. The King of Nightmares has also long since ceased to be the Nightmare that you know."

"Cut the crap, it still comes down to true power." The general with black chest hair didn’t mince any more words, pulling out a pair of black handguns and twirling them with a swoosh.

　　********

The one in front of Nightmare is the female leader of the demon hunters, Elysha.

"King of Nightmares, you are indeed very strong, but I’m only here to keep you occupied. As soon as those two are done, your death will be imminent." Demon Hunter Elysha laughed coldly.

"Are you joking?" Nightmare yawned.

"What do you think?" Elysha pulled out a black lace belt from her pocket, and actually blindfolded herself. "Your hypnotic power is 80% reliant on sight. Unfortunately, I’m strongest when I’m not using my eyes…"

"Oh?" Nightmare got slightly more serious. Elysha was one of the strongest Demon Hunters, the strongest of her generation. That wasn’t a title you got by bluffing.

But how many of those who managed to get to Smoke Island were small fry, anyway? They all had impressive abilities and resumes. To really find out who was stronger, the only way was with face-to-face battles.

　　*********

Foom!

Garen’s right claw pressed onto Palosa’s arms, his sharp fingernails digging deep into Palosa’s arm muscles.

"Secret Technique, Shadow Fist!" Palosa’s arms suddenly became blurry, almost as though he grew another pair of arms, abruptly appearing in front of Palosa’s chest."

"Divine Statue, Red Palm!" Garen had absolutely no intention of dodging, the corners of his lips turning cruel. His left palm pressed towards Palosa, the palm completely red, glowing and smooth like a jade. Even the veins, muscles and bones were slightly visible.

Foom!!

There was yet another blunt noise, and the two were blasted apart, each of them taking a few steps back.

A charred black handprint appeared on Palosa’s chest, blood leaking out of his mouth and nose. His fingers quickly pressed a few more dots onto his body, and a small cube-shaped swelling on his chest vanished in a trace. His expression improved a lot with that.

"Once more!" Garen threw caution to the windows, rushing forth once more. His feet stomped down hard on the floor, boom boom boom! Madly charging forward like a behemoth, his enormous legs smashed into the floor hard, like stone pillars.

Each step brought with it extremely heavy tremors.

Compared to Palosa, the two handprints on Garen’s chest were merely surface deep, and had barely caused any damage at all.

The two of them collided into each other once more, both of them using brute force and aiming to kill, without holding anything back. After Palosa’s meditative retreat, he had managed to regain the power he had at his peak. And Garen had also progressed beyond the level of power he had when they first fought.

With every time they made contact, they created an intense explosion of aura. The powerful gusts of wind kept blowing in all directions, compressing the air with high pressure and creating fierce bursting noises, as though they were lighting firecrackers.

Bam!

Before Palosa could catch his breath, Garen’s palm landed on his shoulder. He retreated more than ten steps back, his fingers hastily using the secret technique to rapidly heal his injury. Then he pounced at Garen once more, without the slightest pause.

It had only been a few seconds since they began fighting, but the stone forest was already in shatters. Nobody could interfere.

Forcing Palosa back with one hit of his palm, Garen rushed forward, and grabbed both of Palosa’s arms with his hands.

"Let’s see you regenerate again after I tear apart your limbs!" The battle had drawn on some of the viciousness in him. The Divine Statue Technique’s extreme endurance allowed him to function at full strength for a few days and nights. Right now, he was practically a humanoid mecha, who knew no weariness. He could even instantly recover from injuries. After all, the Divine Statue Technique had always been known for its extreme regenerative power.

A series of hits, all of them taken head-on, was a bit too much for even Palosa.

Pom! He pushed apart the hands grabbing him and stumbled before taking yet another palm blow. Another mouthful of blood leaked out of his lips. But at the same time, he landed a kick on Garen’s abdomen.

However, it was obvious that his opponent was planning to take a hit for a hit. Seeing how energetic Garen was, it seemed that he had improved a great deal more since last time. Even the attacks that landed on his body were stiff, the power unable to spread.

"Do it!!" Polsa suddenly roared.

Shocked for a moment, Garen abruptly felt a great gust of wind rushing towards him mercilessly, hitting him in the middle of his back.

Pomm!!

Garen’s whole body was pushed a few steps forward, before his legs dug themselves into the ground and steadied him. He had no time to think, because there were five terrifyingly threatening presences coming at him from all four directions, as well as from above his head.

Other than Palosa, the other four were each at least as strong as Duskdune Shura, while the strongest among them was almost equal to Palosa.

These five elite fighters all came at him at once.

It felt to Garen as though all the air around him had been sucked away, and he was standing in a vacuum. The skin on his body, face and arms were all rippling with the force of that immense wind.

Looking from above, Garen was standing alone in the middle, while Holy Fist Palosa, The Glorious Chancer, the Werewolf Bedega, and the Clown King were coming from all four sides.

Above him was the last Weisman general, holding a spear like a tuning fork as he aimed for Garen’s head from above.

The five enormous auras merged and mashed together, all aiming for Garen in the center.

"Palosa!! You have fallen!!"

Garen howled with mad laughter, holding his arms wide.

A pale shade of platinum began to spread rapidly across his skin, as though he had been plated in platinum. The result had an indescribable sense of sacredness and purity.

Platinum aura gathered around him in an instant. Countless currents of platinum aura gathered together, slowly becoming a strange image!

It was a huge platinum face, Garen’s own face!!

Baroom!!!

The platinum aura abruptly erupted!

　　*********************

Northern Territory

The whole Northern Territory was covered with blood and corpses. There was almost no one left alone. Only the central region.

In the center, amidst a wasteland of gore, Sylphalan stood quietly among the corpses, his face covered with splattered blood.

His body was emitting an unspeakably terrifying black aura, just like viscous black tar, covering the entire area and turning it into a dark hell.

On his brow, countless veins had gathered and formed a strange symbol like an eye. It was as though he had grown a third eye.

The God of Spear, Mare was kneeling not far away from him, the short spear in his hand having been broken in two. There was a large hole in his shoulder, so much so that the white fog behind his shoulder was almost visible.

The King of the North Pole was deathly pale, lying unconscious on the floor nearby. There were pieces of metal shrapnel all around him, probably something from an airplane.

The King of the Gun, Nikon had been broken into two, his eyes wide at the injustice of his death.

Boom!!!

Amidst a thick fog in the distance, a beam of platinum aura burst toward the sky.

Throughout the whole island, every living creature’s spirit responded with a jolt.

Sylphalan looked in the direction of the distant south, and it was as though he could see Garen’s face.

"Aura Solidification…" In that instant, it was as though he saw that unbeatable figure from his youth. "Big Brother…"

He pointed his finger at the sky.

Boom!!!

A surge of black aura suddenly formed a pillar, shooting into the sky and becoming an enormous face. It wasn’t his, but that of a gentle and beautiful woman.

For a moment two huge faces from the North and South stared at each other across the distance.

　　　**************

Garen stood quietly in the same place as before, platinum aura emanating from his body and dying the entire central area white.

He stood alone in the center, his platinum-colored skin clear and eye-catching, as though he was the only God in all the world.

The three generals, Palosa, and the Clown King were all forced down by the platinum aura. Each of them were injured to some extent in the blow just now, drastically reducing their power. Just then they were being held down by the aura and fought against it desperately, but to no avail. All they could do was struggle in the tiny area of their own aura.

Garen looked into the distant North. In the sky there, a black face was looking at his direction.

"Aura Solidification… Sylphalan…"

Chapter 223: Appear 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"A level of power where one is able to use aura to influence the currents. It’s a peak level that Palosa only achieved in his heyday, when all his personalities were one."

Andrela stood with Nightmare, looking at Garen’s wild aura covering the sky as he explained softly. "That is the legendary highest level of a martial artist. In ancient times, such a person was called the King of the Century! Garen… he has finally achieved this level!!"

"King of the Century…" Nightmare looked up at the platinum aura pillar, a similar expression of awe and shock on his face. This aura was as limitless as the sea, and just one touch brought with it an overwhelming sense of enormity and infinity. It was almost enough to make one get onto their knees. "To think that martial arts could really reach such a level…" He had never believed that martial arts could go so far. With the accelerated advent of firearms, the fall of fighting arts was all but certain.

And right now, Garen’s eruption truly showed him the end of this road.

The black night sky was practically lit up by the platinum aura. The white light pierced through the fog, as though it was truly sunlight shining across the island.

But it wasn’t really light, just an illusion of the nervous system caused by sensing that aura.

Everybody watched the two auras in the sky over the island, shocked. That was the level of the legendary Aura Solidification, the level known as the King of the Century!

All those people representing the different powers around him retreated backwards one after the other, trying to escape being enveloped by that platinum aura. They had to retreat up to several hundred meters before they could escape the range of the aura.

Within the range of that aura, it was a matter of Garen’s will for anyone to immediately end up just like those five elite fighters. It was akin to being caught in a cage.

Garen pulled his gaze back, and looked around him.

The five elite fighters were all constrained for now, and had no chance of escape.

With one wave of his hand, the platinum aura was abruptly pulled back, distilling into a huge platinum divine statue behind him.

At the same time, the statue suddenly reached out its arms and grabbed the Clown King.

The enormous platinum arms got hold of the Clown King with a rush of violent aura.

"No!!" The Clown King screamed. With a loud pomp, thick blue mist erupted and hid the giant platinum hands within its depths.

Wherever the fog touched, thick layers of blue ice formed on the spot. It was extremely strange. Some of the grass between the crevices were affected, and quickly became a puddle of blue liquid.

Boom!!

Another burst of flames exploded from inside the blue fog.

The giant hands vanished, as did the fog flames. All that remained where the Clown King had been was a pile of minced meat.

But Garen frowned slightly. An intense eruption of the platinum aura could indeed hold everyone down, but such an eruption couldn’t last long, and took a heavy toll on his spirit.

As soon as he withdrew his aura, the other four presences pounced at him ferociously.

The Glorious Chan and the Werewolf Bedega came at him from the front, one of the wielding a blade while the other had sharp claws shining red. The air rippled with the rush of wild and violent aura. The giant whale and black wolf formed by their respective also bore their fangs at the platinum statue madly.

At the same time, there were two more equally powerful presences and currents from others behind him.

Garen snorted coldly, and ignored them all.

"Divine Statue, Ten Thousand Mammoth Trample!!" He crossed his arms, and faced the two in front of him directly. The invisible aura emanated from him in waves, the roar of trumpeting mammoths rising from the air.

Bam!!!

His arms collided with the blade and claws, producing a sound loud enough to make one’s teeth ache.

A large amount of platinum aura broke through the Glorious Chan’s and the Werewolf leader’s aura without mercy, piercing straight through like a sharp knife. Both of them coughed blood as they quickly fell back, their faces turning from white to red rapidly.

There were also two dull noises behind Garen. The impact of their hit made him jolt slightly, but he ignored that as well, pouncing forward.

Smack!

His hands curled into claws and he grabbed the Werewolf leader’s throat, the platinum aura putting an end to all future resistance in an instant. Although it was just a moment, that was already enough.

Ker-chak!

The bones in his throat were shattered with a light pinch. Bedega held his throat tightly and retreated, falling to his knees.

Garen’s expression remained unchanged, his right palm glowing like red jade. He turned it backhand, and met with Palosa’s palm in the middle of the latter’s sneak attack.

His left palm slammed into the Glorious Chan’s shoulder, as fast as lightning. He had also taken advantage of the second after his opponent’s aura had been broken through, and the opponent fell into a temporary moment of numbness.

Bang-bang-bang-bang!!!

It was one palm against the Glorious Chan’s shoulder, but there were four sounds of impact.

With every sound, the Glorious Chan’s shoulder sunk some more. By the fourth sound, the entire left side of his body had been utterly destroyed.

In the end, he fell a few steps back in a daze, his eyes quickly losing all light before he collapsed onto the ground.

"Big brother!!!" A roar of grief came from behind Garen.

Garen’s face was emotionless as he turned around quickly. One more palm hit.

It went up directly against the sharp tip of something like a tuning fork.

Clang!!!

The tuning fork vibrated intensely, neither the sharp tip nor the palm giving way. The Wesiman general in front of him had an expression of madness, all the skin on his body as red as a cooked lobster. It was evident that he had used some secret technique to increase his power exponentially in the shortest amount of time.

Garen was just about to retreat and escape. Just then, there was another ‘boom’ and a huge wave of power, forcing him to remain where he stood.

He tilted his head slightly to look back, and saw Palosa huffing through his moustache, one palm on Garen’s back as his expression remained calm.

"It’s over." A sharp voice came from the air above him.

Garen looked up abruptly, his pupil dilating. A flowery figure was falling on him rapidly from above.

It was the Clown King!!

He held a rune blade in his hand as he pierced straight down. Little bits of black light danced on the sharp tip of the rune blade.

It was that little of black light that gave Garen a sense of immense threat. From the corner of his eye, he suddenly saw something tied onto the hilt of the rune blade.

It was a bundle of purple explosives!

And at the same time, another general as well as the Demon Hunter leader Elysha rushed over at the same time. One held a sword and the other a gun, neither of them pausing for even a second.

"Save him!!!"

Andrela and Nightmare jolted at the same time, and rushed over from each side.

But it was obviously too late.

Garen’s raised face could already feel the sharpness of the rune blade, and the feeling of the tip piercing through his brow.

Suddenly, he smiled mildly.

Opened his mouth and exhaled.

Clang!!

A pillar of white air erupted into the sky, hitting the middle of the rune blade. The blade broke accordingly, the tip flying to the side and passing through the Weisman general’s forehead before sinking into a black stone statue with a whoosh. A string of bright red blood followed in its wake.

The Clown King’s smile froze in a second. He suddenly remembered how he had shown Garen the rune blade before, and his body fell to the ground in accordance with gravity despite himself.

"East King Hand!!"

Garen roared, invisible aura appearing around his body and looking almost solid. Behind him, Palosa was forced back by more than ten steps.

Rripp!!

The Clown King’s body was directly torn apart by Garen’s hands, scattering onto the black stone surface. There was not even a complete bone to be found, everything was shredded by that mad power.

In that moment, everyone stopped whatever they were doing. Even Andrela and Nightmare, who had been rushing here, stopped in their tracks and stared at the minced gore on the floor, feeling slightly nauseous. Their gazes on Garen were different too, as though they were seeing him for the first time.

"And I thought I had become his match, to think…" Nightmare bit his lip unhappily. "Is this the limit of martial arts? That’s too much!"

Andrela, on the other hand, was struck speechless. Only his knuckles on the sword hilt were white.

Arooo!!! Arooo!! Arooo!!!!!

The howls of grieving wolves came from the distance. It was the werewolves mourning the death of their leader. They didn’t rush forth, choosing instead to retreat in twos and threes.

Palosa’s back was against the stone statue as he looked at Garen calmly, a hint of the end in his eyes. He glanced at everyone around them

Elysha and the Weisman general who had rushed over earlier also stopped in their tracks, standing on the spot and afraid to come any closer.

Of all the other elite fighters remaining, all of them had been utterly destroyed in that second. The Glorious Chan, the other general, the Werewolf Bedega, the Clown King. In exchange for those four lives, all they had accomplished was a little scrape on Garen’s brow.

"I thought you had just recently achieved this level and couldn’t steady yourself. Looks like I was wrong." He suddenly heaved a heavy sigh. "There are two keys, how about we take one each? There’s no more reason to fight."

He glanced at Andrela and Nightmare. "Those two over there have no intention of fighting for the keys, right?"

Garen was also watching him calmly. From before until now, this old man’s expression hadn’t changed much. It was obvious he still had a trump card hidden. Even when he ganged up on Garen with the others earlier, he hadn’t truly brought out all of his power.

"Take three of my palm hits. If you’re still alive after that, I’ll pretend that ganging up just now didn’t happen," he said suddenly.

Palosa wasn’t surprised in the least. He merely took a deep breath, his expression turning unprecedentedly solemn. "Three hits? How arrogant of you! But according to your condition and power right now, you do have the right to say something like that. I accept!"

He had initially planned to use all the elite fighters here against Garen at once. Even if they couldn’t kill him, they should be able to fatally injure him. To think the opposite happened, and they forced such a terrifying power out of him.

Once one attained this level of martial arts, it was another transformation in itself. For those who did not deserve to touch fighters of that level, it was a miracle that they managed to hurt Garen at all.

Palosa’s thoughts were in a whirl, but he slowly opened his legs to stand steady. "To think that the trump card I had prepared for Sylphalan would have no choice but to be used on you in advance…"

He held out three fingers, his thumb, pointer and middle fingers.

Those three fingers abruptly pressed onto the center of his brow and both of his temples.

Smack! After a small sound.

Palosa put his hand down again, a huge amount of pure white aura erupting around him. The large aura rippled and crashed like sea waves, quickly forming a huge white bird.

Screee!!!

The giant bird made a strange sound. In terms of height, it was actually equal to Garen’s platinum statue.

Palosa’s eyes turned completely white, so that not a trace of his pupils could be seen. The clothes on his body were torn apart by his rapidly expanding muscles, his height increasing from 180cm to more than two meters. His whole body had the perfect proportions and lines.

Phew!!!

He exhaled slowly, two pillars of white air bursting out of his nostrils and smashing into the ground, even leaving two small dents there.

"The three personas have become one, is it?" Garen finally turned serious. Seeing that Palosa’s aura was actually as tall as his, it was obvious that as he was right now, he had the right to fight Garen face-on.

"To be able to perfect a simple Assassination Fist to such an extent. Palosa, you are truly the number one!" Garen curled one hand into a claw, and closed the other hand into a fist before pointing it at the air, his legs in a forward stance. It was as though his whole body was holding up an unbelievably heavy, extremely huge object.

"Take my first hit." Garen rushed forward soundlessly. The platinum statue’s fists also became white currents, twisting around his arms and forming two platinum spikes from his palms.

Chapter 224: Appear 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Smack!

His right palm lightly knocked against Palosa’s raised palms. There wasn’t any intense explosion, and neither was there a ferocious all-encompassing impact of aura.

There was just two spikes of aura darting forward like poisonous snakes, and then flashing back like lightning, leaving everything exactly like before.

Similarly, Garen shot back in an instant, landing on an empty spot ten meters away.

"The second hit!"

Without pausing, he dashed forward once more.

Exactly like the previous palm hit, he once more struck against Palosa’s palm lightly.

"Shape Sever Finger!!" Palosa roared, his fingers dotting Garen’s palm like raindrops. The moment each finger touched his hand, it flashed with a hint of grey-green.

The two separated once more, and both fell silent.

"The last hit!" Garen leapt forward, the platinum statue abruptly merging with him to become one. His entire body was edged with a platinum light.

"Southern Fists."

He leapt lightly and landed in front of Palosa, both his palms pressing forward soundlessly.

Boom!!

In that split second, a great platinum aura burst out around Garen’s figure, the aura and the currents mixing together to form countless sharp knives flying at Palosa from all directions.

Pom!! Dang-dang-dang!!

Palosa took ten steps back. Each step formed a deep imprint on the ground.

Garen pulled back his fists and stood.

"Go." The flush in Garen’s face was gone in a moment, and he walked towards Andrela and Nightmare.

"Then he…?" Nightmare looked at Palosa in confusion.

But Andrela tugged at his clothes, and said no more. The three of them took the two key-shaped black stone pieces, and gave them to Dale Quicksilver and the others who had been waiting for safekeeping. Together, they walked towards another clean spot in the stone forest.

Palosa stood in the same spot quietly, looking at his hands with a melancholy smile.

The truth was, as soon as he used this form, the result had been decided.

"In the end… I was just afraid of the loneliness…" He shook his head and laughed. His body erupted in a series of explosions.

Bang-bang-bang-bang!!

It was as though someone lit firecrackers inside his body. His skin and muscles began turning from round and full to dried-out husks, as though he had stood in the wind for countless years in the blink of an eye.

His previously flushed face rapidly began to dry out at a visible rate, like thousand-year-old tree bark. His tall body also shrunk quickly, his whole person morphing from a powerful warrior into an ancient mummy in a moment.

He leaned onto a broken statue slowly, his gaze going across the gray mist, as though he saw himself in his most glorious days.

Suddenly, Sylphalan’s mad face appeared in front of his eyes.

He paused for a moment, and understood.

"So I had lost, all the way back then…"

A light breeze blew past, and there was no longer anybody by the stone statue. Only a heap of clothes, falling onto a mound of white sand.

　　　　********************

On the edge of the largest stone statue in the Southern Territory.

There were two figures like the Central Area’s stone statues in the North Territory. The ruins could both be opened by keys, and once the entrance was open, naturally everyone could go in. But only those with keys truly had the right to use the Black Smoke Pot.

The fog dissipated, and time passed.

The fog gradually changed from grey to black, and then from black to grey-white, and finally from grey-white to completely white.

Garen sat cross-legged in the middle of the forest of stone statues, his eyes closed. There was a vertical gash on his chin where he was hit by Palosa’s final explosion.

The Divine Statue Technique’s natural healing powers quickly closed up and healed the wound, leaving only a thin red line.

After merging his three personas into one, every move of Palosa’s was equal to unleashing a secret technique. Before he knew it, he had sustained a certain number of internal wounds. The Divine Statue Technique was crazy enough to be called a legendary divine technique, but even after he perfected it, Palosa could still harm him. Compared to his condition when he was fine after taking Palosa head-on, this was as different as heaven and earth!

"Too bad… I’ll have one less opponent in this world…" At Garen’s level, there were far too few people who could really catch his eye. And this one trip to Smoke Island, cost them so many elite martial fighters…

Suddenly, he heard footsteps and voices from deep within the mist.

Garen opened his eyes slowly, and saw Nightmare and Andrela bringing along Dale Quicksilver, Miss Si Lan and co. White Eagle was there too, looking unusually unkempt. The group also brought with them an unconscious boy and girl.

"Found them?" Garen stood up.

"Your injuries are fine now?" Nightmare looked intrigued to see Garen stand up. Getting closer, he tapped Garen’s chest with his scallion-like fingers. "You were breathtakingly fierce just now, do you wanna play a game with Big Sister here? ~~I just love you fierce types~~"

Garen was exasperated as he watched Andrela drag Nightmare away. Even now, it was hard for him to get used to Nightmare’s fetishes sometimes.

"Alright, stop fooling around. How much more time until we open the ruins?"

Dale Quicksilver looked at his watch, "Twenty more minutes."

"Then do you want to come with us?" Garen glanced at Dale Quicksilver, Si Lan and co.

Quicksilver shook his head. "Sorry, my daughter, White Eagle and the others need to rest properly. And the poison in my body… is a little complicated…"

"I wasn’t careful enough," Garen said apologetically. "Even though you warned me."

"It’s alright, luckily I’ve encountered this poison before, so it’s not too bad." Dale Quicksilver smiled openly. "Next, if you guys want to obtain the right to use the Black Smoke Pot, you will have to face the Northern Territory’s Immortal Palace. With our level of power, we’ll only become your burdens if we get involved. So it’s best for us to stay away."

Garen understood that he was right, and so he nodded.

"If you need any help, you can come find our White Cloud Gate."

"Much thanks!" Dale Quicksilver nodded solemnly.

Then it was White Eagle, and the appraisal expert Yoke, who each came up to thank him.

Miss Si Lan took one step forward, and actually blushed for once.

"Thank you for saving me… uhm… your body is really nice..." She said that before realizing what it was she said, and ran off in a hurry. It was a far cry from her usual cool and collected demeanour.

"Your body is really nice~~" Nightmare repeated in a strange voice. "She’s fallen for you, y’know~~"

Garen was utterly speechless. Looking at his naked upper body, he had no idea what kind of expression he should wear.

After bidding them farewell, Detective Dale and his group gradually disappeared into the fog, until their footsteps vanished completely.

"Let’s begin."

Taking a deep breath, the three of them stood in front of the stone statue in a triangular formation, in order to respond quickly to threats from all sides.

Garen took a black stone key from his pocket, and inserted it into a small keyhole on the statue’s abdomen. It turned easily.

There was clattering of gears from inside the statue, and the noise grew steadily louder into a crescendo. From inside the statue, it quickly spread to the ground underneath its feet.

For a moment, it was as though the whole forest of stone statues had erupted into a cacophony of clattering.

Brrr…

Suddenly, the entire south end of the island started to sway gently, light tremors rippling through the earth’s surface.

Garen, Nightmare and Andrela watched the black stone statue quietly. It was s black statue of a human who had one hand raised and the other on the ground, which shook for a while and then fell still.

"The Southern Territory’s key has been activated, now it’s up to the Northern Territory," Andreal said softly. "There’s no mistaking the time. It has to be when the moon is full, but not necessarily at night. It’s late in the afternoon now, almost evening, so we should be able to see the moon outside."

Garen nodded.

As soon as they finished speaking, some more intense tremors came from behind them without warning.

The ground in front of them slowly split apart to reveal a black underground tunnel. The tunnel was square and made of black stone, with many scars and dents on the walls inside. There were even bones scattered on the floor.

As soon as it opened, a stench of rot rushed out from within.

All three of them maintained their expressions. After retrieving the key, Garen glanced at the underground tunnel.

"This is the final battle, where only one will emerge the victor. Do you two still want to go in?"

Nightmare took a step back. "I haven’t lived enough, and it’s not my wish to fight Sylphalan to the death. My only enemy is Flamingo, this has gone beyond my safety parameters." They pouted. "Faced with monsters like you guys, elite fighters just one level lower can’t do much anymore. I’d rather not join the party."

Andrela gripped his sword hilt tightly.

"I’m with you. I’m here to transcend my limits anyway, so I can’t back out halfway."

"Have you truly decided?" Garen looked at him calmly.

Pom!

Nightmare caught Andrela, who had passed out.

"He’s decided, he’s not going. We’ll go back first and wait for you, have fun." She smiled brightly and waved Garen good-bye. And then Nightmare picked Andrela up and ran straight away, vanishing into the thick fog before long.

Garen’s eye twitched a few times, and he was rendered speechless.

Then he turned around to look at the pitch black corridor in front of him.

The tremors had finally stopped. The island was silent for a moment, and then suddenly gave a huge jolt.

Boom!!!

Waves of fog started to roil, gathering in between the north and south, forming a large thin ring of white clouds.

All the smoke and fog above Smoke Island disappeared in a second, revealing the clear evening sky.

Through the cloud ring, rays of twilight red sun shone past the stone forest to land on Garen’s body.

He looked up in the direction of the area between north and south, to see an enormous black statue of a person standing there.

The statue had one hand pointed towards the sky and the other touching the earth. There was a small smile on its lips. But most surprising was how there was a gap between the top of its forehead and its hair, just like the viewing platform on top of the Statue of Liberty.

The stone statue, standing at several thousand meters tall, was like a huge miracle that had withstood the test of time, standing proudly in the exact centre of the entire Smoke Island.

Garen touched the book pendant hanging in front of his chest, and stared at the middle of the statue’s head. Vaguely, he could see a tall figure standing there.

Without any doubt whatsoever, Garen just knew, that was Sylphalan.

He pinched his pendant, and jumped into the tunnel.

Chapter 225: Final Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Clang.. Clang… clang…

The chiming of a clock sounded slowly, coming from somewhere unknown.

Garen dashed down the pitch-black corridor. The path in front of him was retreating rapidly, and the bones on the ground had been crushed underfoot. As he turned a corner, some of the powdered ashes was wiped off his clothes.

He didn’t pause at all, following the uphill-slanting tunnel as he advanced.

Smack.

Leather boots stopped in their tracks, Nightmare glanced back while supporting Andrela.

In the dim evening sunlight, it was as though the huge stone statue had been plated in a layer of red-gold light.

The heavy clanging of a clock came from the top of the stone statue.

"How majestic," Nightmare murmured. "Garen, don’t you die now…"

By the beach, Weisman’s general with the black chest hair was waiting for the rapidly-approaching military ship. He turned back at the same time as Demon Hunter Elysha, to look at the black humanoid statue towering over the island.

There were only about a dozen Demon Hunter left, and there weren’t that many Weisman soldiers left either.

"It’s the final competition… To think that the twilight bells have already sounded… Truly a battle to look forward to." The general’s gaze was full of thoughts. "Too bad… Those two idiots will never hear it again. I told them living like they did was a surefire to not live long, but no one listened."

Elysha touched a scar that had remained on her face, a wound she had gotten in the mixed brawl.

"The Glorious Chan is dead, too. Aren’t you sad at all, General Milo?"

"Sad? It’s good he died, now my family is the sole dominating force. Once I get back, I’ll swallow two other clans! Hehe!!" The general with the black chest hair cheered up instantly. Suddenly, he saw the army ship approaching.

"Hey!!"

He rushed over and waved, yelling loudly.

"I’m here!! Cute little Sally!!"

************

Northern Territory.

Amidst the pile of bloody bodies, the God of Spear Mare helped up the King of the North Pole.

"Big doofus, you okay?" He slapped the King of the North Pole twice, hard.

The latter opened his eyes slowly.

"Not yet dead…"

"So this what makes a main force, your skin sure is thick." Mare sighed. When they had teamed up against the Immortal Palace’s Sylphalan earlier, this King of the North Pole was the quickest to jump into the fray, and naturally was injured the most as well.

But as expected of the man known as the Polar Bear, his body was so strong it didn’t seem human. He took four direct hits from Sylphalan, and could actually still talk normally.

Just then, the distant clock chimes reached them from above.

"It’s the twilight bells, the last battle has begun. Wanna go look?" Mare looked up at the top of the huge stone statue.

"I can’t… That guy is basically a monster, if I go I’ll just be asking for a quick death," The King of the North King snorted, and replied weakly.

"It’s alright, there’s another monster over in the Southern Territory. We shouldn’t even think of the Black Smoke Pot anymore, but no matter what we can’t let the Immortal Palace get away with the spoils," Mare said quietly.

"It’s alright… Hmph, no one who got hit by my Three-day Arctic Needles can live past three days!" The King of the North Pole laughed coldly.

"No one from the Immortal Palace is normal," Mare emphasized."

"Ugh… Fine, but I guarantee they definitely don’t have the strength to bother us right now. Why else would the two of us still be standing here safely?" The King of the North Pole said unhappily. "I advise you to just stay here obediently and wait for their reinforcements to fetch us. You’ll just waste your energy struggling blindly."

Mare shook his head.

"I have a reason I must go…"

"Then it’s up to you." The King of the North Pole snorted again twice, and sat in a corner alone. He began to rest, and checked his injuries. "Alright, your wife is still okay, right? If you lost your pathetic little life… I’ve been watching your wife for a long time, you know that. Don’t blame me later for not considering our friendship."

Mare was appalled.

"I say, it’s one thing for you not to help. But who takes advantage like that?"

"Either way I don’t care, you just go ahead. Don’t forget to make a sound before you die, I’ll go get your wife immediately." The King of the North Pole was too lazy to bother with him.

Mare applied some medicine to the wound on his shoulder, and tied a few rounds around it with the bandages he had prepared to compress the muscles and close the wound. His brow was already covered in sweat. Seeing the King of the North Pole resting with his eyes closed in a corner by himself, he shook his head speechlessly. Turning around quietly, he jumped into the pitch-black underground tunnel, disappearing into the darkness quickly.

The King of the North Pole waited for a moment. When there was no more sound, he opened his eyes.

"You actually went. Haih! I say, have you really gotten tired of living?" He turned around to glance at the direction of the stone forest, where he vaguely heard noises approaching. After a moment’s hesitation, he clenched his teeth.

"Gah! You suicidal maniac! You’ll be the death of me!"

He also jumped into the pitch-blank tunnel, sinking into the darkness.

************

Flamingo leaned on the stone statue, looking at the dried-up old man dressed all in black in front of him quietly.

"That guy ran off?"

The old man nodded. "First I got hit by the Three-day Arctic Needle, and then that guy succeeded in landing a sneak attack on me. But he was pierced by Sylphalan’s sword, too, so his injuries shouldn’t be any lighter than mine." He bent his back slightly. There was a gory knife wound on his abdomen, and it kept dripping blood.

Flamingo raised his head to look at the top of the giant black statue.

"Sylphalan went up already. That guy should still be hiding, waiting for his chance. I plan on going back now, what do you want to do?"

The old man was mildly surprised. "You’re not going to help?"

Flamingo shook his head.

"No, and there’s no need anymore."

Something seemed to occur to the old man, and his expression changed. "I’ll go with you."

Flamingo turned around and walked towards outskirts of the stone forest. There was a puddle of red-black blood on the spot where he had previously stood.

The old man in black hurried to follow him.

　　************

On top of the stone statue, Sylphalan’s long figure seemed almost inhumanly beautiful. He was holding a long red sword upside-down, quietly watching Garen as the latter rushed up the slope.

Going up the tunnel’s stone steps, Garen gradually slowed his pace, and looked up at Sylphalan, who was standing at the tunnel’s entrance.

This was the man that had been involved with him from the very start. Right now, he was wearing a long silk black robe. It made a striking contrast against his pale white skin.

The strong winds kept blowing past them, sending Sylphalan’s long black hair flying to the left. His black robes also rustled in the wind.

"Garen…"

He raised his right hand in front of him, and splayed open his fingers. A simple book necklance was lying quietly in his palm.

"The Eternal Starry Night, it’s still with you, right?"

Garen steadied his step, pressing the necklace in front of his chest in his hand.

"If I remember correctly, didn’t you take it away from me in the first place?"

"I didn’t take the necklace, but something else…" Sylphalan turned around to leave the tunnel entrance open, walking to the edge of the platform. The maelstrom blew his long, watersilk-like hair into a constant dance.

Garen walked out of the tunnel slowly. The tunnel was built inside the stone statue, slanting upwards to the statue‘s head, and the exit opened up to the platform on top of the head.

On the very top of the huge black stone statue, on the platform in the gap there, Sylphalan and Garen stood about a dozen meters away from each other.

The whole black platform was about a hundred meters wide. It was oval-shaped, and was surrounded by black stone guardrail. Some parts of the rail had already been damaged and fell off. There were minute words and symbols carved everywhere, on the floor, the walls, the ceiling. As though the breath of a whole other civilization was recorded here.

The distant chiming kept coming from above them. It was heavy and ancient, carrying with it waves of faint echoes.

The evening sunlight shone inside, landing by their feet. The whole platform in the gap was lit up, a bright golden-red.

Garen stares at Sylphalan’s back, walking around him to reach the guardrail. He looked down.

Underneath the guardrail, a sea of white clouds formed a white garland, turning around the stone statue slowly in a circle. Underneath the gaps in the ring of clouds, many tiny black dots were boarding a boat by the edge of the island, one after the other. Some ships were leaving, others were drawing near.

A wisp of white cloud floated past Garen. He reached out his hand, and lightly grabbed the vapor.

The cloud vapor actually twirled around his hand and remained there, like a white translucent silk ribbon."

Garen’s fingers were like the petals of a flower freshly bloomed. Spinning it around naturally, softly and delicately, without a hint of hardness. He actually managed to keep the cloud wisps there, unable to escape.

"Northern-style Cloud Capturing Hand."

Garen flicked his finger. Psst!

The white cloud vapor transformed into a strand of white silk, shooting at Sylphalan. Soundlessly.

The white string reached a meter of Sylphalan, and stopped abruptly. It was as though it rammed into an invisible wall. Then it exploded without warning into tiny white shards, fading away.

"I remember that the last time I met you, you were far from this level you are now." There was a strange smile on Sylphalan’s face. "Do you hear the clock chimes above us? Those are the twilight bells, signifying that the first stage of the Black Smoke Pot’s activation."

"The first stage?" Garen looked at him with narrowed eyes, waiting for the rest.

"That’s right, there are two stages to the Black Smoke Pot." Sylphalan put his hand on the guardrail, a glimmer of reminiscence in his eyes. "The last time the Black Smoke Pot activated, I heard the chimes of the twilight bells. As for the second stage, in fact it has already begun. From the moment we entered here, it has begun."

"Oh?"

A layer of platinum slowly formed on the surface of Garen’s skin.

"That is, only one living person can remain here." Sylphalan smiled, carefree, and slowly waved the Sword of the Sprites that he held in hand.

Garen’s right palm made a grab downwards, and absorbed wisps of the white cloud vapor around him.

The strands of white clouds gathered like white thread, gathering under his palm from all direction. Finally, they formed a white cloud ball in the middle of his palm.

"When it comes to martial arts, who on this earth could be stronger than you and me? To think that despite that, the two of us will have to decide on a victor here." He walked towards Sylphalan slowly, each step carrying the majesty of a tiger stalking or dragon’s prowl. It was soundless, traceless, but it was as though the whole stone statue and the floor were trembling.

"This has nothing to do with the Black Smoke Pot. The truth is, we’ve waited very long for this battle." Sylphalan held up his long sword horizontally in front of him, tracing his finger lightly across the blade. The entire blade gradually began to glow a blood-like red.

He tossed the blade lightly, and a strand of red thread floated off of it slowly, severing the guardrail on the right without so much as a sound.

"Let’s start… Right here, let’s end it all."

The Sword of the Sprites slanted diagonally downwards, pointing at the ground.

"Nothing to do with the Black Smoke Pot."

Garen raised his palm suddenly, and pushed forward!!

Baroom!!!!

A clap of dull thunder exploded in the sky.

In the gap on top of the statue, a great deal of cloud vapor erupted abruptly with the red light, forming a halo of red and white that slowly drifted apart.

An unknown air spread from the top of the statue. It was colorless and shapeless, gushing into the sky.

The sky darkened in an instant. Countless dark clouds gathered, growing thicker, growing darker. The whole island began to shake slowly, the pebbles on the ground jumping and trembling. A large amount of smoke wafted out of the crevices in the ground, forming a lot of white vapor, drowning the whole giant stone statue in its midst.

Chapter 226: Final Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On top of the stone statue.

Garen and Sylphalan collided into each other madly.

The palm and the sword met head-on again and again. Each collision sent a large quantity of white vapor and red light flying everywhere. They rain down on the surrounding walls and onto the ground, constantly creating new and uneven holes.

"Divine Statue, East King Hand!!"

A platinum divine statue appeared suddenly behind Garen, and rushed into his body in an instant, the two of them merging into one. Carrying with it an incomparable platinum light, his hand stirred the cloud vapor around them, and his palm grabbed straight for Sylphalan’s head.

Psst!

Sylphalan’s body leaned back, Garen’s clawed fingers brushing just past him. A moment later, a red light lit up from behind him, just like a peacock displaying its plume. The red light then became countless red threads, aiming to pierce Garen.

The red threads shot out from all directions, and for a moment everywhere the eye could see had been surrounded.

"Crimson Moon Shadow." Sylphalan somersaulted away, his fingers pointed at Garen. All the red threads instantly shot towards Garen.

"Ten Thousand Mammoth Trample!!" Garen jolted his arms, and a circle of transparent shockwaves spread around him, blowing away most of the red threads.The few remaining threads pierced his body and made the hissing noise of cutting metal. In the end, all that remained were several white marks.

He leapt across to Sylphalan again, the platinum aura completely gathered onto his body, without any wastage whatsoever.

With his current condition, if the opponent was anyone but Sylphalan, all they would see would be his shadow. The seemingly overwhelming difference in power could have struck fear in their hearts.

This was the highest level of this world’s martial arts, when the aura and the human body merged into one. People called it King of the Century!

Similarly, Sylphalan was also covered in black light now, like a sun during the eclipse. His aura stuck close to his body, the two becoming one.

As the two fought madly, the stone statue also began to shake intensely. Each meeting between the two of them was like a bomb explosion.

Boooooom!!!

Inside the entrance to the tunnel, a thin black shadow was quietly making his way to the stone statue’s peak.

"Go on, keep fighting… Hehe, when the two of you have beaten each other, be it the Black Smoke Pot or the Eternal Starry Night, all of it will be mine!" He couldn’t help but laugh in his deep voice.

The intense tremors kept coming from the tunnel’s stone walls, growing stronger and heavier.

"The opponent this time is far stronger than last time. Sylphalan, your time has finally come." The black shadow reached out his hand to touch the stone wall, laughing coldly. Suddenly, he sensed something amiss.

"Wait, why are the tremors growing stronger?!"

He stopped in his tracks, and turned his head to look. Unbelievably, there was a hint of red firelight in the pitch-black tunnel.

"That is… a bomb!!???" His eyes widened abruptly. "No… No!!! Sylphalan, you madman!!!!" He started screeching madly, his whole body rushing towards the tunnel ahead of him.

　*************

The God of Spear Mare stood quietly in front of the tunnel, looking at the part of the tunnel that had collapsed after the explosives went off. For a moment there, he didn’t know if he should advance or retreat.

"Go back."

The King of the North Pole walked out from behind him.

"Sylphalan is a madman. In order to make sure no one disturbed this final battle, he went ahead and bombed up the whole tunnel."

Mare gripped his fist tightly. Wordlessly, he turned around and walked away.

"Where are you going?" The King of the North Pole looked at him, confused.

"..." Mare did not reply. He just walked faster, disappearing down the tunnel in the direction he had come.

　*************

On the beach

Andrela sat cross-legged on the ground, his long sword stuck in the sand beside him. He was looking up blankly, staring at the dark and dull sky.

Black flower petals fell slowly from the sky, dancing and twirling, sprinkling his sword, his clothes, even his face.

A snow of black flower petals had descended on the entire island.

"What… is this?"

Andrela reached his hand out to pinch one of the petals, but it disintegrated into powder in his hand.

Nightmare was standing right beside him, and caught a petal lightly, trying to keep it intact.

"I don’t know, but I got a bad feeling about this. Let’s get away from here as soon as possible."

"Wait for Garen to return, then we can go together." Andrela was unmoved.

Pom!!

Nightmare lifted up the unconscious Andrela.

"You won’t listen even if I tell you. Why don’t you think of what kind of level Garen has reached. Even if he survives, you might not."

She took one last look at the red and white cloud vapor erupting constantly from the top of the statue.

"Garen, don’t die."

　***************

The island shook vigorously, and black snow fell from the sky.

The petal snow completely engulfed the entire Smoke Island.

Baroom!!

A large flurry of red flames erupted from the stone statue’s waist area. At the same time, a large of black fog sprayed out.

The whole giant stone statue began to tilt slowly. The upper half began to slant gradually, breaking apart, and sliding towards the island.

At the same time, there was the rumble of thunder in the sky, as though weeping for the destruction of the giant stone statue.

On the stone statue’s peak.

Garen and Sylphalan were face to face, the red threads and white clouds between the two of them morphing into two blurry shadows. Countless red threads and white shadows knocked into each other, turning into countless red and white shards, spraying and scattering to the sides.

The statue’s whole head also began to tilt and shake vigorously.

The platform in the gap slowly tilted to the right.

Boom!

Garen’s back crashed into a portion of the wall, and completely decimated that part of the wall with a crash. It left a huge hole, allowing them to see the roiling black sky outside.

"Divine Statue Return!!" His eyes glared suddenly, his whole body engorging explosively. His muscles expanded rapidly, and many platinum lines appeared on his body, forming several strange and distorted natural images and symbols.

"Sylphalan! Die!!" he roared, his hair standing on end. His palm expanded until they were like plantain fans, attacking Sylphalan from both sides. It was like a huge platinum giant grabbing a dwarf with both his hands.

The soundwaves from the loud roar complemented the pulsing of all the muscles in his body, creating a strange but intense tremor that made his body increase even further. In the end, he had enlarged until he was two and a half meters.

Before the move hit him, Sylphalan already felt sharp winds attacking him like knives, cutting into the skin on his face.

Both his ears felt the two huge pressure coming on both sides at the same time, as though two behemoths were charging at once, and he was temporarily dazed. This power was more than twice as strong as Garen had been just now.

Sylphalan didn’t retreat. Instead, he advanced, a small calm smile on his lips.

Creak…

With that tiny sound, countless black veins started surfacing on the skin of his face, like countless insects and worms. All of them gathered to the center of his brow, forming an eye-shaped lump.

He reached out his hand and swept the blade of his sword. In an instant, there was a flash of red light.

"Sovereign Sword!"

He thrust his sword at Garen’s face, seemingly unaware of Garen’s palms coming from both sides.

The Sword of the Sprites was as blinding as the setting sun, instantly radiating an intense and burning hot light.

Clang!!

The chime of the clock went long and far.

Garen’s hands hit nothing but air, as did Sylphalan’s sword rays. Both of them switched positions.

In a split second, it was as though all sound had ceased. There was only the long lament of the ancient clock.

Another chime rang out.

Clang!!

Garen’s hands grabbed the long red sword, the white vapor and red threads of light tangling up and colliding with each other. The whole space was covered with shaved black stone shards. The black light around Sylphalan’s body strengthened, and he held the sword with both hands.

The last chime of the clock.

Clang!!!

Sylphalan gave up on the sword and used his hands instead, pointing one finger at Garen’s chest. The tip of that finger sank deep into Garen’s skin. Garen couldn’t avoid it in time, and stared down at his own chest.

In that moment, both of them froze completely.

Barrooom!!!!

The head of the stone statue exploded in a ball of red flame.

The ground underneath the platform was torn apart by the intense explosion, and countless black shards flew out from the flames as charred shrapnel. Both of them were entirely engulfed.

The whole top half of the giant statue collapsed, and smashed onto the island floor, creating a splash of smoke and ash in its wake.

Boom!!!

Where the statue fell, a pillar of black smoke rose into the sky. It blew the infinite black petal rain in all directions, growing thicker as it went.

*******************

Ground Zero1

Garen gripped Sylphalan’s arm tightly. He was beginning to vomit blood-- dark red, almost coagulated chunks.

The two stood facing each other. Sylphalan’s whole right arm had gone through Garen’s chest, protruding from his back.

As for Sylphalan himself, blood-colored cracks had formed along his right arm and shoulder. Like the hairline cracks on a piece of porcelain that would fall apart with the slightest touch.

Oddly, the cracks were still spreading towards his head.

Blood started to ooze slowly out of Sylphalan’s body, but it was barely visible on the black coat. The only proof of his injuries was the blood dripping down his leg.

Barroom!!

There was the rumble of thunder in the sky.

The two of them were currently standing on the forehead of the giant statue. Beneath them was a steep cliff, that opened up to a valley of bright red, blinding hot lava ten thousand feet below.

A large body of lava was spraying and splashing. Worse of all, it was rising, slowly but determinedly.

The place the stone statue had fallen turned out to be the mouth of a huge volcano. The whole volcano mouth was round and over a thousand meters in diameter, forming a giant cylindrical abyss.

Wafts of thick black smoke sprayed out of this exit, scattering volcano ash that looked like black petals. They floated down and scattered everywhere.

The top half of the giant stone statue had fallen beside the mouth of the volcano, and its head was suspended in the middle. Heatwave after heatwave rose and roasted it.

The red-hot light had dyed the entire stone statue completely red. Even the two people standing on it had become scarlet.

"Divine Statue… Return!!" Garen roared abruptly, all the platinum aura around his body exploding away. It became a platinum round disc that spun in the air above his head. This huge attack stampeded towards Sylphalan viciously.

"Omniscient Eye!!!" Sylphalan also roared, the lump on his brow splitting open. A ray of sharp yet shapeless telekinesis shot out like a blade, ramming towards the platinum attack.

Boom!!

The two shapeless powers collided. Sylphalan flew back, falling into the mouth of the volcano. His right hand grabbed the side of the stone statue, but somehow, his hand was suddenly suspended in mid-air before he pulled it back.

He suddenly looked slightly lost and calm, as though his thoughts had flown off into the distance somewhere

Smack!

Garen’s hand grabbed his right hand, and kept him hanging off the cliff.

Some small pebbles tumbled off the edge and fell into the red-hot lava, melting into nothing in an instant.

"Do you really want to die that badly?" Garen looked at Sylphalan with clenched teeth.

"Don’t you think… the scaret flames… are really pretty?" Sylphalan smiled. For some reasom, his smile looked slightly lost.

Woo…

All of a sudden, a piercing cry came from the clouds in the sky.

Garen looked up. It was the sound of an airplane gliding through the air.

Smack!

Suddenly, Sylphalan broke free of his grip. Lying horizontally, he fell quietly into the abyss. His coat beat about in the wind, making him look a black swallow that had fallen into a sea of red.

"What a beautiful scarlet…" he murmured, looking at the red light on his body. And then he looked at Garen, who was staring at him with widened eyes from the cliffside.

In that moment, Garen’s face overlapped with that handsome, charismatic and confident face from the past.

"Big brother… To think, I could never walk out of your shadow, even until the very end…"

Soundlessly, Sylphalan fell quietly into the lava. He was engulfed completely, leaving not a single trace, just like the rocks that had fallen before him.

"You little…!!!" Garen gripped his fists tightly, his teeth clenching together with a loud clack. All the muscles in his body were trembling.

His hand touched the right side of his neck. The bloody red gash there was clear as day, and it had been inflicted with ease by that Omniscient Eye just now. If Sylphalan had used that move from the start…

"A victory like this… You just handed it to me!!???" Garen felt an unprecedented sense of shame and unhappiness. This was the final battle he had looked forward to all this time, and yet his opponent just threw the match?

Woo!!!

A piercing wail came from the sky.

In that moment, an intense sense of danger rose in his heart.

"You want me to die?!!!"

His whole body was expanding vigorously, the platinum aura surrounding his body expanding madly in all directions.

In between his mad howling, Garen raised his fists and swung them at the sky. Behind him, a huge platinum statue burst into form, and raused its fists at the same time, swinging them through the air.

A soundless bolt of lightning. A black mushroom cloud rose from the ground, the intense radiation spreading in all directions with abandon.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

Lit. the place [they] fell

Chapter 227: Reincarnate 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Radiation blanketed every inch of the sky, raining in from all directions.

After the explosion settled, the aftershock came seconds later. An impossibly bright flash blinded everyone within the proximity.

Most had already escaped to their boats just outside the Smoke Island. Those who were looking at the Smoke Island were blinded by the light and were no longer see anything but darkness afterwards.

On a white boat.

The King of Nightmares and Andrela were standing quietly at the edge of the ship as they looked at the mushroom cloud rising in the distance. Both of them had a rather ugly expression on their faces.

Although the both of them had avoided being blinded by the explosion with their inhuman reactions, it was not because of this that they bore the ugly expressions in their faces.

Andrela gripped the handrail with both of his hands, so tightly that his fingerprints were faintly imprinted onto the metal.

"It’s a nuclear bomb… It’s definitely the people from Weisman!!"

"That was a small one, I heard that their experiment had succeeded not long ago, but I hadn’t expected it to be put to the test this soon…" The King of Nightmares stared at the shockwave travelling from the mushroom cloud and said. "Their motive wasn’t to kill the people on the island. They were trying to the eruption of the giant volcano on Smoke Island!"

Boom!!

The boats out at sea were like paper boats following shockwave, rocking about, risking capsize at any minute.

Navy personnel started to stabilize the boats and ignite the engine to accumulate distance from the island.

The mushroom cloud refused to dissipate, sending a column of black smoke soaring into the sky.

Boom!!

It was another vibrating roar. Red halation emerged from the sky above Smoke Island.

The halation spread out and rained down in all directions. To shock, what fell was in fact red and black lava!

lava rained down everywhere, large amounts of viscous liquid swiftly flooded the whole island, turning the island fire red.

Blankets of black volcanic ash spread out and covered the sky, spreading out thousands kilometers into the horizon.

The few boats that were too close to the island were overturned by a rogue wave. Still others were caught in the rain of lava, and were either broken in half or engulfed in flames.

The boat that carried the King of Nightmares and Andrela was hit by a swathe of lava in the middle, and broke in two.

The sound of screams were completely drowned in the seemingly ceaseless roar of the eruption.

Light from the sun in the sky was completely snuffed out by the thick smoke and volcanic ash. It was impossible to tell between night and day.

The blue surface of the sea was completely covered with volcanic ash and black debris, resembling a blue handkerchief littered and stained with blank ink.

Boats engulfed in flame were small red dots floating on the sea, glowing faint red embers of fire.

The King of Nightmares and Andrela, each with a person on their backs, immediately swam away from the range of destruction of the volcano.

Even so, the toxic smoke emitting from volcano kept invading their lungs. They all knew in their hearts that no matter how strong Garen was, he might not have survived such a terrifying natural disaster.

Majority of the experts were caught in the disaster, unable to escape in time. Only one in ten had managed to got out of range. Weisman’s objective had finally been achieved.

They managed to kill most of the high level masters from all over the world. It was an ideal condition to use the latest technology they had on hand.

In but a fraction of a second, the world had incorrigibly changed.

****************

Black...

Everything in front of him was pitch black…

The last memory Garen had was of him releasing all of his anger, sending his fist at the bomb in the sky.

He knew the objective of the enemy was to ignite the volcano.

Smoke Island was practically the world’s largest volcano, as most of the volcano’s structure was under the ocean. Its volume was shockingly immense. The entire Smoke Island was actually the volcano’s crater, and was of the incessant mist on the island. This was a sign that it had been on the cusp of an eruption.

As the gigantic volcano erupted, the small, neighbouring countries were affected. The air pollution caused by it would severely alter the structure of the planet.

Garen thought that Weisman had underestimated the volcano’s destructive power and scale, and had decided to act in such a reckless manner.

However, none of this mattered anymore. What’s important now was the question of his current situation.

He wanted to move his body, but realized that he no longer had the concept of limbs. It was as if his body was in a deep sleep, and his brain was not fully awake and thrown into chaos.

His surrounding was pitch black; there was nothing to see.

In his last moments when his body was disintegrated, he could still feel the immense pain just from recalling this fresh memory. He clearly remembered his body completely melted by the intense heat.

In the instant the volcano erupted, it felt like the earth was in rage, and Smoke Island, which was the crater, unleashed a limitless amount of white and gold magma. The thousand-degree lava had completely melted him instantly.

In actuality, he had a feeling that he wouldn’t be able to escape the moment he saw the bomb.

If it was just an ordinary, powerful bomb, he had no reason to be afraid as he was confident in his resistance to heat. As long as it wasn’t core temperature, the most he would be affected by was the debris and shockwave from the explosion.

However, it wasn’t just any bomb, it was a nuclear bomb. Although it hadn’t been fully developed yet, it was still a nuclear bomb. Furthermore, the issue was not this but that Smoke Island was a giant volcano on the verge of eruption.

The nuclear bomb was nothing but a catalyst.

The eruption of the volcano was the one that did him in.

He was defenseless against the instantaneous high temperature impact and was completely engulfed in it.

"Never in my dreams had I thought of such an ending."

Garen recalled silently in the dark. Sylphalan and he himself were the strongest people in that world.

If Sylphalan had not sought death at the last second and kept on fighting, both of them might have ended in a draw. Practically, with his Divine Statue Technique, immense aura, and his abundant essence were already at an appalling level.

Sylphalan was no different. He had a terrifying explosive force and lethal attacks. Even Garen had a tough time against him. The only thing he lacked against him was his recovery.

Everything was decided the moment Sylphalan gave in to Garen. In a battle between two equals, the result was obvious the moment one party gave in to the other.

Garen understood everything in the darkness.

The world would no longer be a world revolving martial arts any longer. The realm of his martial art was at the peak and there was no room for any more improvements.

The next world should be similar to Earth, the firearm era. The level of his martial arts could only be describe as perfection.

It was pure darkness in all directions.

"Death may be the ending for some people. Clearly that’s not the case for me."

He was alone in the dark. He was a shapeless object without the concept of a body.

Garen didn’t know how long he had been floating in the darkness.

A day… two days…

A year… Two years…

He didn’t know how long he had been there. As time passed, he counted up to millions and there was still nothing happening.

Gradually, he was back to the beginning of transmigration and his thinking gradually stalled as he travelled through the universe.

After some time, suddenly he passed by some sort of mist, and saw a ray of light at the bottom.

Far away in the darkness, a dark blue nebula slowly appeared, and he got closer and closer and the nebula became bigger and bigger.

Within this nebula laid a planet painted in dark blue. Suddenly, innumerable images flashed past his mind, like a million rays of light shining in his direction.

Garen saw everything clearly as he looked at the images. It was a series of events that happened on the planet, the changes it had been through.

It was as if a movie was playing right in front of his eyes.

He Suddenly felt his body burning up.

He looked down and saw that a quaint book-like pendant was floating beside his body. It was the Eternal Starry Night Pendant that he had been wearing.

Unfortunately this necklace, which effect was unknown, was already lined with innumberable crack lines. The once gleaming surface had become dull, as if it was about to disappear.

A familiar faint red symbol appeared just below Garen’s vision.

‘Unknown force has been fully depleted… the travel is about to stop. Do you want to enter the nearest planet?’

Garen was stunned. The Eternal Starry Night Pendant was the source of his travel through the universe.

He immediately answered with swift reaction.

"Yes!"

Suddenly, his talent and abilities were transferred, and he felt his body guided by numerous thin red beams. He was then pulled by the beams to the planet at an incredible pace. A few flash and jumps, but he was nowhere closer to the planet.

His target planet was the one that he had glimpsed earlier.

The planet got bigger and clearer with each second. As Garen turned his head around and looked back, a similar blue planet had already became a small dot and blended itself in with the other stars in the sky.

"I will return…"

"Pew!! The speed had increased even further.

He felt a jolt in his brain and completely lost consciousness. The Eternal Starry Night Pendant let out a and was broken into millions of pieces as it scattered among the universe.

************

Night.

There was a young man, probably in his early twenties, busy writing something in a brightly lit room.

He was sitting at the copper red study desk, holding onto a white quill, occasionally dipping it inside black ink and writing something onto the paper after giving some thought.

The faint yellow light radiated by the candle reflected brightly off his hair onto his fair and handsome face.

‘Sun Calendar. Year 3567, twentieth of the fourth month. I had once met Aquarius from Walton. Oh my goodness! This is the third time in my life that I have been burnt by her beauty. She is too beautiful… So beautiful that she is as pure as a lily and as white as a moon. As beautiful as… As beautiful as…" The youngster stopped writing and started to think carefully of his next praise.

"Ah!~~~~" He suddenly released a long sigh as he pressed his chest with one hand. "Oh the beautiful Aquarius, I shall be your fated prince!!"

Ugh…

A faint footsteps could be heard just outside the door.

"Little Giles! You’re eavesdropping on me writing my poem again!! Stand still!!" The youngster threw his pen down and rushed outside the door. It was completely dark outside as he saw a small human figure rushing down to the first floor as he disappeared into the darkness.

Chapter 228: Reincarnate 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The young man gently closed the door and went back to his study desk.

He knew that his reputation wasn’t good in his household, but that wouldn’t stop him from achieving his dream.

He had truly fallen head over heels for Miss Aquarius since the day he met her. He would give anything! Even his life!

As he thought of this, he suddenly felt that he was possessed by an ancient poet and had instantly entered the realm of a great poet who would sacrifice his body for love. He was drunk on the feeling of inspiration.

"I wonder what happened with the document Miss Aquarius wanted me to take from her father." He suddenly recalled with bliss. Miss Aquarius would definitely be extremely moved when she saw the tremendous effort that he had invested in her. She would eventually fall in love with him deeply, throw everything behind, leave this world together and become the perfect romantic love story.

Knock knock.

Someone had gently knocked onto the door.

"Cia, have you slept?" A clear female voice came through the door.

"Big Sister Sofea, is that you? Please come in, the door isn’t locked." The young Cia immediately stood up with a hint of happiness on his face.

The door clicked and was pushed open.

A tall beautiful girl came into the room.

"How many times do I have to tell you! Call me big sister Hathaway!" The girl had golden hair tied in a ponytail. Her skin was fair, face as sharp as knife and she gave off a British, glamorous vibe.

"Okay…. Big Sister Hathaway." Cia nodded his head. "Oh right, Why are you here at such a late hour? Do you need anything from me?"

The girl walked a full circle of the room and eventually set her gaze onto the white paper on the study desk. "Where’s the Astronomical Edict I gave you last time?"

Cia was stunned and shook his head as he smiled innocently. "What Astronomical Edict? What are you talking about big sister? When did I ever taken anything from you?"

Hathaway squinted her eyes and stared at her most beloved younger cousin.

"Brother, I won’t say a word if you use the Astronomical Edict for yourself. However, if someone had egged you on..."

She had risked her life for the royal family to obtain two Astronomical Edicts. This was the culmination of 10 years of hard work. She had been taking care of Cia, the only male child in the whole household, since young, and he had been loved by many since young.

She didn’t mind giving her one Astronomical Edict. However, if it was someone who had instigated it…

"No one instigated me." Cia kept shaking his head. His reaction was an immediate denial. "I didn’t take something called the Astronomical Edict! Big sister you have to believe me!"

Hathaway was quiet for a moment and reached out her hand to caress Cia’s hair.

"Whatever. I don’t get to use that thing anyway. Please don’t do it anymore."

"I really didn’t take it!" Cia was still denying it.

He didn’t really understand what the Astronomical Edict represented and of how important that item was. To her cousin , that item was her reward and proof of her lifetime of hardwork. It was considered an ultimate pardon, an escape no matter how serious the crime was.

"Also, you lost two manors during your gambling session, didn’t you?" Hathaway changed the topic. "Do you know how valuable those two manors were!? This is especially so for the manor in Varian. You have lost them just like that."

"I will win them back sooner or later!" Cia answered hatefully and immediately feared his cousin the moment he saw his cousin’s angry face.

When he was ten years old, he was bitten by a strange poisonous snake. It was Big Sister Hathaway who saved him with a mysterious antidote from an unknown source. When Hathaway found out that her cousin was poisoned, she disappeared for a day or two without leaving word behind. The ever so healthy and resilient girl came back with a severely injured body, her strength having decreased tremendously. She resigned from the Royal Knights and enrolled into the Royal Department to become a Lieutenant.

The Astronomical Edict was actually her reward for her contributions and hard work as a Royal Knight. Now that Cia had taken away one of her Astronomical Edicts, he started to feel bad for her.

"I will make up to you some day, sister…" He replied softly.

Hathaway released all her anger the moment she saw her brother’s ignorance towards his recklessness.

"I don’t want your compensation! You have to understand the danger of gambling!! How much of the family wealth have you lost for these past few years!? You have lost so much of uncle’s fortune! If you keep going down this path, no matter how wealthy your family is, you will definitely lose everything!"

Her voice was getting louder and louder as she felt more and more angry towards him.

"Sis… You have to believe me! I will definitely win back everything!" Cia replied immediately.

"Are you still thinking of gambling!!?" Hathaway couldn’t resist anymore and slapped Cia’s face with all of her might.

Slap!

Both Cia and Hathaway were stunned.

Acacia was the only male child from his family and was pampered by everyone in the household. Even his father Sissas was reluctant to hit him.

And it was the first time Hathaway couldn’t hold herself back and gave him a slap.

At that instant, both of them were rooted.

"So what!! Isn’t it just a piece of Astronomical Edict that I took? How dare you hit me!!??" Cia’s cheek was completely red. He soared his chest and continued. "Let me tell you something Sofea Hathaway! No matter how much I have lost, it is my family’s problem! All these wealth belongs to me in the future. How much I have lost is none of your business!? I have the successor of the Trejons Household! You are nothing but a Royal Family’s Lieutenant. What right do you have to control me!?"

"You!!!" Hathaway was completely furious to the point where she was completely speechless as she pointed at Acacia with her finger.

Never in her dreams could she imagine that the cousin she had pampered for her whole life would say such hurtful words to her.

Sadness, disappointment and rage were bursting and blending in her heart at that moment.

Without any hesitation, Hathaway turned around and left the room and slammed the door.

Acacia was clasping his left face as he gently tapped his cheek.

Hiss…

"It’s so painful!" He took a few steps back and reached out his hand to take a red medicinal oil from the book racks. He applied onto his face, and it was very effective in reducing swelling.

He suddenly recalled that this item was gifted to him from Hathaway.

"I will never use anything she gives me ever again! Never!!" He grabbed the glass bottle containing the red medicinal oil and threw it onto the ground with all his strength.

Splash!

The small bottle shattered into millions of pieces on the ground, the red medicinal oil was spilt across the floor.

"Even Father has never even hit me before!!" Acacia was walking back and forth in the room in a rage. The sky outside was overcast with the faint rumbling of thunder. It seemed like it was about to rain.

Kacha!!

Suddenly, thunder cracked loudly above his head.

Shocked, he stepped onto the red oil and slipped. He immediately fell backwards and onto the ground.

Thud!!

By chance, the back of his brain landed on a sharp piece of broken glass.

In an instant, his body arched upwards and his eyes rolled, and he gradually stop breathing after a few moments of struggling.

At this very moment, A ray of white light came into the room from the square window.

The white ray, which was in a shape of a butterfly was as big as a fist, passed through the tightly shut window and circled the room in a delicate manner.

It soon noticed Acacia laying still on the floor.

With a click, the white ray disappeared and diffused into Acacia’s forehead.

After a while, Acacia who was laying down on the floor opened his eyes. His vision was a complete blur, as if he just woke up from a long sleep.

He slowly got up from the floor, only to realize that he had been laying in a pile of faint, red-stained wooden flooring with glass shards strewn everywhere. It was very uncomfortable as the glasses were prickling his butt.

He touched the back of his back and noticed that his hair was rather cold, and there was a blood clot as well. The injury had completely healed.

Cia stood up and looked around his surrounding.

"I guess… I’m in a different location now…"

He took a deep breath and gently gripped his fist and what he sensed was a weakness that he had never felt before.

He felt chills all over his body, which was most probably due to him laying on the floor for a long period of time.

Ah chiu!

He couldn’t help himself but to sneeze. As he sneezed, the snot started dripping out from his nose.

"Who am I…?" He kept griping his fists tightly and released it afterwards.

"I am Acacia… No! .. I am Garen Lombard!!"

His vision started to clear up and and he started to feel an anger that he had never experienced before.

Knock knock knock.

"Master,can I come in and clear up the room now?" The female servant asked carefully from outside of the room. She had been waiting outside for a long time. She was probably waiting for her master to cool down before she dared to come in and clean up. She would be scolded by Acacia and her salary would be partially deducted if she came in the wrong time.

"Forget about it! You should leave first. I don’t want to see anyone at the moment!"

Garen shouted as he copied what Acacia would say from his memory. It was a sentence that was most frequently used by Acacia. Hence, all he needed to do was to follow his words.

It was a language that resembled Portuguese. Garen was slightly familiar with the language’s overall structure from Acacia’s memory.

Afterwards, he started to recollect his disorganized memories in his brain.

Although Acacia’s memories went all the way back to twenty years, most of them was forgotten. However, as it was very difficult to digest everything, he had no choice but to read the main contents of the memory.

This world was similar to the last one, both of which was of primarily western culture. However, this world had barely just entered the steam era and was far behind compared to the previous world in terms of technological advancement.

While this world’s overall structure was ruled under a dictatorship, the country’s property had already started blooming.

This body originally belong to a person called Acacia Trejons. He still had a long surname after that and he was the only successor in the Trejons Household.

This whole planet was separated into two major continents, namely the East Continent and West Continent. There were many island countries in between these two major continents.

The East Continent had hundreds of countries, and the Great Kovetan Kingdom was one of the three strongest countries in this continent.

Kovetan had a total of thirty two districts. This body’s family household had established their presence in some areas of the Lush Forest district which was located in the south of the country.

Among the Trejons Household, there were only five main members in this generation. They were Acacia’s parents, Acacia himself, his cousin Sofea Hathaway and her sister, Danielle Hathaway.

Acacia had never once stepped out of the Lush Green District his entire life.

His household was located in the center, and the surrounding cities were all within his activities’ range.

Chapter 229: Reason 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Looking through Acacia’s life, he realised that he was a gambling addict, a pervert and slow-witted. He didn’t even realize that he was completely exploited by a girl called Aquarius. All his family wealth that was rather important was ‘sold’ to Aquarius in order to get into her good graces.

Garen took a deep breath as he looked at the countless unfortunate encounters of this body. Although looking at Garen from the previous life and his own life on earth, Luo Jing had an above average intelligence; this body was definitely in the lead in terms of idiocy.

"Alright… Let’s look at the current stats."

He concentrated his mind and started to examine his body’s status in detail.

The familiar faint red ability words appeared just below his vision.

‘Strength 0.8, Agility 0.8, Vitality 0.7, Intelligence 0.4, Potential 1872%, Possesses unknown natural endowment.

Secret Technique -- Divine Statue Technique, Ten Thousand Mammoth Battle Skills.

Full recovery in 377 days (1 year).’

Garen furrowed his eyebrows slightly.

"Recovery requires a year? Also, why is this body’s attribution so useless? What does it mean by possessing an unknown natural endowment?"

The Ability remained mute, which was rather obvious considering the memory did not have enough information.

He continued to look at the last symbol.

Naturally, the meaning of this symbol swiftly appeared in his mind.

‘The primary potential has yet to be lost due to an unknown source of protection during the transmigration. Hence, all statuses will slowly recover through the adaptation of the soul.’

"Unknown source? Is that the Eternal Starry Night Pendant?" Garen thought. "The primary potential has yet to be lost. Does that mean I have to learn the secret techniques from scratch if it weren’t for the pendant?"

He recalled that he had depended on himself during his first transmigration. Perhaps there was some electrical energy involved, but that electrical energy was very minor.

Suddenly, he noticed another weird symbol appearing at the end of the his ability pane.

It wasn’t faint red in color but dark red, which had appeared for the very first time.

He focused his attention onto the symbol.

‘Discovered an unknown message. Do you wish to receive it?’

‘Discovered an unknown image message. Do you wish to receive it?’

‘Initiating automatic protection of the memories during transmigration. Begin recording of the unknown image…’

‘An unknown fluctuation in space time has occurred… Energy source has been shattered. The fluctuation has stopped. Playback recorded messages?’

Four messages came into Garen’s memory in an instant.

It was obvious that all of his memories would be disintegrated during his travel in space time without the protection of this ability.

He had a small epiphany, an enlightenment started to swell up from his heart.

The red debris from the bottle had kickstarted his abilities, and he could achieve a strength that was unimaginable in this world as his secret martial techniques had been merged with his energy spirit.

This was also the reason why he could recalled this transmigration instantly. The last time he transmigrated, he could only recall a portion of it.

"What is this recording thing…" Garen suddenly recalled the lights on the planet as he was travelling through the space time.

He opened the window and quickly cleaned up the room. The room reeked with the odour of the medicinal oil, and its stain was virtually un-cleanable.

He had no choice but to open the window to allow some fresh, cold air to enter.

Since there was still a long time before he fully recovered, he took out a chair, sat down and quietly recalled the light he saw during his transmigration.

It was a ray of almighty light of an unknown color. Even as Garen started to recall it, he was still unable to make out the color of the light.

It was like a three dimensional object appearing in a two dimensional space. He was able to instantly understand the two dimensional image, which was voluminous but had no obvious content. It was a feeling so strange that he couldn’t get used to it.

He believed that he could find a way to return to the previous world, or even the one before it, if he could fully understand the nature of this ability.

All in all, he had many concerns that had yet to be solved in two of the previous worlds that he was in.

He laid against the chair and started to sort out his thoughts.

"How was I able to see that light? Why didn’t I see it during my first transmigration, then? Was it an effect of the advancement of my abilities? How was I able to find a habitable planet in such a short amount of time, especially when there were so many planets out there? It felt like I was guided here by something."

He recalled the scene during his transmigration.

It was as if there was a force guiding him to this planet as he flew here at an incredible velocity.

During his first transmigration, he floated in the universe for a very long time, as he passed by countless, inhabitable planet before reaching Garen’s planet.

No matter how he looked at it, it was much faster than before.

He finally set his vision onto the symbol at the end of his abilities pane.

"Looks like I should be able to find some clues on the recorded unknown image message."

‘Do you want to play back the recorded message?’

The symbol asked again.

"Yes."

Garen answered with absolute certainty.

Silently, a huge amount of information gushed into his brain.

Ah…

He lowered his head and gripped it with his hands, as all he could feel was his brain in complete chaos. This came with an incredible headache, where he felt like his brain was about to split into two with an axe, stuffed in between with a large chunk of something, before being sewn back up again.

The light that appeared from the planet instantly appeared in his memories.

The sceneries kept passing by in his brain one after another.

The wars, conflicts and misfortunes.

The succession of political power, the changes of the world and the loss of power.

It was the light of the past. It was the light of history that showed the major historical events of this planet.

He accidentally received this information during his transmigration when he was still light-years away.

An endless stream of information entered Garen’s mind instantly.

The Terraflor Society, Obscuro Society, Totem, Luminarist, the fall of the royal power, the country’s recessions, the changes of the planet…

A myriad of scenarios swiftly appeared in Garen’s mind.

Soon, the images connected together and became a complete structure…

Sun Calendar Year 3570 of the 10th month, there was a major uprising in the east continent.

The Kovitan Empire was the second to fall.

The countless images portrayed just a part of the history.

There were many powerful empires in this world, with the emperors using cold weapons and outdated firepower to rule the world.

However, hidden in the fabric of reality, there was a group called the Luminarist. They hold the power of the totem.

Luminarists, who used white silver to forge their totems, were professional experts with extraordinary abilities. They were the specialised members who could create totems, and was considered a rare talent.The world revolved around the Luminarist, who hid in the fringes of society and held true power and influence. The Luminarists were separated into two sects, each having their own ideals. They were the Seraph Light and Phantom Light Sects respectively.

When the Luminarist moved, the world moved with them.

The Seraph Light, who represented purity, and the Phantom Light, who represented evil were the two separates forces in this world. These two sects had their own respective ideals. The Seraph Light’s ideal was peace whereas the Phantom Light’s ideal was of survival of the fittest. These were the main differences in their leadership. On one hand, one used their strengths for peace, while the other used their strength to further themselves. These were the differences between the sects. These also represented two different political systems: democracy and dictatorship.

The society that represented the Seraph Light was the Terraflor Society.

On the other hand, the society that represented the Phantom Light was the Obscuro Society.

Both sects were standing at the pinnacle of the totem world and had been battling against each other for a long time.

Among them, one who had triggered the change of the world was a young man named Beckstone and his partners. They were the successors of the Terraflor Society, which represented the Seraph Light, and would become the strongest society of the Seraph Light in the future.

Garen finally slightly understood a few key connections after he completely laid out the information structure.

"Simply put, this was the history of how Beckstone and his companions battled and eventually won against the Obscuro Society of the Phantom Light…"

"It’s obvious that this happened in the uprising era, where dictatorship started to fall. However, this body is currently living in the era where dictatorship is still stable, and there were not even one uprising reported thus far. If what I saw was real…"

Suddenly, he recalled the recorded message he had just seen earlier.

At the last sentence of the record: Unknown fluctuation in the space time continuum has occurred…

"Theoretically speaking, the distance between two habitable planets which were from different solar systems should have been light-years apart from one another. If this theory is true, going back into time isn’t impossible…" He speculated.

"If it was really a backward flow in time, then the scenario that I have saw should probably be the future events of the planet."

"This means that when I was lightyears away from this planet, I received an unknown light, and saw the events of this planet. However, as I travelled through lightyears of distance in an instant, I have arrived to this planet’s era where the uprising occurs?"

He managed to clear up his train of thoughts. This was the only logical explanation that that could mould all of the clues together.

"Assuming that this hypothesis is true, the Phantom Light will lose, causing the Obscuro Society to collapse and the world will adopt the capitalist social system. This means that the Seraph Light has obtained victory. Judging from the looks of it, Beckstone is the legendary brave and spirited man, who is also the main character? He’s a person who came at the right moment. Even without him, world would still change, and a second Beckstone would have arrived to take his place. Such was the world’s desire…"

"The most troublesome thing isn’t this at the moment…" Garen frowned. "Based on Acacia’s memories, his father Vanderman is an upper class aristocrat of the Kovitan Empire and he has rather strong influence and authority. Furthermore, he had another identity, which is a Luminarist of the Obscuro Society. He is still an independent Luminarist and hasn’t completely entered the Obscuro Society yet."

"This situation looks dire…" He face was rather gloomy. "If all of the future events are true… This body’s father, Vanderman who is the protector of the dictatorship, is a common Luminarist of the Phantom Light. Based on the images, Vanderman is one of the fated Phantom Light members who will be destroyed together with the Phantom Light by Beckstone…"

Chapter 230: Reason 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The current identity that Garen had reincarnated into was Acacia, the son of a Luminarist whose life was wanted by both the Seraph Light and Phantom Light. His father Vanderman was a Luminarist with average strength. He had occupied a place but he was fated to die from either sect as he did not listen to the Obscuro Society’s command, and because of the crimes he committed in the past. His household’s land was also fated to be seized and his family members killed, so that the rebel bases could be built here.

"It’s still too early to think of these. I need to see if my predictions are true." Garen stood up, walked towards the window and looked outside into the distance.

"If they are, judging from the current timeline, the news of the uprising’s failure in the valley should come soon. After that, there would gradually be difficulties to collect tenant rent."

Garen let the cold air breeze on his face and golden hair. It cleared his mind a little as the cold air cooled down his overworked brain.

"We’ll see. If what I saw from the message is true, I will have to start planning early."

This body’s father, Vanderman was a self-willed man. The only person he was kind to was his son, and he viewed him as the successor of the family. It was unfortunate that he had abducted a few young boys and girls as materials for his experiment to research the special abilities of the Phantom Light. Among abducted children, there was a girl named Leanna -- Beckstone’s childhood first love.

Leanna was dead. This meant that there shall be a hateful grudge, an unforgivable resentment.

On the other hand, Vanderman complied with the Obscuro Society’s orders in appearance, but opposed it in his heart in order to sustain his status and identity. However, he did not listen to most of the orders and dissatisfaction eventually accumulated. He was eventually killed by an elite from the Obscuro Society as he invented rather interesting special abilities.

"It’s not that surprising if all of this is true… If this goes on, I wonder how many Luminarists like Vanderman would lose their lives..." Garen gazed into the distance outside the window.

A faint yellow line formed by the yellow dots were moving slowly, faintly, in the dark forest far away.

There were torches held by the patrol group from another household nearby this area.

Bam!!

Suddenly, the group of yellow dots ground to a halt as a clear gunshot travelled through the surrounding. A faint sound of a small deer was mixed among the gunshot.

Garen could heard laughters from the group that was far away. They seemed to be quite happy.

"It’s another wild deer! We’re very lucky! Haha…" The sound travelled faintly from afar.

The group soon disappeared from his vision.

The mountain opposite of his window had no more movement after that.

Garen shifted his sight to his surroundings.

He was currently standing on the second floor of a double story house which was made out of wood. This wooden house was just a small portion of a big manor.

There were at least ten buildings of different sizes and arrangements in the manor, all of them painted in white.

Acacia, his father and a female housekeeper lived together in this building. There were at least ten female servants, grooms, gardeners and chefs who lived in this manor as well. The whole manor was as big as two soccer fields and one would be lost easily as the routes were wrapped around from one end to the other.

The building he was currently in was placed at the rightmost corner of the manor.

Acacia was the kind of person that was very frightened of his father. Although Vanderman had never beaten him before, his deep and dense aura made Acacia not want to stay near him for any long period of time. He would immediately flee after his usual greeting routine.

He even chose the place that would be the furthest away from the center of the manors, all to stray further away from his father.

His cousin Sofea Hathaway and Little Giles, who often came to play were present today. Little Giles was the son of Vanderman’s favourite student. Hence, Sofea and little Giles would often visit his father Vanderman.

Garen listened to his surroundings carefully and could faintly hear Little Giles speaking loudly from afar. It was obvious that this kid was playing with the dogs again as he could also heard the dogs barking.

He could also hear the servant's’ footsteps passing by during their night patrol.

This manor was located deep in the mountain, and it felt like it had been isolated from rest of the world. They had their own vegetable garden, farm, livestock sheds and even a small self sustaining town at the foot of the mountain.

His father Vanderman kept lurking in his manor all day long and no one knew what he was up to. He didn’t go out to socialise and he would occasionally attend classes in the royal academy as he was a professor there. Other than that, he had done nothing else for the past five years.

On the other hand, Acacia often attended the balls and parties nearby. His cousin would occasionally visit him as well.

There was only one way to communicate between the manor and the outside world: Every once in a while the female housekeeper would go out to collect rental, tax and sell some local specialties. She would came back with daily necessities and some condiments after that.

He tidied his messy hair and peeled off the blood clot at the back of his head painfully.

He sat back onto the study desk as he had a better understanding of his surrounding environment.

"I should focus on the so called Luminarists of this world. I wonder how strong the Luminarists are, with their totems as their weapons…"

He gently held his fist, and he could feel that his body was slowly recovering. Although it was very slow, it was much better than when he had just woken up.

"Currently, the strongest Luminarists are the president of the Obscuro Society, Ghost Gate and the leader of the Terraflor Society, Sisley. The images have information of their battle…" Garen felt strange that most of these images looked like Beckstone’s perspective during his adventure. All the major events were recorded clearly from the beginning until the defeat of Ghost Gate of the Obscuro Society.

The remaining information related to the Luminarists was completely recorded down.

He didn’t know what kind of other capabilities his abilities possessed but the current main concern was not this.

He started to skim for every event that was recorded down in the message. The images kept flashing by in his mind. Time flew…

"Found it!!" He suddenly stopped at a portion of the message. Two commoner figures appeared in front of his mind.

"There were at least ten records of the battle between Luminarists in the forest near the Trejons Household land in the Lush Forest district. The most recent battle… was between a person called the Emin of the Seraph Light and Clyde of the Phantom Light." Garen examined this portion of the record in detail only to find out that they were Luminarist with below average strength and hence had very weak abilities. Thus, the scenario was very cloudy and nothing could be seen clearly. When he opened the message, there were stripes of colorful lines similar to that of a television without a strong signal. The recorded images from the abilities were all mixed together and nothing could be made out of them.

"Let me look at the time… To be precise… It was after the event of rental difficulties and… before the uprising by the valley, which is in two days time."

Garen picked out the most recent battle in the record.

The image messages recorded by his abilities were so detailed that Garen took a long time to sort out the most recent details in his timeline.

"The lowest tier of a Luminarists. Let’s compare their strength with secret techniques and see how strong they really are."

Garen took a deep breath, got up and laid onto the big soft bed. He covered himself with the white blanket as he felt a sense of drowsiness settling upon him.

From the war in the previous world, to the transmigration, up to the sorting of his memories… his nerves had been under stress for all of them. Since he had a clear grasp of the situation he was in and there was no danger nearby, he could finally relax.

"Acacia is dead. From now on, I am the new Acacia…" Garen laid on the bed and thought, as he felt his brand new and unfamiliar body.

After a while, he drifted into his dreams…

He was back to Smoke Island, right before he punched the nuclear bomb.

In that instant, the nuclear bomb beamed out a ray of bright light and the mega volcano erupted below him. His body was disintegrated instantly.

The powerful eruption shot his very last piece of consciousness up into the sky.

In Garen’s dream, the eruption of the mega volcano looked like a giant black smoke pot as he turned his head around and flew away from the planet.

"So this was the legendary Black Smoke Pot…" Garen finally understood. "Then what’s the deal with the legend stating that it could be used to communicate with the dead? Also, how does the ancient endo’s culture discovered the mystery of the volcano and they even build so many stone statues on top of it. Furthermore, I didn’t even see any trace of corpses until the very end."

"The Black Smoke Pot that is able to go beyond the limits… I guess no one had succeeded since history began…?" Garen thought.

Was it a rumor that became a legend or a legend that became a rumor. No one will never know.

However, one thing was certain. It was not a coincident that he was able to arrive to this planet. He would most likely not able to reach this planet if not for the volcano’s assistance.

The strangest part was that he had leaped countless light-years.

"The last time Smoke Island erupted was most likely a very long time ago. Is it possible that the totem’s power and the so called Luminarists on this planet are the relics that was left behind by the mages from the previous world? Or maybe there are some form of connections in between?"

Garen suddenly thought of this possibility in his dream.

The legends of the mages from the previous world were not uncommon. In that strong and advanced era, there was always a possibility that strange phenomena would occur.

Chirp… Chirp...

Garen opened his eyes as the golden rays showered his blanket. Sunlightpassed through the window’s and reflected off the dust floating in the room.

There were two pigeons chirping loudly just outside the window.

"Where am I?" Garen looked up at the unfamiliar ceiling as he was not able to react in time.

He sat up and felt a warm sensation as he let the sunlight shining freely on the back of his hand.

Soon, everything in his brain clicked.

"I am now Acacia… I am no longer Garen Lombard or Luo Jing." His had a strange look on his face as he was inside an unfamiliar, weak body. He was not used to anything at all.

Chapter 231: Preparation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen sat quietly on the bed for a while, before getting up and changing into a white casual shirt with silver sleeves that he had obtained from the wardrobe.

He set his sights on the the attribution pane just below his vision.

The attribution pane was no different than before.

He hesitated for a moment as he looked at the remaining ten or so potential points that he currently had, and decided against using them to speed up his recovery..

"Since I haven’t found a new source of energy, I have no choice but to ration the potential points."

The potential points were obtained via absorbing the Antique of Tragedy, and he did not know if they existed in this world. Even if they did, ten potential points were considered a very large amount, and should not be spent haphazardly.

Garen tidied his shirt properly, since he was the kind of person who loved to be clean and well presented. He touched it up, and even used different kinds of cologne.

Garen frowned as he looked at the diary that wasn’t finished from last night. All of the notes were praises and admiration towards Aquarius.

He picked up the book and flipped for a few pages to find out that there wasn’t much content inside.

As he gently closed the notebook, he walked towards the mirror and picked up the comb that laid beside it and started combing his hair tidily, just like Acacia normally would. He then picked up the usual colognes and applied onto his body.

"Who uses cologne?!" He placed down the cologne bottle with disatisfaction.

After checking everything in front of the mirror to ensure everything was flawless, he then turned away his gaze and walked out of the bedroom.

He walked along the faint yellow wooden corridor and walked down to the first floor through the spiral staircase.

The two female servants who were cleaning up the main hall placed down whatever was in their hands and kneeled at Garen as they saw him approaching. They then continued what they were doing after that.

Garen glanced at the two female servants. They were in their forties and weren’t beautiful in the slightest. However, they were very agile and they would make a good helpers.

He passed through the main hall and walked out of the building.

The lawn outside was as green as emeralds, and they looked very pure under the sunlight. A few big, grey trees were scattered in the lawn, and the leaves sung as the breeze blew. Occasionally, a few green leaves with yellow leaves mixed among them would gently drop to the ground.

There were a few people of both genders in grey long sleeves and long pants on the lawn cutting bushes at the edges.

Garen looked at the sun that had just risen from the horizon. Since it was still early, considering that it was not 7 o’clock yet, heh decided to circle the manor to familiarize himself with the surroundings.

As he walked along the lawn, he slowed down his pace as he walked passed the buildings. These buildings were of different sizes and had different purposes. They were used for living quarters, storage, collection, guestrooms, etc.

Garen spent twenty minutes slowly at first, but hastened his pace as he circled the whole manor.

The only impression he felt towards the whole manor was desertion.

There were too little people. A manor that could fit up to fifty to sixty people was only occupied by ten or so. This quantity had already accounted for the servants, gardeners, grooms, etc.

A lot of these places were not properly cared for. Weeds were growing wild in some areas, and a few buildings looked grey with paint starting to crack and peel. It looks like it had been a few years since a guest had come visiting.

The area of the manor that was actually fully utilised was only about one third of the whole manor. Many places were deserted and it gave off a sense of strange quietness.

Dang… Dang…

The melodious morning clock had rang.

Garen looked up at the clock tower and could barely see a person hitting the bell.

He turned around and walked towards the main building in the center of the manor.

His morning routine involved greeting his father, and most importantly, the female housekeeper would also be there with the latest newspaper from the outside.

Going through the newspaper was the fastest way for Acacia to understand the situation outside the manor.

Garen squinted his eyes as he needed to prove that the images he saw during his transmigration was real.

He walked along the patterned lawn as he headed towards the building in the central area. As he reached his destination, he saw a tall middle aged man standing at the balcony on the second floor.

The first impression he had from this man was majesty. He was a tall man with a face filled with black moustache. His moustache was trimmed neatly, and his hair was combed from one temple to the other.

He had two moustaches above his lips and a sharp beard right under his chin.

The moustache didn’t give an impression of messiness. Instead, it gave an impression of cleanliness as it was perfectly trimmed.

The man was in a black coat as he looked down from the balcony.

"Is that Acacia."

"Yes, father." Garen answered with his head down as shown in his memories. He even mimicked the cringy expression.

"Come up here. Du Qian has returned and she brought you the Black Duran Cologne you wanted." This man was Acacia’s father, Vanderman Trejons.

This man was already in his fifties. On the surface, he was an upper class aristocrat of the Kovitan Empire and the professor of the Royal Academy. In fact, he was a Luminarist of the Phantom Light and possessed incredible strength.

Garen walked into the building and there were two people, one girl and one boy, already sitting opposite of each other on the sofa in the living room.

These two were called Edney and Maxilan and they were Vanderman’s most loyal right-hand-men. They were also the strongest among Vanderman’s underlings. Although they were not Luminarists, the royal army could not be compared to them in terms of sword and gun arts.

Garen took a glance at the two. and he remembered clearly that they would die in the hands of Beckstone and his team in the near future. On the other hand, father Vanderman would die in the hands of an elite member of the Obscuro Society.

He, as Vanderman’s son, would die from one of the Obscuro Society’s lackies as he escaped from the manor, while his cousin was protecting him.

No matter how one looked at it, these two were definitely loyal to the Trejons Household. Their profit and pride were placed with the Trejons. Their loyalty was placed not just with Vanderman himself, but with all of Trejons.

"Sister Edney, brother Maxilan." Garen greeted them politely as he recalled from his memory.

"Sir Viscount is currently upstairs and he will come down soon." Maxilan was a gentle uncle.

Two of them were not that familiar with Acacia. Since Acacia would be the next successor of the household, they treated him politely as if he was the master of the household. Their actions were not affected by the news of Garen’s gambling habit.

"Where is sister Du Qian?" Garen looked around as he didn’t see her.

"She’s upstairs reporting the situation to the Viscount." Maxilan replied. He was wearing red casual clothes with a sword hanging by his waist.

"Oh…"

Garen nodded and sat on an empty sofa at one side as the female servant poured him a glass of lemon tea.

Garen picked up the glass and drank the tea as he noticed a stack of newspapers at the corner of his eye. He reached out his hand to the newspaper and placed it on his knees as he started to read them casually.

Maxilan and Edney were whispering to each other about something off to one side. They seemed to be unhappy, in fact it was rather obvious.

Garen ignored them and focused his attention on the newspaper.

The first thing he saw was ‘The dangers of self abortion’

Garen was speechless and went to the next page.

‘Are you well prepared to take care of your breasts?’

He flipped to the main page of the newspaper with a poker face.

‘Lush Green Sanitary News’

He raised his head up to find out that Maxilan and Edney were trying to hide their laughter with all their might. He could also heard a faint laughter off one side.

"Fine. I just wanted to see the latest news for this country. Is there anything wrong with that?" Garen shrugged.

"It’s this one." Maxilan took out a folded grey newspaper and passed it to Garen.

Garen took the newspaper and the first big headline he saw was: ‘Danpalas Five to interview Kovitan in the near future.’

Below the big headline: ‘Both leaders are to negotiate regarding the turmoil in the valley.’

"Turmoil in the valley?" Garen whispered.

Daniela was one of the top two strongest countries in the east continent. In terms of power, Daniela was on par with a super country in the west continent when allied with Kovitan.

Garen continued reading the article.

It was the uprising in the valley that he saw in the images.

Garen felt a chill down his spine.

He continued reading the article but did not find out anything of significance.

He then changed to another newspaper.

This was last week’s national newspaper. The second headline was the nation’s protest regarding rental of a small farm.

It was at this moment Garen began to understand. To assure himself, he searched his memory to confirm the location and the date of this major event and compared it to the date and location reported on the newspaper.

It was exactly the same!!

Garen used the newspaper to block his face from everyone as he tried to hide his shock.

"Looks like the thing I saw will definitely happen in the future."

"If the events I saw in the images are real… Then, what I really saw was the history of the planet?"

He closed his eyes and recalled the scenario once again.

"Garen, when did you start to care about the nation’s problems?" Vanderman’s voice came from behind his back.

Garen put away the newspaper and noticed Maxilan and Edney had already stood up and had their sight set behind him.

He turned around and saw Vanderman in a black tuxedo and he had a black hat in one of his hands. His overall look could only be describe with the word elegant, and there was a beautiful woman with an hourglass body figure standing beside her.

Garen immediately lowered his head.

"Father, you have came down? I have made an arrangement with Garcia so I will be leaving now."

"Leaving already? Why not have a breakfast together?" Vanderman walked over and sat on the sofa. The lady beside him followed his movement tightly and sat down as well.

"No thanks." Garen had his head down the entire time as he looked at Vanderman’s footsteps. His footsteps was slow and calm like a delicate clock and it sent a chill down in Garen’s nerve.

It was fortunate that his rejection was similar to of Garen. The original Garen didn’t really want to hang out with his father as well so both of them shared this side of the personality.

"Fine. You can leave now. Don’t come back too late." Vanderman replied calmly.

Garen nodded his head, placed down the newspaper and smiled at Edney, Maxilan and the woman beside Vanderman before he rushed out of the building.

Chapter 232: Preparation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It was just a simple morning greeting, but with Garen’s extensive experience in Martial Arts, he caught a whiff of the thick scent of blood from this viscount-slash-professor. Not only that, he also exuded a sense of extreme meticulousness.

Having left the small building, Garen walked on the lawn under the sun, warming his body up, to his delight.

He walked straight to the entrance of the manor and asked the carriage driver to prepare his double-seater white carriage with silver edges.

Mounting the carriage, he ordered the driver to drive along the only road to the outside. He himself sat inside the carriage and looked at the environment from the inside.

Under his request, the driver went around the manor so he could get used to the environment near it.

The Trejons Manor was surrounded by forest with a small lake on one side. The path went along the woods, extending to a small town called Mirrorlake Town belonging to the Trejons Family. Even so, it was about a dozen kilometers before they arrived at the town.

Garen let the carriage cruise the town twice. After memorizing some of the more important landmarks, he alighted the carriage and walked toward the woods. His driver didn’t stop him. The whole area near here was his family’s territory and was frequently patrolled.

Walking alongside the edge of the lake, Garen walked into an area with black-leafed trees.

The forest was dark even in bright daylight, appearing gloomy and damp.

Pigeons and doves from the manor played around on top of the lake, some black swans waddled casually in the lake, combing their feathers occasionally.

Garen slowly compared his view with the location he scanned during the ride, examining the area and making his way toward where he mentally dropped a location pin.

Eventually, he arrived at the edge of his family’s patrol border. In the distance, he saw an outpost with sharp, gray-white roof. The flag on top of it shows a black swan on a white background with silver outline. That’s the family flag of the Trejons family.

There were two sentries wearing the same gray-white color on the outpost. One of them was having a drink, the other was drying clothes by hanging them.

Garen evaded the outpost to avoid being seen and turned left and right by himself, finally arriving at a clearing with tombstone.

The clearing was roughly circular, as if cleaned out to make space for something. It also had wooden fence around it, even though a significant part of the wood had rotted and started to fall off.

Garen compared the scenery with the ones he saw in his memory. The two Luminarists were battling here.

He examined the ground for fighting marks, there was none.

"Not yet, obviously…" He went in front of the tombstone and looked at the name. ‘Hill Clinton Phalange’.

This area was only recently included within the borders of the family patrols. Before that it was just listed as a wasteland. No one knew about the old headstone here.

Silently, he returned to the patrol area of his family after memorizing the location of the spot.

"In the memory, this tombstone is the direct cause of the conflict between the two Luminarists. But these has nothing to do with me. What’s important is to get a sense of how strong a Luminarist is…"

Garen was in deep thoughts on his way back.

For three years, he studied Secret Martial Arts. Even though it was because of his special ability that he managed to attain the maximum stats, he had put in a lot of effort before he transformed into someone who had the courage to fight numerous elites with his life.

His constant self-encouragement, hard work, and persistence were also not to be ignored.

The limits of Secret Martial Arts was already apparent during the fight with Sylphalan at the Smoke Island. According to the images he’d received when he first transmigrated here, Luminarists’ powers are obviously more fantastical.

They seemed to be able to control a number of powers to fight against one another, and their powers seemed to be stronger than Secret Martial Arts’ too.

The one thing Garen wanted to know the most, was that between Martial Artist and Luminarists, who’d be stronger.

After preparing the things he needed, he returned directly to the manor and into his room to start training to breathe as per the Divine Statue Technique. That way, he could return to his normal strength with most efficiency. At the same time, he planned to wait until the battle that was going to happen.

　　**********

After returning to the manor, he started living like Acacia, doing his daily routines, he’d read the books and the news, he’d take care of his beloved lilac rose garden, and he’d go out every afternoon to where the tombstone is located and spied from afar.

Other times, Garen would focus on training his body. The restoration of Divine Statue Technique can’t be done within a day, but through stimulating his body over a long time. That said, the training combined with the healing effects of his special abilities, he could tell it was returning to him faster than he’d expected.

He waited patiently. The battle of the Luminarists will be within these few days.

　　**********

Between the utensils clinking, Garen and Vanderman sat opposite each other, having their dinner.

The lazy afternoon sun sauntered in through the window on the left and cast itself on the floor left of the rectangular white dining table.

On the dining table were turkey meat, bacon, grilled duck, squirrel broth and onion stewed tomato soup.

Both of them ate without a word.

Vanderman looked at his son, his son who was never a stickler for rules, was suddenly obedient. Usually he’d have gone out to gamble or to court Aquarius whatshername, but the past few days he’d been quiet.

"When Sofea left yesterday, why didn’t you see her off?" He asked, "You shan’t be so rude, do you hear?"

"Yes, father." Garen nodded and muttered. He forgot. He’d been paying attention at the tombstone so much, he didn’t know Sofea had left.

"About the Astronomical Edict, you were in the wrong. Don’t think I won’t know just because you don’t tell me. But you’ve already given it away, there’s no need to take it back, lest other families shame you. You owe your Big Sister Sofea an apology." Vanderman closed his eyes for a moment. "I will repay her on your behalf. Do not do it again."

"Yes, father." Garen nodded conscientiously.

The original Acacia did behave that way with Vanderman.

Whatever wrongdoings he had had, Viscount Vanderman was tepid at best, he never really showed any distinct expressions. He would gently take over and solve things as being Acacia’s ‘loving’ father.

Somehow, Acacia was just afraid of his father without any specific reason.

Vanderman finished his soup and wiped his lips clean before standing up.

"Alright, enjoy the meal. I will be out for a forum in the afternoon and will return late. Do stay in the manor for this evening, it may be dangerous out there."

"I understand." Garen nodded with alert.

Danger in the evening? What danger?

He started to have a guess for the possible reasons. Vanderman never used to warn Acacia like this. As a Luminarist himself, if he would consider something a danger, he definitely knows something.

Could it be that something is happening within the Luminarist circle?

Guesses kept flashing through Garen’s mind.

He had been following Acacia’s behavioral pattern for the past few days. He also minimized interaction with people who were close to him, for example, his friends. They sent him an invitation to a ball the previous night, and he’d turned down the invitation.

The point for this seclusion was to slowly change the impression people have on his behavior, to adapt to this life.

After all, no matter how much he disguise himself, Garen and Acacia are two very different people.

Staying in his seat, he watched as Viscount Vanderman left the dining hall.

He sped up and finished up his food, and wiped his mouth as he stood up. A servant passed him his palate cleanser soup, which he swallowed after gargling with it.

He excused himself to go have a walk by the lake, and under two guards’ protection, he strolled along the lake.

The guards here, as compared to the guards in the last world, were just two normal people who were slightly stronger. They wore leather armor and were equipped with daggers. Only a captain would qualified to carry a gun.

Even with Garen’s weakened body, he’d be able to take out the guards by himself. It doesn’t matter if they’ve been trained as a Royal Guard, the outcome would be the same.

He found an excuse to get away from the two guards. There were the patrols and the outpost nearby anyway, he needn’t worry.

Alone, Garen walked until he could see the tombstone from afar.

Viscount Vanderman’s warning had him thinking the battle may be happening that day itself.

The timeline for the battle in the memory aligned with the current period too.

He hid himself in the bush and concealed his presence using his Martial Arts breathing technique. His weakened presence quickly wicked out of existence. After all, he’d learned the Turtle Breathing Technique in his last world.

Inside the bush, Garen paid close attention to everything around him, especially for the sound and movements.

"According to the last world’s classification, I was a Grade B at my highest achievement, that’s the power level of a guided missile, my destruction level is equivalent to a mobile bomb able to cause mass destruction."

He calculated his rate of recovery.

"Within four days, I only recovered to the level of a normal adult."

When he was chosen as a core disciple for White Cloud Dojo, he was already close to attaining Grade E barring some combat experience. Grade D was Grandmaster of Combat level, Grade E was Fei Baiyun and First Senior Sister Rosetta’s level. They were qualified to open up a dojo of their own and teach.

With a body of normal human being, there are a lot of skills in the Divine Statue Technique he can’t use, with the exception of some basic battle and grappling skills. However, with his experience in combat and knowledge of the Secret Methods, Garen was confident he could beat anyone below a Grade E.

In other words, his body was weak, but his mind was one of the strongest fighters, of the King of the Century.

"It boils down to how Luminarists fight now…" Garen’s presence sank deeper and deeper into concealment, even his breath became slow, trickling, and drawn out. He could already sense something wrong in the environment with his rich experience in combat.

Chapter 233: Power 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A tiny breeze swept through the black-leaved woods, causing the leaves to swoosh loudly. Some dandelion seeds glided in the air, and bees buzzed around a bush littered with tiny red flowers.

On the side of the graveyard, in walked a middle-aged man in a black dress suit through the rundown fence.

He looked cleaned up and had a pair of white gloves, like a nobleman who’d just gotten out of a carriage.

Silently, he stared at the headstone with a solemn look on his face, seemingly reminiscing the past.

A faint footstep rattled behind him.

"Who’s there!"

The man turned abruptly, vigilantly stared at the trees behind him.

Deep in the woods, a maroon-colored windbreaker appeared in his sight.

It was a young man walking through the woods with great strides. Stopping ten meters behind the man in suit, he glared at him with a dark look.

"Emin, how dare you show your face here?" The man with red windbreaker said coldly. "Twelve years! This is your first visit here in twelve years!"

"Aren’t you the same?" Man with black suit replied with equal darkness on his face. "Clyde, this is my wife’s tomb, you’re not welcomed here!" He stressed on the word ‘my’.

"You’re the one who killed her! What right do you have to say that? Even her grave is crummy!" The younger man argued.

Both of them confronted each other with their outfits as contrasting as night and day.

Emin, the one wearing a suit, looked around as if searching for something when he realized.

"You were tailing me!"

"How else would I be able to find Hill’s grave?" Clyde, red windbreaker, smirked. "Just give up, Emin, I shouldn’t have let you take Hill back then. I thought she’d have a happy life with you, rather than suffering in the army with me. Had I known… Today, I’m going to settle the score with you!"

"I admit, I’ve failed her, but you’re in no position to lecture me!" Emin stared at his former rival in love. "Clyde A. Jackson, you don’t scare me! I just don’t feel the need to compare with you."

"Why are you still babbling about?" Clyde raised his right arm, revealing a ruby ring on his middle finger. "Come on, show me what you got after all these years!"

All of a sudden, the ring glowed a brilliant red. From the surface of the ruby, a thin red beam shot out.

It landed on the ground and transformed into a huge red-furred wolf as tall as half a person’s height.

Aroooo!

The wolf howled with a red glint in its eyes. Its physique was just like a real wolf if it wasn’t for its glimmering red eyes.

Its fur fluttered in the wind, making a sort of windswept grass plain effect.

The huge red wolf was three meters long and one meter tall, its claws were sharp and deadly, with a little bloodstains on it.

Garen hid inside the bush, stunned at the sight.

Every single detail, from the red beam shooting out of the ruby ring, to the beam transforming into a wolf, had been seen by him.

What’s even more surprising was Clyde, who released the red wolf, was shrouded in a faint red glow. That red light formed an egg shape around him, enfolding him completely without a gap.

"That’s… intriguing…" Garen thought the Secret Methods from Secret Martial Arts were fantastical enough, and the Sword of the Sprite was equally wondrous, but those were top tier forces after all. Unlike those, the two here only represent a normal level for this world!

"A giant red wolf?" Emin kept his face straight, and took out a small silvery-white cane hanging on his waist.

Lightly waving it, the tip of the cane sent out a beam of white light that transformed into a white bear.

Grrrr!

The white bear is as tall as a man when it stood up on its hind legs. It growled at the giant red wolf.

The white bear didn’t look too distinct from a normal polar bear, there was also no special light surrounding Emin.

"Clyde, I lost to you then, but I’ll never lose to you in front of Hill. Never!" Emin took off his white glove, revealing his scarred hands.

"Nothing comes from just talk." Clyde smirked, gesturing with his ring hand. "Attack!"

Red wolf growled and zapped past the right side of the white bear. Its claws glowed red as it sank them into the white bear’s skin, slashing it. The white bear’s fur around the wound was scorched and was emitting a charred scent.

The wolf was so quick, the bear only realized what had happened after the wolf landed behind him.

The patch of grass the red wolf landed on burnt, emitting green smoke.

Roar!

The white bear roared loudly as it pounded at the wolf. It missed.

Crack!

A branch was hit instead. It cracked, sending splinters toward the ground.

The white bear chased after the red wolf, pounding it with its paws and tearing at its torso with its teeth.

The beasts rolled against each other, causing the ground to rumble.

Still hiding, Garen observed the beasts’ attacks.

The wolf’s claws and teeth seems to have the effect of burning things they touch, it was so potent they can blacken trees and grass.

The bear was strong, its skin and fur seems to be able to withstand heavy damage, it hasn’t been hurt much in its few clashes with the wolf. Only when it was bitten that some tear wound appeared.

While the beasts were fighting, their masters didn’t even move, they just stood there without actions of any kind.

Garen observed carefully and was shocked to find them both surrounded by egg-shaped lights of their beasts’ color, and their feet are not touching the ground, but instead slightly hovering above.

"This is a Luminarists’ totem?" Garen noticed the none of wounds on both of the beasts bled. The flesh that was torn off the body just disappeared in a swirl of red or white light.

The two beasts kept tearing at each other, their attacks affected nearby trees and rocks, making a mess. However, as if with tacit understanding, they didn’t even go near the tombstone, so Garen on the other end of the clearing wasn’t concerned about safety at all.

"If these two beasts were totems, their destruction level is about the same as a Grade D in the Martial Arts world…" Garen eyeballed from the wreckage they’ve caused.

The two Luminarists were very normal, their power levels are only mediocre.

In other words, anyone who’s a Luminarist would have the power level of at least a Grade D Martial Artist.

Recalling the memory he received, there were other stronger Luminarists in the future. Garen winced.

"There are other stronger Luminarists, this world is stronger than the Martial Arts World!"

Crack!

The white bear snapped a tree with a half-meter diameter with its paw. Some parts of the tree fell off and hit Clyde, but was immediately blocked by the red glow surrounding him and bounced off.

"So that’s why they don’t fight themselves, they have that light-thing protecting them."

Garen noted.

He realized the Luminarists in the memory were all like that, they never ordered their totems to attack other Luminarists. Looks like this was the reason behind that.

White bear finally caved after defending against the red wolf’s burning attacks. Its wounds cumulated, but it still kept fighting, roaring, as if saying it will take the red wolf down together with it even if it dies.

Not far away, Emin’s eyes were bloodshot and he’s clenching his jaw, flicking his cane in the air continuously, as if there were something there.

"Have you gone mad!" Clyde’s face went frantic. "You’ll destroy your totem if you keep this up!"

The words didn’t even registered in Emin’s brains, he just kept flicking his cane with frenzy.

Arooo…

The red wolf was finally pounded on its abdomen and was sent rolling. Red light spots detached from its body and dissipated in the air.

"Don’t force me to do this!" Clyde’s face showed a savagery that wasn’t there. "Don’t you think you’re the only person daring enough to sacrifice your totem!"

"Do it then!" Emin replied, gritting his teeth.

A slight hesitation flickered in Clyde’s eyes.

In that instant, white bear charged at the wolf, lifting it skyward.

Roar!

White bear seemed to have increased his strength dramatically, no matter how hard red wolf struggled, it just couldn’t get away. The bear claws ripped into the wolf, tearing it apart.

"Sivak!" Clyde screamed.

Raising his right hand, the ruby ring erupted into a burst of radiant red.

The red wolf’s torso tremored, flashing red, and started to bloat up, the bigger it got, the redder it flashed.

Boom!

The red wolf exploded like a balloon bursting, golden flames billowed out of its torso.

The ground shook, the booming sound of the explosion spread in all direction centering the beasts.

The trees and the soil shot outward along with the blaze, devouring the two Luminarists. Scorching red liquid spewed as far as twenty to thirty meters away, igniting the trees around.

Garen already felt something’s wrong when Clyde screamed and bolted away. When he heard the explosion, he rolled on the ground and ran a dozen meters.

"It’s almost as powerful as a high-explosive bomb… That’s something." He commented as he stood up.

The flames stopped advancing not far before him. Within a twenty-meter radius, every rock and tree and flower had been burnt black. All the trees were felled by the force of the explosion, burning trunks and branches were everywhere on the ground.

"Such force…" Garen looked at the center of the explosion, trying to catch a glimpse of the two Luminarists.

Boom!

An explosion larger than the last one. Once again, blazing fire burst out from the explosion center and charged at him.

"F*ck!" Garen turned and took off. The impact carried him for several meters and set him down beside a tree. If it wasn’t for his foundation in Martial Arts, he would’ve eaten dirt.

He glanced backward. Centered around the two Luminarists, everything within thirty meter radius in the black-leaved forest had been turned into a sea of fire. Trunks, bushes, grass patches, even rocks, everything was on fire.

The fiery red shone on his clothes, dyeing them bright red. His hair and parts of his clothes were slightly scorched, too.

Chapter 234: Power 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"What is this flame…" Stunned, Garen watched as a boulder was melted quicker than he could count to ten. It crawled, joining the other dark-red liquid that almost flooded the uneven ground. It looked like a red marsh that releases heat.

The heat reminded Garen the lava at the volcano back at Smoke Island.

"The flame is definitely close to a thousand degrees*…" Garen dared not get close. He stared at the ground in the area of the explosion, feeling kind of creeped out.

"If any common Luminarists have this power of this level…" He cringed at the thought. The power, the destruction, it was too horrifying!

"This isn’t a Grade D… This kamikaze attack is at least a Grade B!"

Garen immediately thought of the father of his current host body, Viscount Vanderman, and if he also had that explosive force.

In the beginning, the two was just fighting with mild strength, nothing too dramatic, but it’s actually because they’ve been keeping their full strength in. In that explosion, every inch of their strength must have bursted out, melting even boulders within thirty meter radius area. This is comparable to an explosion of a tiny volcano!

By association, Viscount Vanderman’s future enemy, Beckstone, as well as the elite members of the Obscuro Society, these are the elites of the elites within the Luminarist circle, outpowering the two significantly.

"If all common Luminarists were at this standard, then Luminarists as a group is terrifying…"

Garen felt as if his blood had been steadily rising in temperature, his exposed skin on his face and hands were hot from the heat.

Even though he had finished his inspection of the power of Luminarists, he did not feel any relief when he thought about the two major enemies he’ll have to face.

He honestly felt even at his peak and mastery over Divine Statue Technique, he wouldn’t be able to withstand the destructive power of the explosion and the heat he witnessed, and this was just the power of two ordinary Luminarists.

Now that Viscount Vanderman had killed Beckstone’s first love, as well as was involved in some infighting at the Obscuro Society, if it wasn’t because of his support for the royals, he would’ve been offed a while ago.

The seed of vengeance had already been sowed.

Flames devoured the trees nearby, lighting up the crowns of the woods. The fiery glow dominated the color palette in the immediate surrounding.

Crackles from wood burning kept coming from the site. The breeze carried the spark into the air and further away.

Black smoke rose to the sky, calling attention to this side of the woods. The smell of the charred woods repelled Garen from his spot, forcing him further from the explosion site.

He looked at the center of the explosion again. No movements. The two Luminarists were nowhere to be found.

If someone told him before that humans can survive that explosion, he might not have believed it, but now, he’s not sure. After witnessing the strength of the Luminarists, he wouldn’t be surprised by things that challenged his knowledge.

He heard the patrol coming from afar, chose a direction, and sneaked away from the burning ground.

On his way back to the manor, his heart felt heavy.

Luminarists’ power exceeded his expectation. The fight in the beginning looked just like the ones in the memory, mild, not very exciting. If it wasn’t for the final explosions, Garen wouldn’t have felt the energy within the totem beasts.

Everything within thirty meters radius area became a sea of fire, even boulders turned into lava by these two normal Luminarists.

Hoof…

Garen let out a long sigh.

When he thought about facing Beckstone and Obscuro Society in the future, he felt slightly depressed.

"Looks like I need deeper information about Luminarists as soon as possible…" He thought of the dates he saw in the memory, "I have two years until Beckstone’s arrival, I hope there’s enough time…"

Whether he like it or not, since he transmigrated into Acacia’s body, he would need to face this danger as him.

Luo Jing wasn’t sure if he would transmigrate again once he died in this body. The Luminarists were no joke in this world, they’re far stronger than the Martial Arts World. If someone could interfere with souls…

Witnessing the strength of Luminarists, Luo Jing started to doubt his own.

With his strength, even if the Divine Statue Technique has fully recovered, there’s no way he could withstand a high heat of a thousand degrees, let alone the stronger enemies after this.

Boom!

Once again, an explosion came from behind.

Garen turned around to look. The flames were getting smaller, the smoke thinner.

From his side, a team of guards in white uniform hurried over to his side.

"Young master! Are you okay? Young master!"

The lead guard was a man with trimmed beard, he asked as he arrived in front of Garen. His face was pale.

"We were late to come here. Why did you loiter around here? It’s so dangerous! It’d be bad if you got hurt in the explosion!" The lead guard pointed at two other guards behind him, "Luckily they reported back to us in time, or else this would’ve been a tragedy!"

"I don’t… I’m fine…" Garen used the Turtle Breathing Technique to create a pale, scared-looking face. "Let’s go back, I was just scared…"

"Of course, of course." Lead guard sighed in relief. "Let’s go, we’ll send you back to the manor!"

Garen returned to the manor with the escort of the guards. He took a nice warm bath and changed into fresh white clothes before noticing his housekeeper Du Qian’s arrival.

The housekeeper was the one he saw beside his father. She’s slightly plump. As she saw Garen, she inquired his health with concern. It was only after she’s sure he’s of good health that she got at ease and asked people to get him some nerve-soothing aromatic herbs. After that, she instructed people to put out the fire in the woods.

Garen closed his door, sat on his bed, turned off the light and pretended to sleep.

He started mapping out his future plans.

"Two years… from the information in the memory, only a Luminarist can fight another Luminarist. When I was in the Martial Art World, I only needed three years to get to the top, I refuse to believe I couldn’t reach a level where I can protect myself in two years!"

"How do I become a Luminarist?"

Garen started thinking about the question.

His father Vanderman is a Luminarist. If he wanted to become one, he only needed to ask. However, if Vanderman was willing to teach Acacia Luminarist in the first place, he would already have, not keeping any knowledge of it from him.

Garen glanced at the attribute pane at the bottom, it was slightly different than before.

‘Strength 0.8, Agility 0.8, Vitality, 0.8, Intelligence 0.4, Potential 1872%. Unknown Talent detected.’

Vitality had already increased by 0.1, obviously from the training for the past few days.

His gaze fell upon the Unknown Talent once more.

"What is this Unknown Talent? Is it the talent to become a Luminarist?"

After lying in the bed for a while, he heard sounds of Viscount Vanderman, it sounded like he was asking Du Qian about the fire. He insisted about his son’s health, that which upon he’s well, Vanderman relaxed audibly. Finding out that he’s asleep, Vanderman didn’t insist to see him.

The voices left as footsteps faded away.

Garen sat in his bed, and considered telling Vanderman frankly about wanting to become a Luminarist to gauge his success rate. At the same time, he was searching in the memory about becoming a Luminarist.

From the memory, Garen found a key point.

Luminarist is definitely a money burning job.

Becoming a Luminarist involves melting silver down to make very detailed work of a totem. He only knew the gist of how it works, but it wasn’t hard to extrapolate that conclusion from the fact that they use silver to create totems.

Garen scanned through the memory he’d received and found that silver was far more expensive than even gold, not to mention other metals, that’s different from how it was on Earth.

In this world, silver became the most expensive metal followed by gold.

Noble families in this world like using silver to indicate their honorable births. This includes Acacia’s clothes, they’re mostly laced with silver.

Garen did a little analysis and ruled out financial reasons. Acacia himself was a very prodigal person, but no matter how much money he’d lost to gambling, Viscount never minded, obviously their wealth is enough to support his lifestyle.

"If it wasn’t because of wealth, then it’ll be something else." Garen very carefully tried to recall Acacia’s memory.

He could vaguely remember a scene.

It was when he’s very young, he inadvertently saw Vanderman doing something mysterious, something fun-looking.

Vanderman was in a private chamber, lights flowed out of his hand, forming something silvery-white in the air, it was pretty.

The silvery lights arranged itself to become a something like a glyph, but the memory was too long ago, too blurry for Garen to make out what it exactly is.

As that was happening, Vanderman noticed little Cia, it seemed like he took a drop of blood from him, it wasn’t painful, just numbing. Vanderman left Acacia’s side and came back looking disappointed. Acacia lost his consciousness at that point.

This also made his memory fuzzy and thought it was just a dream. Now, it seems it might be real.

"Since it said I have some ‘Unknown Talent’, it may just be one for becoming a Luminarist. But Vanderman was disappointed, so if the memory is correct, that’d mean his talent didn’t meet his expectation." Garen sat cross-legged on the bed, analyzing. This body’s Intelligence is a little low, affecting his brain power and thinking speed.

"Intelligence is his weakness…" Garen sighed speechlessly. "Should I just spend some Potential on his Intelligence to make sure the calculations are correct?"

He thought his own Intelligence was low, but evidently, when compared to this body, he must be like a genius. This made him feel much better about himself.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

Translator’s Notes:

Here it wasn’t specified what temperature system Garen/Luo Jing is using, but since it was written for a Chinese audience, it could be extrapolated that it was the metric system, hence about 1000°C or 1832°F.

Chapter 235: Willpower 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Recalling Vanderman’s expression, Garen suspected it was because of Acacia’s low Intelligence that he wasn’t taught to become a Luminarist…

It was getting quiet outside, human voice and footsteps slowly faded away. Only occasional howls in the woods remained.

The sky was getting darker.

Staring at the dark sky outside, Garen slowly calmed down.

His anxiety-ridden brain was slowly tranquilized, returning to his previous state.

"Two years… Last world I was able to become the top in the world, I refuse to believe I can only accept my fate in this one!" He sat with his legs crossing, his eyes shining brightly in the night.

He recalled everything in the last world, Sylphalan, Old Man Gregor, Andrela, King of Nightmares, Ying Er, his uncle… Familiar faces keep popping up.

Garen closed his eyes slowly, and breathed deeply.

Sssss…

A breeze of cold air entered his lungs, lifting his spirit.

"Luminarists…"

Wordlessly, he sat in his bed trying to comb out his thoughts, attempting to find a way to become a Luminarist.

"If it was really because of his Intelligence, it would be problematic to look for Vanderman. No one would believe someone else would become smarter, and even adopted so many extra behaviors overnight. Luminarists are not so stupid they couldn’t tell the difference. So unfortunately, this is out for now."

He continued brainstorming.

"Then I’ll need to find other Luminarists, learning by my own is definitely out of the window, too time consuming. If I don’t understand how it goes outside, I’d be boxing myself in and other people might take me by surprise." He reviewed the memory meticulously to see if there are any more valuable scenes.

The memory is large, he could only scan through it one by one.

The clock ticked…

　　***************

Martial Arts World

Garena and Sylphalan both perished amidst the nuclear bomb and volcano eruption. The Smoke Island rose and became a huge crater for the volcano. People called it the Black Smoke Pot Crater.

Only a portion of the elites who participated the Smoke Island battle managed to escape. Most of them suffered from some sort of side effects.

The world’s Martial Art community was in a decline.

Half a month after the volcano erupted, King of Nightmares entered the White Cloud Gate. Together with Celestial Circle Gate, he managed to stabilize the Martial Arts community in the South. Then they planned to head toward the East in a systematic way.

Due to the volcano eruption, the air was mixed with volcano ash. Air quality was deteriorating around the three continents, the sky was dark, the ocean polluted. Floras and faunas were all affected, poisonous material were spread everywhere in the world.

One year later…

Celestial Circle Gate, White Cloud Gate, and The Sirens bought one giant ship each. Under Andrela’s lead, they were all headed to the East.

At the same time, Garen’s family, as well as his uncle’s family were all hypnotized onboard.

"Can you tell me how big brother died?" Ying Er asked Andrela who stood at the bow. Her waist-length purplish-black hair swayed in the wind, adding to her innocence.

"You big brother…" Andrela paused to think, "He may have been the strongest man in the world…"

"The strongest man in the world?" Ying Er’s eyes widened.

Andrela looked out to the horizon and slowly recounted Garen’s stories. "In the pursuit of Martial Arts, he’s already at the limit of what humans can achieve. His spirit and strength joined together seamlessly."

"In the three years he’s been studying Martial Arts, he had battled countless enemies and won, he had arrived at the peak of physical achievement!" Andrela stated calmly. "As his sister, you should be proud."

"It is so." An enchanting woman spoke from behind them both. King of Nightmares.

She transformed into Ying Er and approached slowly. They look the same, but her attitude is completely different from Ying Er’s, not having a single strand of purity.

"Garen used only three years to become a Saint of Fist Technique and killed the First Divine Warrior Palosa, taking over his title! His strength is out of this world!"

Ying Er was sad, but at the same time she felt a sense of pride. The praises the two top elites in the world sang of him made her feel a surge of exhilaration.

The three stood at the bow of the ship, silent, deep in their own reminiscence.

Three ships sped toward the Eastern ocean.

Boom!

A bomb dove into the water less than a hundred meters in front of the ships.

A white column of seawater burst into the air and rained on the deck.

"Warning! Black flags! Pirates!" A sailor on top of the mast yelled. Cannoneers hurried to their places.

Andrela waved his arm.

"Raise the white flag!"

White flag?

Ying Er did a double take, doesn’t white flag mean they’re surrendering?

She noticed, there were words on the white flag, so it’s not a flag of surrender. The words were…

From afar, scores of ships of different sizes had their Jolly Rogers raised. Several pirates were watching their prey with a telescope, and reported, "It’s White Cloud Gate! Let them pass!"

The pirate ships turned back without hesitation.

Ying Er stared at the leaving pirate ships, stunned. There was a shocking feeling of disbelief in her heart.

"This is the prestige of the strongest fighter in the world!" Andrela sighed. "We’ve met twenty-six different pirates, no exceptions, just raise the flag."

"Even Immortal Palace, Behemoth Gate, and other countries have recognized Garen as the strongest man in the world!" King of Nightmares continued. "The moment Weisman released the nuclear bomb, many elites saw Garen punching at the sky, his Divine Statue Aura was clearly seen above the Smoke Island."

Andrela nodded, "It’s not that the pirates were scared of Garen, it’s their way of showing respect. They respect his bravery to challenge firearms as a Martial Artist. The pirate king Macks is also an elite Martial Artists, he just couldn't arrive at the Smoke Island in time, but he also saw the platinum-colored Divine Statue Aura."

"Rather than saying that they respect his power, it should be said that they respect his attitude and spirit." King of Nightmares added, "Garen Lombard’s spirit is now a popular culture among the Martial Arts community, even in the army of each country. Some soldiers even tattooed his face on their bodies. He symbolizes the spirit of Martial Arts! One that does not give up even though they are in a tough spot."

"That was your big brother."

"That is your big brother."

The two mused the same words one after another.

Ying Er stood against the sea breeze, her heart burning, eyes watering even though she was not sure if she's sad or proud.

Woo-woo!

In that instant, black ships sailed in an orderly fashion on the opposite direction from them toward the three continents.

Sirens kept blaring. Numerous cannons spotted on the deck of the ships. The black on the ships almost covered wholly the deep blue of the sea.

"That is the Pirate King, accepting the summon of the Immortal Palace Alliance to attack Weisman’s army!" Andrela stared at the ships, and explained. "Sylphalan and Garen both died when the nuclear bomb exploded in the volcano. The Immortal Palace were so mad, as if Sylphalan’s death had stopped their plans permanently. Two people from the Immortal Palace wreaked havoc within the borders of Weisman. Flamingo himself blew up two ammunition depots of their military base, as well as a biochemical research base in three days. His method Estelle as extreme as always!"

"Weisman didn’t expect such a repercussion from bombing the Black Smoke Pot volcano. As of now, the armies of every country banded up into a coalition to take down Weisman." King of Nightmares laughed unapologetically. "When we left, the Confederation and the Tulip Republic coalition had already started attacking the bay of Man Marseille."

"There's the Immortal Palace wreaking havoc from inside, and there is the world's army on the outside. Weisman is finished." Andrela nodded.

　　******************

Garen kept thinking while memories of Luminarists was dug out one by one.

It may be because he had not mastered the Divine Statue Technique, or maybe he realised his strength in this world is weak. Without unrivalled power, he's not confident in being invincible.

However, he's confident in getting stronger even though it's not the same world. The only problem is how much time he would need.

If you wanted to return to the last world, he'll need to make sure there is no more accidents. Transmigration through death had never struck a chord with him. He can't guarantee returning to the last world after his death, or going to a completely new world, or even perish.

If he wanted to avoid that, you'll need to solve the problem that is coming in two years.

After his battle with Sylphalan, the feeling of dropping to a level of normal human from the strongest man in the world had slowly healed. Right now, his thoughts are as calm as a cat.

A tiny scene flashed through his mind.

"No!" His brows furrowed, thinking hard to remember the scene that almost escaped him.

Soon, a man with a black fedora appeared behind a group of people. He was wearing a black suit with a pair of white gloves, and he was carrying a short cane.

"He’s that Luminarist called Emin! He’s not dead?" Stunned, Garen immediately recognized him.

He jumped from his bed, wore his shoes, and went to the window.

Near the dark lake, wisps of smoke was still visible above the woods.

"If he’s not dead, it would mean that he had survived the battle! This is an opportunity!"

He examined the places around the explosion site, there were several people cleaning up, preparing to leave.

Standing beside his window, he waited for a dozen more minutes until they’ve all left. It was then that he dressed up, changed into his boots and sneaked out of his room.

After leaving the manor, Garen went straight toward the direction of the site. Very quickly, he’d arrived around the explosion site.

Chapter 236: Willpower 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The ground was left a black glass-like shell, stones and metal and mud melded together. There were no trees, no grass patches, all of it vanished, melting together with the other materials.

The explosion site has turned into an oval black crater.

Garen made his way carefully along this area, while at the same time checking for places that might hide bodies.

There was only a slight spillage of moonlight that night. Garen could barely see the silhouette of the objects in the woods.

The air was cool, but the site was still a little warm from the explosion. The ground was hot to the touch, he could feel it through his boots.

Garen checked the place thoroughly around the oval crater. Nothing. He widened his search area.

It was getting late by the second. He checked everywhere, in the bushes, behind trees, between boulder cracks, under the branches etc. He has searched everywhere that could hide people, but there was not a single sign of anyone hiding.

He did, however, almost stepped on a nest full of black swan eggs.

Slowly, his search area widened to include the lakeside.

Garen believed the person he saw in the memory is the Luminarist called Emin.

This was an opportunity of a lifetime, it’s also the most practical. If he could could find the Luminarist called Emin and save him, then he could request him to be his teacher, that’s the idea with the highest success rate.

Garen didn’t show any impatience searching for Emin even if it’s taking a long time. When he was training his Martial Arts, he had to constantly repeat the same movements, some were not only uncomfortable, but painful as well, but he persisted.

It can be said that even without the help of his special ability, he’d be able to become a decent Martial Artist within a certain timeframe. His special ability merely gave him a key to reach the peak.

Compared to those days, this was nothing.

He had decided to fully utilize the night to look for the Luminarist Emin. In an explosion like this one, he would’ve been badly hurt.

Walking along the lake, he started to examine the water. Soon, a dark silhouette entered his sight, it was floating on the water, unmoving, but it still looked like a human shape.

Garen hurried over, and threw a pebble at it.

Slap.

No movement, the pebble sounded like it hit flesh.

Garen had a slight suspicion. He closed their distance to better make out the silhouette’s true shape.

It was a charred, curled up body. Floating beside it was a short cane covered in soot.

"This might be him." With a little hope, Garen approached him waddling through the water.

Flipping him over, he revealed a soot-covered pale face, it was the Luminarist Emin.

"It’s him!" Garen sighed in relief. "Hey, are you alive? Wake up!"

He patted Emin’s face and pressed his stomach, he wasn’t bloated, he didn’t drown. He gave Emin two slaps on the face. No reaction.

He used his fingernail to press hard against Emin’s philtrum point*.

After a few tries, Emin finally groaned weakly.

"How are you doing? Do you need treatment? I’ll send you to a hospice." Garen pretended as if he didn’t know him. He felt weird saying that.

"No… No need…" Emid said weakly. "Child… I just need a some antibiotics*… Just a little would do…"

Garen touched Emin’s forehead, it was cold.

"You’re too weak. There was an explosion here just now, it’s not safe. I’ll bring you to where I live."

Not waiting for an answer, Garen dragged Emin back on land before piggybacking him home slowly.

Within moments, Emin was out cold again, not making any sound.

Garen managed to return to his house without waking anyone up. He removed the lake seaweed on Emin and set him down on the recliner. Then he started the fire in the fireplace and placed Emin near it to dry.

Adding firewood to the fireplace, Garen fiddled with the fire. He looked at Emin who was on the recliner.

"This is my first time looking after people. If you don’t repay me when you wake up, I will not let it go." He murmured. He wasn’t sure if Luminarists have any way to investigate the past, so he continued his act even when Emin was unconscious, including the way he murmurs.

Emin wasn’t moving much on the recliner, but his face was slightly redder because of the fire.

Garen continued playing with the fire. He thought it weird how Emin had no burn marks from the explosion, only a slight bruise.

After making sure the fire would burn a while, he went to get the first aid kit, got out a few white pills and poured a glass of water from the water room.

When he returned, Emin was awake. He sat up straight in the recliner, watching the fire crackle. His expression didn’t give away what he was thinking.

Hearing the footsteps, he turned to Garen.

"You saved me?"

"Who else did you think save you out there?" Garen threw the question back at him, "This are the pills you wanted, take it." He walked toward Emin and gave him the pills and the glass of water.

Receiving the pills, Emin swallowed them with a huge gulp of water.

"Thank you." He returned the glass to Garen.

"How were you floating on the lake? The lake water is bone-chilling at night, you should choose a better time to swim if you really want to. Afternoon’s great, some of the my guards like swimming in the lake too." Garen set the glass down on the table, "Not Black Swan Lake though, if you’re found out by my father, you’d be dead meat!" He shrugged, pretending to not knowing anything. "My father hates it when the water source was polluted. Oh, he’s the viscount that owned this land. If you were found to have dirtied the lake, it’s probably a light punishment to be sent to the gallows.

"I’m sorry… I don’t actually like to swim at midnights, but this time I just had to." Emin shrugged the same way Garen does. After drinking the water and dried off by the fire, his speech was much smoother. His accent was melodic, obviously he wasn’t local.

"I understand, it’s okay." Garen nodded, "Unfortunately, I saw your fight with that guy. Losers deserved to be pitied."

"You have a sharp tongue…" Emin was speechless at that comment.

"You should be happy because you’re alive, and he’s probably dead."

"This is true." Emin nodded, his face expressing wonderment. "You said you saw our fight?"

"Of course, it’s so intense, it’s like bardic tales." Garen replied honestly.

Emin sized Garen up.

"If you can see our fight, it means you’re also someone talented. You also saved me, is there anything I can do to repay you?"

"Of course," Garen answered. "I would like to learn that fighting ability from you."

"You know what that is?" Emin asked, surprised. He regained his composure soon after. "Right, you have the talent, you must know about it already. Your parents or someone in your family must be one of us. But why do you ask me, a stranger, instead of your parents?"

"My father won’t teach me. My family is poor." Garen answered without hesitation. Being poor… If only Viscount Vanderman had heard about this… Even among the Luminarists, the Trejons Family is one of the wealthier ones, they’ve got a long way to become ‘poor’.

Emin’s face froze, and suddenly started reminisce.

"It’s true… I used to be poor…" His gaze toward Garen turned soft, "Don’t worry, since you saved me, I will pay for your future studies."

"You agreed?" Garen showed a surprised look. If he’s still being deadpan at this point, it’ll look very put on, it doesn’t suit youngster like him.

"Call me teacher." Emin nodded, "I will teach you until you’re also one of us, think of it as a thank you gift."

"It’s that simple?" Garen was stunned.

"It’s that simple."

"I thought it may be a little too casual…" Garen muttered under his breath.

"You’ve got the talent, you don’t look stupid, and you’ve saved my life. I have the money, I have the knowledge and experience. Everything would be based on those, what else do you want?" Emin said, wryly.

"What if I don’t have the talent?" Garen asked suddenly.

"Then it’s not gonna work. Answer me this, did you save me because you want to become a Luminarist?"

"Of course, who else would have the mood to take a walk in the wood at midnight? Do you think I’m crazy?" Garen mocked.

"Fine…" Emin has no comeback to that. He suspected this young man to have ulterior motive when he saved him. Hearing him admitting it frankly, it made him feel as if he’s the one at fault.

He paused.

"Well then, last question." He looked straight at Garen’s eyes. "Tell me your name, young man." He raised the slightly charred cane as if he’s going to point at something.

For a moment, Garen was dazed, but he gave a calm smile right after.

"Acacia, my name is Acacia Trejons, but I like people calling me Garen."

He genuflected as a sign of respect toward Emin.

The cane touched his right shoulder and momentarily flashed silver.

Emin stared at Garen, his face full of gentle reminisce, as if seeing himself on his knee back when he was initiated.

"With this ancient ritual, I swear to never reveal any of teacher’s knowledge and skills. May the Silver be ever-luminescent."

Two immature voices rang in his mind, overlapping, it was hard to tell Garen’s from his own.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. Lit. “person’s center acupuncture point”. Traditional Chinese Medicine practitioners use this point to cope with emergencies when a patient faints either in the middle of an acupuncture treatment or because of drowning or shock.

2. It was literally written as “anti-inflammatory medicine”. According to the description that came after it, imagine Xanax.

Chapter 237: Friend 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A week later…

Emin left without a word. Although his injuries hadn’t healed completely yet, he was now able to move on his own. After writing Garen a handbook of notes, he also gave an address before he left. His requirement was that Garen learned everything in the book and achieved the standard stated there, before searching Emin out again.

Garen didn’t step out of the estate for an entire week. Every morning, after having breakfast with Vanderman, he would lock himself in his rooms and forbade anyone from entering. There, he focused all his attention to deciphering that handbook.

The handbook had a lot of messy and scattered bits and pieces of knowledge, with no sense of organization whatsoever. Therefore, Garen couldn’t use his special power to read and absorb it as a whole.

And there was another key problem, which is that Acacia’s, or this body’s intelligence was simply too low. The quality of this body was simply not there, and could not satisfy the basic conditions to learn the special ability. That was why he could only study the traditional way.

The handbook had no name. In it was a great deal of the most basic information about Luminarists, just the very basics.

It was only after Garen read some of these things that he began to understand the true mysteries behind the existence of the Luminarists.

This was a very powerful group of people.

They relied on a basic, inherent talent in quality appraisals, to achieve the level where they could sense and control silver.

At one point, some of the geniuses among them suddenly discovered that they could use silver to create a resonance of mysterious power, and so the Luminarists were born.

They used silver to form many different totems, and then used unique structures and principles to eventually light those totems, activating them. These then became their helpers or subordinates.

But these totems themselves didn’t have much intelligence, so they were only equal to a Luminarist’s second body.

From the handbook, Garen found out that you had to fulfill three conditions to become a Luminarist.

One: Appraisal, a basic talent.

This was the basic or basics. Without this, it was impossible to enter this circle. You woudn’t even be able to see through a Shielding Light that someone cast casually.

Two: Intricate blueprints.

The creation of a totem required an extremely intricate silver blueprint, and it had to be three-dimensional rather than flat. The level of accuracy needed was extremely high. Someone without this talent couldn’t become a Luminarist either. This was the basic method and road to transforming knowledge into power.

Three: Basic tactics.

The Luminarist was the base, designing the totem, creating the totem, and helping the totem to fight or work. These were all a series of tactic, and in actuality a totem can be broken down into countless basic tactics.

A totem was like a complex machine made out of countless tiny components, and the tactics were the most basic of intricate components. At the same time, they could be used individually, to increase a totem’s ability in any one area.

These three points were the key to becoming a Luminarist.

And when it came to basic tactics, there was actually a lot of basic knowledge to learn. Each and every different Luminarist had their own accumulation of knowledge.

The further they went with their knowledge, the stronger the totems they created.

In truth, totems were like the physical embodiment of their knowledge. As everyone’s understanding was different, the totems would turn out different even if they used the same basic tactics.

The handbook only contained the basic contents of intricate blueprints, for Garen to study.

This area of knowledge needed a steady hand and a calm mind. They had to focus intently, and their emotions must not be disturbed.

This was also why most Luminarists were quiet by nature, because this was the basic requirement for making intricate blueprints.

He practiced for a few days in the manor, but he didn’t improve very much. It was obvious that this body’s innate talent really wasn’t all that. He wasn’t steady at all, and despite his frustration, he couldn’t do anything but wait for his body to regain some of its old quality, before he can improve it and then learn faster. Right now, all he could do was repeat the exercises mechanically.

This time he couldn’t take any more shortcuts. Just like other normal Luminarists, he had to start training his steadiness from scratch.

************

Near the Trejons territory: the Palato family grounds.

The thick forest of trees was like a dark green carpet. Towards the left of a waterfall, there was a grey-black estate under renovation.

In one house on the estate, the balcony of the second floor.

Garen was lying lazily on a deckchair, looking at the blue sky through narrowed eyes. He heard gentle piano music wafting out from inside, feeling so comfortable he nearly fell asleep.

The balcony was a white semicircle. Garen lay on a chair near the edge, wearing white casual clothes with silver trimmings, long sleeves and long pants. His golden hair blew about in the wind.

The sunlight fell on him, reflecting a light that was so white it was nearly blinding.

"Cia." The glass door opened, and a young man with a black ponytail walked out. He looked at Acacia, stretched out on the chair, with mild surprise. "Aren’t you going to play a few hands in there? Marin and the others had put out a table just for you, what’s with you today?"

Garen tilted his head and looked at the young man.

"I don’t want to play today… Recently I’ve been thinking about the meaning of life."

The young man’s face went blank.

"Wha? The meaning of life?!" He stood there frozen, an expression of disbelief as he looked at Garen, "I say, Cia, we were best friends since we were kids. You can talk to me about anything, but don’t go doing anything stupid!1"

"It’s fine, I just understood some things recently." Garen waved his hand. "Alright, go on in, or those young masters and misses in there will have to call you again."

"Save me, Prynne! Andel wants to smear cake on me!" On cue, a girl screamed inside.

"What are they doing now?" The young man turned away exasperatedly, going in past the glass door. There was cacophony inside.

Garen continued narrowing his eyes disinterestedly, staring at the white clouds slowly floating through the sky. In his head, he kept repeating the basic points of knowledge from the handbook.

This was Acacia’s life, going out and gathering with three bad friends every day. Today your place, tomorrow mine. Or after a few days, everyone would go book a large hotel room, and occasionally they would have a barbeque, go hunting, swim.

Gambling, racing horses, watching wrestling, and then they would drink beer together and tell tall tales when they rested. Whenever there was a special occasion or some big incident occurred nearby, the four of them would always be the first to rush over and watch.

Things like foreign circuses, wandering theaters, these were all their favorite activities.

The four of them were one of the two circles with the highest family backgrounds among the nobles around here. Acacia and Prynne Acivis were the representative members, eating, drinking and playing. Whatever was fun, they’d do it.

Prynne’s mother was the lady of the largest territory in Lush Forest district, his family’s power stronger than even Acacia’s. Normally, people thought he was the main player, while Acacia was the sidekick. As for the other two, Andel and Marin, they were also girls from two noble families who played together with Prynne since they were young. Their families were slightly weaker, but not by much.

The four of them represented half of the noble families in the entire Lush Forest.

Through these memories flashing in his head, he remembered that when Acacia was young, the four of them had stood and compared how far they could pee… That really was a spectacularly embarrassing memory. Two boys competing with two girls to see who could pee further while standing…

Unlike regular families, noble families could get whatever they wanted. And there was a lot to learn about etiquette and culture when they were younger, so whenever they got to play, they threw caution and logic to the wind.

As they’re continually spoiled by kowtowers, they had played almost all there was to enjoy. All that was left was emptiness.

And so they look for more extreme things to do.

For example, look at the four of them now. If it weren’t that their families strictly forbade anything sexual to prevent bodily harm, they would probably have gotten tired of that by now too.

Garen lay quietly on his deckchair. After revising his basic knowledge, he rested a little more and took a short nap. Then he started to think back again. If there was anything he couldn’t remember, he would take out a tiny note he had copied and check.

Time passed before he knew it.

The room started to grow quiet. A guest had come to visit, and was rejected by Prynne lazily. The two girls them chased away the pianist and randomly hit some keys on their own, creating a ruckus.

Amidst the chaos, the glass door to the balcony opened again, and a tall girl in a black-purple dress walked out. She had blonde-brown hair falling over her shoulders, and she walked up to Garen before crouching down.

"Hey, what’s the matter with you recently? Why do I feel like you’re growing more and more listless."

"Leave me alone. I suddenly feel like it’s time to grow up," Garen said mildly, mimicking Acacia’s tone from before.

"Is it because of Big Sister Hathaway?" The girl’s rather plain face looked as though she understood. "It’s just an Astronomical Edict, there’s nothing to it. At the most, I’ll steal my uncle’s one to make up for yours." She clenched her teeth, as though it had taken her a lot of determination to make that decision.

"Leave me alone, Andel, I’m just not that happy inside." Garen stood up and took a deep breath. "Recently I’ve wanted to learn some things, and stop messing about like this. I mean, we’re already twenty, what will happen if we just continue like this?"

"The families have everything arranged for us, don’t they? We don’t have to worry about anything, and just follow the script, right?" Andel smiled, but there was a hint of unhappiness in it. "Once we’re old enough, we’ll just get married, have kids, and continue messing around like this. What’s wrong with that?"

"That’s what you say, but deep inside you don’t like it either, do you?" Garen glanced at the girl.

"Aren’t we all like that?" Andel retorted.

"That’s why I want to learn something, and stop wasting time like this anymore." Garen was starting make preparations for his future change.

"Forget it, you?" Andel pouted disbelievingly. For some reason, she was feeling slightly angry, so she went back inside and decided to ignore him.

She didn’t know why, but when she saw Garen saying that he wanted to learn something so seriously, she just felt really suffocated inside, and panicky.

Watching Andel walk away, Garen didn’t say anymore. He got up from the deckchair, and stood on the balcony, looking down into the distance.

The white waterfall roared as it left long white streams in its wake, falling down into an emerald pond. A few birds circled over it at times, and a few coaches were stopped next to it, the horses snorting away.

Everything seemed unusually quiet and peaceful.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

The language suggests contemplating suicide.

Chapter 238: Friend 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This was Prynne’s most secluded estate, so they could avoid a lot of the adults who wanted to suck up to the four of them to build connections. These adults always found distant connections from all sorts of cracks and crevices, making them impossible to refuse when they say they just want to visit. And then they come one after the other, non-stop, so that they don’t have any more time for themselves.

These few days, Garen had been enjoying the excessive lifestyle of a rich heir. As the only son of an upper noble family, there were powerful people visiting him every day as soon as he stepped out of the house. All of them wanted to establish a relationship with Vanderman through him.

He only had a bit of me-time when he was together with Prynne and the others, so that was when he could study the knowledge on the handbook. That was why he agreed to hang out with the three of them.

It seemed like an easy life, but he had to be constantly feigning, and at the same time he spent a lot of energy on studying the handbook. So in truth, these days were pretty tiring for him.

And these days, while he was studying, he was also thinking how he should increase his own power.

Two years from now, - would surely come to Lush Forest for revenge, and the Obscuro Society was already fairly unhappy with Vanderman. Their life looked quiet, but in truth they were already surrounded by dangers.

Garen decided that he would find a way to first understand the entire Luminarist community’s overall situation.

During the time he spent with his teacher Emin, he more or less understood that the Luminarists were an extensive organization. Out of the several billion people in the Kovitan Empire, at least a hundred thousand of them were Luminarists.

Other than the Luminarists in the two main powers, Oscuro and Terraflor, most of them were regular Luminarists. Regular Luminarists made up ninety percent of the total.

In other words, Obscuro and Terraflor were at the highest level, completely out of reach for regular Luminarists. Their whereabouts and actions were mysterious and unpredictable, and normal people had no way to find about more about them.

Besides, most Luminarists liked to do research and lived quiet lives. Their social relationships weren’t anything to shout about, so they communicated even less with the outside world, and the latest news about them was even harder to obtain.

These were all basic things about Luminarists that Garen found out from Emin.

Thinking back on the related information he had, Garen glanced at the attribute pane at the bottom of his field of vision.

‘Strength 0.9, Agility 0.8, Vitality 0.9, Intelligence 0.5. Possesses Luminarists’ appraisal ability.

Secret technique -- Divine Statue Technique, Ten Thousand Mammoth martial arts.

Time until full recovery: 367 days (one year).’

"My power and intelligence improved just a smidge, it’s way too slow…"

"Cia! Are you going to the barbeque tonight?" A pretty girl with a maroon ponytail ran out and rushed at Garen, yelling, "Your goddess Aquarius is going too, y’know? Wanna come?"

Garen hesitated. He did want to see this woman that had the original Acacia wound around her little finger. "Alright. Who else is there, other than Aquarius?"

"There are two of her friends, both pretty girls," the girl with the maroon ponytail said mysteriously. "Thank me, I was the one who pulled them all here. If you weren’t looking so down recently, I’d be too lazy to take the initiative and invite them."

"Thanks a lot, adorable, pretty little Marin." Garen hastened to thank her.

"Saying it like that has no sincerity at all, gimme something with substance. I love your poetry, is there anything new?" Marin squeezed up to him, asking. A faint fragrance of roses wafted into Garen’s nostrils.

"You like my poetry? ..." Garen’s expression went blank for a moment. There were actually people who liked Acacia’s poetry?! It was an unbelievable assault to his understanding of this world’s beauty standards.

"That’s right, just tell us if you got anything new so we can all appreciate it. You’re our resident genius, y’know." Andel had come out as well, followed by Prynne.

Prynne’s expression was approving as well.

"Don’t hide it and keep it to yourself, just read it out for us," Prynne hurried him.

Garen looked at the three expectant faces in front of him, and began to wonder if it was his sense of beauty that had problems. That nauseating poetry actually had so many fans!

"Hurry up and read it out, what are you waiting for? Don’t tell me you ran out of ideas?"

"No way, I just heard one of Cia’s new poems recently!"

"Don’t disappoint us! This is one of our regular activities!"

Seeing the three of them staring at him expectantly, Garen started to feel a bit constipated.

Poems… Sure, there were some, but for him to stand up and read it to the three of them with a straight face… No way, that would be a source of eternal shame..

"Um… my throat’s been feeling off recently… why don’t you guys read it yourself." Garen hurriedly took out the notebook Acacia always carried around with him, and stuffed it into Prynne’s arms. Then he quickly darted into the large living room inside.

Prynne flipped open the notebook.

"Fine, we’ll read it ourselves."

"Beautiful lily! Thou art so fragrant~~ My goddess Aquarius, thy face art like that flower vase… uh, there’s an extra word here, it’s like that flower, so beautiful and fair."

Prynne posed as though performing poetry, and began to recite it loudly,

"O Beautiful Aquarius, worry not that thou lose thy beauty, worry not if thou art ugly. Even if thou became a toad, I would not give up on thou, I would love thou unconditionally! Aquarius! Ah! Aquarius! Ah! Ah! Ah~~~~!!!"

Each of the ‘Ah’s increased in pitch.

Inside, Garen felt his whole body going numb. Every hair on his body stood on edge.

"What a good poem!! As expected of my best friend, Acacia!" He could hear Prynne’s praises from the balcony. "I want to publish this poem to the love poetry magazine, and let everyone witness, the poetry of my brother Acacia! Look, these last three exclamations, they’re practically heavenly muse!"

"My favorite line is ‘Even if thou became a toad, I would not give up on thou’! Mm… so touching!" Marin kept agreeing beside him.

"Cia, how could you hide such a good poem after writing it? That’s mean of you!" Prynne voiced his dissatisfaction loudly from the balcony.

On the sofa inside, Garen was thinking that his dignity in this life, no! The previous life, and the life before that! His dignity since the very beginning had all been utterly lost.

"Suit yourselves…" Garen replied weakly.

What kind of eye would see this sort of thing even remotely as good poetry…

Prynne and the others repeated the lines over and over again on the balcony, and even had heated discussions about it. They were so loud that even the servants downstairs could hear them clearly. Only then did they enter the room, still dissatisfied.

"Cia, what’s the matter with you? Why does it seem like you’re feeling kinda down?" Prynne looked at Garen, sprawled over the couch and unmoving, with disbelief. "As expected of someone deeply in love. Your poetry is even better than usual!"

"Don’t mention poetry to me, it makes me nauseated…" Garen replied, more constipated than ever.

"As I thought, writing poetry takes too much out of you. True, classic lines like these would take up quite a bit. In that case, you’d better rest. We’ll call you when it’s time."

"Alright…"

"Then we’ll go ahead and prepare. We’ll decide on the choices, that okay?"

"Sure…"

Ker-chak.

With the sound of the closing door, the room suddenly became slightly empty.

There were only two young maids standing respectfully in the corner, quietly awaiting orders.

Garen lay on the couch. After a moment’s pause, he slowly recovered from his speechlessness.

Grabbing the black notebook, he tossed it fiercely to a side.

"What on earth is this!"

He stood up and returned to the balcony, lying on the deckchair to rest. And then he pulled the small papers out of his pocket to memorize the information from before. At the same time, he had to recall a few important matters.

Regarding the Aquarius he was going to meet at night, he found some relevant information in Acacia’s memories.

She was a very beautiful woman, with a small waist, long legs, a large bust and a breathtaking face. She had lively almond eyes, and when she looked at people, her expression always invoked love and pity. Especially when she looked directly at you with her eyes widened, her pure gaze would always make one lower their head in shame, unable to meet her eyes.

But Garen sensed something amiss about this woman.

This woman, who looked so weak and like a social butterfly, seemed to be perfectly at ease at a series of banquets and events. In fact, she seemed to take the initiative.

And even more strangely, many rich and powerful people also lowered their heads to her out of shame, and allowed her whatever she wanted. Her body was unusually soft, her skin as smooth as the highest quality white jade.

"Aquarius Senbenita…" Garen narrowed his eyes. "This woman was probably trained in martial arts… and probably some joint-related techniques used in assassination. She’s not what she seems…"

"Vanderman allowed this woman to play his son around, and didn’t do anything at all about it. Why?" Thinking back to what Vanderman said, he had absolutely no intention to trouble this woman. Instead, he had cleaned up after his son’s mess.

Garen began to vaguely suspect Aquarius’s identity.

"We’ll see when the time comes. If she really was a spy who was trained in assassination techniques, this would also be a great chance to see what the fighting level in this world is like."

He moved his shoulders, and they made small cracking sounds.

Although his body was recovering very slowly, he was still a top level martial artist. His fighting level was still no lower than E.

In the previous would, level E was already part of the letter levels, and was only lower than a Grandmaster of Combat. Regular small machine guns would not pose a threat to them unless wielded by a top level shooter.

Even outside, they were perfectly capable of starting their own groups.

Garen chased the two little maids away and stood alone in the living room. Then, he began to relearn a few tips and tricks to combat joint techniques.

Soon, Prynne rushed over to call him. Everything was ready, he said, so Garen had to go over there and prepare to leave.

They planned to stay a couple of nights on the mountain, and return home a few days later. They could take this chance to hunt and hike, too.

Garen asked the driver to inform his family, and got onto the carriage together with Prynne and the others. They drove towards the depths of the forest, a few strong bodyguards following them closely to maintain their safety.

They were going to the nearby Blackflower Mountain more than ten miles away, and planned to start a campfire there. There were few people and many wild animals there, so it was their newest hunting spot.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

蛋疼, lit. egg (meaning testicles) pain. Bet you always wanted to know that.

Chapter 239: Encounter 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Amidst the sea of dark green trees, there was a thin, pale green roadway. It crawled through the forest like a slow earthworm, wider in some places and narrower in others, twisting and turning unpredictably.

A carriage drove slowly along that road, followed by a team of horseriding bodyguards in black.

The sky was beginning to dim. The setting sun was obscured by layers of thick clouds, only the slightest bit of red light seeping through.

The carriage soon stopped at the end of the road. The old driver steadied it, and turned around to yell,

"This is as far as we can go, the carriage can’t go any further."

"Got it, you can go back now, Old Peter. Come back here to fetch us in two days." The door opened and a young man in tight black clothes jumped out as he spoke loudly.

"Yes, Young Master."

A few more young people dressed luxuriously jumped out of the carriage, two male and two female in total. They were all wearing black clothes that seemed to be for hunting. Their pants legs were stuffed into long breeches, and there were sharp short knives tied to their belts.

"Prynne, where did you guys decide to meet?" the other boy asked casually. He had blonde hair and a handsome face, with a studious air. It was Garen, who had come along with his companions.

"Right over there, we need to walk another distance. Let’s go over there first, I’ll tell a guard to go pick up Aquarius and the others. Do you wanna go along, Cia?" Prynne glanced at Garen.

"It’s fine, I’ll stay with you guys." Garen shook his head. Right now, he was carefully observing his surroundings. "The plants here look pretty old, it does looks like people don’t usually come here."

"Indeed." Prynne looked slightly proud of himself. "I even purposely asked travelling merchants who go out a lot, and finally came up with a place they don’t go. Of course there wouldn’t be anyone here."

"It won’t be dangerous, will it?" Marin was combing her her long maroon hair, and asked worriedly.

"Relax, even if there is something dangerous, we have so many guards here. There’s nothing to be afraid of!" Prynne shrugged, pointing at the team of guards riding behind them. "The people I brought this time are my family’s elite fighters, they’re definitely capable, so you don’t have to worry about safety!"

Prynne walked up to a tall and strong-looking man, with a broad back and thick waist, and patted the man’s chest.

"This is Hanson, he once tore a forest grizzly up alive! He’s the strongest of men! And he’s also the defense captain in charge of our safety this time!"

Hanson was an entire head taller than Prynne, with limbs as thick as an elephant’s. The muscles on his body were about to explode out of his skin-tight armor, keeping anyone who looked at him on edge.

"Leave it to me, Hanson! No problem!" Hanson patted his chest, and flexed his muscles like a bodybuilder. It instantly garnered some laughs from the girls.

Whoa!!

"Hanson!!" "Hanson!!" "Hanson!!"

The guards behind him drew their scimitars at the same time, raising them above their heads as they cheered for their captain.

"Our safety is in your hands, Big Brother Prynne." Andel giggles as she got closer to Prynne.

"Speak for yourself, I still think Cia’s side is more reliable…" On the other hand, Marin walked up to Garen. "Big Brother Cia, you gotta protect me~~" she purposely said flirtily.

"Cia is head over heels trying to get Aquarius, he won’t have time for you." Andel didn’t hold back with her words.

Garen shrugged exasperatedly. "I’ll protect you, relax." He turned around to glance at the middle-aged man standing behind him.

This man was wearing a long-sleeved dark green shirt and similar long pants. He said little to nothing, and wore a metallic black armguard on his forearm. He looked to be in his thirties.

His name was Ulun, the bodyguard his father Vanderman had sent to protect him.

Garen lowered his voice helplessly.

"You guys know it too, Prynne had always been in charge of our safety, and we were too lazy to bother with it ourselves. It’s just that there was a huge explosion in my family’s territory this time, so my father specifically sent someone to protect me.

"So you’re saying this guy is really good?" Marin stuck out her tongue.

Garen nodded.

Ulun was indeed very strong. Even in the previous world of secret martial arts, he wouldn’t be your regular Joe. Judging from the way he walked, his reactions, as well as the killing intect on him and his gaze, he was definitely an elite fighter with several dozen lives on his hands. Only people like these would have that vague sense of disregard and contempt whenever they looked at everyone else.

But Garen never saw Ulun in a fight himself, so he couldn’t quite assess his total abilities. One thing was sure, Ulun might not look like much, but his abilities were definitely no lower than the guard captain Hanson.

Seeing that Garen and Marin were talking about him, Ulun put his right hand on his chest, and bent his head with a smile.

Having more or less introduced the servants, all four of them knew who was who. Hanson took the lead, and the team of guards protected the four of them on both flanks. Only then did the procession continue walking to the edge of the forest.

Axes continuously broke through the bramble, cutting open a path. Snakes, rabbits, and forest mice that darted out occasionally were also cause for the two girls to scream dramatically.

Marin always preferred to stick to Garen, whereas Andel stayed with Prynne.

As the group went further into the forest, the four of them quickly decided on a relatively flat piece of land. The guards started to chop up the bushes and trees nearby, setting up an activity spot.

Hanson and Ulun split up, patrolling the surroundings and chasing away poisonous snakes or bugs.

The four of them had barely stopped to catch their breath when soon they heard the rustle of activity behind them. Someone seemed to have caught up from behind.

Soon, a group of people dressed in dark green approached them quickly.

"It’s Aquarius," Marin whispered beside Garen. Her gaze was slightly complicated, but she hid it well.

Garen looked around him. Prynne, Andel and Marin were all staring at him. He knew he had to do something. After all, the previous Acacia liked Aquarius more than anything else, and even fought with his older cousin who loved him the most over her.

He stood up helplessly, and took the initiative to meet the team.

"Is it Miss Aquarius?" he asked loudly.

"Cia! Is that you?" A response came immediately from the approaching group. The crowd parted, and a girl in white walked out, holding up the hem of her dress. She wore a long one-piece dress, had long dark brown hair over her shoulders, and extremely thick makeup. Garen’s first impression of her was one of those unconventional beauties from Earth.

She had an oval face, with smooth and fair skin. Her eyes were made larger by dark green shadow, forming perfect almond eyes. Her eyebrows seemed to be drawn too, a textbook example of eyebrows like willow leaves, thin, long, and dark green. A straight nose, pink lips. Add that to her thin waist and thick bust, her long legs. There were even dainty crystal pendants hanging from her ears lobes.

At first glance, anyone could see this was a beauty of luxury, and she really knew how to dress herself up. In truth, her real face was nowhere near this level.

But to innocent boys like Acacia, this kind of makeup was more than enough to have him head over heels with her, his eyes stuck to her like glue. Compared to Aquarius, Marin -- who was quite pretty among the four of them, but who didn’t know how to use make-up -- was like the duckling next to the swan."

"It’s been a while since we met. Since I heard you were coming this time, I thought, it’s not like I have anything else to do. Coming to meet you lets me relax at the same time. I wonder, am I welcome here?" Aquarius’ voice was full of calm confidence, giving the impression that she was very in control of herself. It wasn’t too loud or too soft, and even the turns in her voice seemed to be fully calculated.

"You are, of course you are!" Garen imitated Acacia from before, acting completely head over heels for her, his eyes not turning away. He looked as if Aquarius had a hand on his soul. And then he followed Acacia’s actions in his memories, grabbing Aquarius’ hand and making to kiss it. But he was instantly pushed aside.

Impatience flashed past Aquarius’ eyes. Every time Acacia took her hand, he would immediately chew on it for half a day and refuse to let go. So even though she was supposed to stretch out her hand first, she pretended to forget about that.

"Why don’t we first figure out how to make a fire? I have two more friends coming over." Aquarius greeted Prynne, Marin and Andel respectively. There was no faulting her manners.

The five of them began directing the guards to stick the vines and branches that had been chopped off into the ground, forming a simple fence. And then they began to put up each of the tents they brought.

Aquarius’ friends arrived quickly as well. They were two pretty girls, one called Maria and the other Cena. They only brought a couple of guards each, and quickly gathered around Aquarius, chatting merrily.

Garen expressed his love for Aquarius every now and then, acting particularly passionate, but the other party didn’t say even a word to him.

The few tents were set up in no time at all, each of them covered with large nets that had leaves tied to them. This was to camouflage the tents from the eye, merging them into the forest.

The seven or eight guards in total also set up a few large tents a little further ahead for shelter.

While they were putting up camp, Garen took that chance to take a walk around the area to stake out the ground. Marin volunteered to stay with him, and they went on the excuse that they were gathering firewood.

Under Ulun’s protection, the two of them began to gather wood.

"Cia, do you really like Aquarius that much?" Marin asked softly as she gathered the wood.

"Do you still need to ask?" Garen replied simply.

"Then what part of her do you like?"

"I like all of her. Most importantly, don’t you think Aquarius is really beautiful?" Garen copied Acacia’s wods directly. The two of them picked up a few small sticks every few steps. They weren’t gathering firewood at all, but chatting as they took a walk. Behind them, Ulun privately twisted his mouth.

"Then, we’re very close, right?" Marin asked again.

"Of course," Garen replied.

"If… I say if, Aquarius and I fell into the water at the same time, who would you save first?" Marin suddenly asked very solemnly.

"Isn’t it obvious? Aquarius, of course! Don’t you know how to swim?" Garen could also see that Marin liked Acacia, but he was following Acacia’s original memories and impressions to the T. Although this answer was very unlike him, it was the answer that suited Acacia best.

Helplessness flashed past Marin’s eyes, and she became somewhat down.

Garen bent down to pick up a few dried out branches, when suddenly his palm brushed a black-green plant next to him. A small cut immediately opened up on the back of his hand.

He frowned slightly, not at all used to how weak his body was now. He was just about to straighten up when something in the corner of his eye made him freeze.

"This is…!!"

He carefully peeled apart this unknown plant with its sharp leaves, revealing a small purple-black flower underneath.

"This is… the amejade1 grass!" Garen’s heart began to race. "This world… This world has that legendary, supposedly extinct amejade grass!!"

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

紫璐草 lit. purple jade grass. Amejade as combination of amethyst and jade because purple be mainstream.

Chapter 240: Encounter 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As the ultimate fighter in the previous world, who scoured through a sea of secret technique manuals and handbooks, Garen could still remember that many of his predecessors had recorded several medicine recipes that could strengthen the body and mind in their fighting journals. Most of these had mysterious and impressive effects.

Unfortunately, these records came from the far distant past, and so many ingredients couldn’t be find. Even those that were discovered proved to be from a different time, and simply weren’t old enough. That was why they had to give up reluctantly.

But this amejade grass happened to be one of the core ingredients in one of those ancient recipes.

These recipes had been added onto the handbooks he had found. Back then, Garen had basically memorized everything in it for the heck of it. After all, with the help of his special power, he didn’t have to worry about his memory in the slightest. To think that he would actually find a precious herb that was allegedly long extinct here like this.

"Good stuff…" Garen’s expression didn’t change as he scanned the ground around the area. Unbelievably, he found two stalks of amejade grass underneath another one of these plants with sharp leaves.

"If I can match this with the pills and solutions on those ancient recipes and then use it on myself, I’ll definitely be able to drastically reduce the recovery time. There might be even be an even stronger effect!"

As for judging the age of this amejade grass, he compared it to the information recorded in the manuals and knew for sure it had at least a thousand years’ of history! The medicinal effect of something like this would be extremely potent, without a doubt.

"I can’t let anyone notice anything different." Garen acted nonchalant as he stood up, and continued chatting with Marin on the way back to the campground. He put the firewood he had gathered in a pile with the rest, but inside he had memorized the exact location where he discovered the amejade grass.

Right now he was impatient to check around this forest, and see what other undiscovered precious herbs this world had in store.

And even more than that, he wanted to see what medicines he could match up besides the amejade grass. If he could find everything on that recipe, then it wouldn’t be much of a hassle at all to rapidly regain his secret technique strength in a short period of time.

"Ahh!! Snake!!"

Just as he sat down to rest and was planning to find an excuse later to dig up those herbs, he suddenly heard the surprised screams of Aquarius and the other two girls in the distance.

He thought it over quickly, and dashed towards Aquarius. At the same time, he observed carefully.

Aquarius and her girl friends were running over to his side in a panic. Unlike her two friends, however, Aquarius only seemed flustered, running as she held up her skirt. When he looked closely at the panic in his eyes, he realized it was ever so slightly fake.

Garen took another look at her steps. They were obviously very steady. They looked messy, but in truth, it would be very hard for her to trip.

"So she isn’t a normal person…" He took a few steps forward, acting lustful, and reached his arms out to hug Aquarius’ waist.

Oh dear!

Aquarius was suddenly tripped by something, and fell into the arms of Prynne, who had just made it here and stood right next to Garen.

"Sorry, I didn’t hurt you, did I?" she said softly to Prynne, with tears in her eyes.

"I… I’m fine." Prynne blushed, and replied with a stammer.

Beside him, Garen snorted and rushed forward.

"Aquarius, are you okay? Are you hurt anywhere, did you get bitten anywhere? I’ll suck it out for you with my mouth, don’t be shy now, if you’re bitten by a poisonous snake then it has to be sucked up by mouth! Otherwise, you might get infected, or poisoned! You’ll fall into the crutches of illness!"

"It’s… It’s fine… Hehe." Aquarius rejected him with a slightly annoyed expression. She suddenly realized that Cia was being harder to deal with today than before. "Even if I was bitten, you’re a man. Using your mouth to… is not right, is it?"

"At times like these I’m just your doctor, and you’re merely my patient! There’s nothing to feel bad about! Of everyone present here, I believe only I’m the best at sucking out snake poison, and this is for your safety as well! Otherwise if the poison gets into your body, you might get seriously hurt, grow really sick, or even end up handicapped!" Garen said with an air of truth and justice. He wanted Aquarius to push him away of her own accord, in order to avoid further complications.

"It’s not so serious, is it…" Everyone around them fell speechless, including Prynne. But it was obvious that Acacia was deliberately exaggerating the effects, so no one stepped out to say anything.

"It’s okay, I wasn’t bitten…" Aquarius wondered if she’d attracted a big pain in the neck, as she stood up from Prynne’s embrace.

"Is that so? That’s too ba.... Good! Hehe… heheh…" Garen purposely said that extra half a word, causing Aquarius to shudder. "Oh, right, Miss Acacia, while you’re injured now, do you want to hear the poem I wrote for you?" He quickly pulled a small black book from his pocket.

"T-there’s no need…" Once he mentioned the poem, Aquarius instantly looked somewhat uneasy. "I’m very grateful for your praise, but I don’t feel very well right now, could you let me rest a little?"

"Where are you feeling uncomfortable, milady?1" Garen took a step forward, and said with a straight face, "I just learned some massaging techniques, I’ll definitely make your uncomfortable parts feels better! I can massage you right now!"

Aquarius said helplessly,

"I’m just a bit tired, and I want to take a short nap. Could you spare me that little bit of time? I know you, sir, are a gentleman who cares for the ladies, right?"

"Is that so?" Garen purposely looked disappointed. "In that case… Okay, I’ll be right around here. If you need me for anything, you can ask me whenever! I’ll be here in an instant!"

"Yes, I’ll do that!" Aquarius reached out her hand to lightly push aside the hair on Garen’s forehead, "Don’t wear yourself out too much, you rest well too."

When the icy cold fingertip touched Garen’s forehead, in that instant, their skin both jolted ever so slightly.

"Hm?" Aquarius’ eyes flashed with surprise. Only expert fighters and killers would have the basic instinct to dodge when the vital point in the middle of the brow was touched. But why would this aristocratic boy with zero skills or talents have such a response?

Perhaps her fingers were too cold? She guessed inwardly.

Garen also noticed that he had blown his cover slightly, but maintained that lovesick expression on his face, at the same time reaching out his hand to grab Aquarius’. Unfortunately, he missed.

"Go rest." Aquarius smiled sat him, then turned around and walked towards her own tent.

Garen remained on the spot, staring at Aquarius’ back, stupid with love. His gaze very obviously and vulgarly fell to her swinging, round buttocks. And his uninhibited, heated gaze was also evidently picked up Aquarius herself.

She felt as though even the skirt couldn’t block those lustful eyes from her butt, goosebumps rising all over her body. Even her steps towards the tent became more hurried.

Garen only heaved a sigh of relief when Aquarius entered the tent.

When facing cunning women like this, the simplest and most direct method would be to be direct enough, and vulgar enough. As long as the other party still cared about their body, this tactic would surely have a decent result. He could force her into a panic, and make her unwilling to see him.

Garen was well aware of his socializing skills. If he were to turn circles with her, he would surely be sold before he knew it. Rather than using his weakness to fight the opponent’s strength, it was better to solve this matter directly in a manner that suited him best.

This was also related to his martial spirit. Once he got hold of the slightest flaw, he would chase it relentlessly and hit it ferociously. He wouldn’t give the enemy the slightest chance!

The group ate the rations they had brought for dinner on that first evening. At night, they lit a campfire, while Prynne recited Cia’s love poem out loud. Evidently, other than the other three people in his gang cheering loudly, the rest of the audience looked constipated.2 But they still had to clap and cheer against their conscience.

Aquarius and her two girl friends, on the other hand, ducked into the tent and hid out of ‘embarrassment’. The others looked as though they were used to it. It seemed this wasn’t the first time she used this trick.

Garen kept thinking about those few shrubs of amejade grass, and so seemed distracted as well. The others just assumed he was thinking about Aquarius, so it fit.

As for whether or not Aquarius was a Luminarist, he couldn’t be sure. Luminarists weren’t like the Martial Adepts, they didn’t have absurdly strong Spirits, and usually they looked just like everyone else. Until the very last moment before the explosion, nobody knew who was a Luminarist.

But upon seeing her face-to-face, Garen was sure of one thing. Aquarius wasn’t very proactive in chasing Acacia. She was just simply toying with him, rather than purposely pulling him closer. Even if she did have a motive like that, she wasn’t taking it too seriously.

If that’s the extent of it, then everything is still fine.

**************

Inside Aquarius’ tent.

Frowning deeply, Aquarius put her legs together as she sat inside the tent. Looking at her two girl companions in front of her.

"This Acacia, how did he suddenly become so disgusting? At first he was pretty gentlemanly, and here I was thinking he had patience, but to think he’s as impatient as other men! No, he was even more direct!"

Maria had a head of long milk-white hair, giving off a spoiled and unreasonable aura. She curled her long hair nonchalantly, acting slightly detached.

"Aren’t all men alike? Big Sister Aquarius, you’re the one who wanted to play around too much. Wouldn’t it be fine if you hadn’t attracted him in the first place?"

"I had no choice, wasn’t it a request from above? Otherwise why would I butt my head in here for no reason, I’m bored out of my socks!" Aquarius glared at her. "Unlike you, I have a good father and mother!"

"Hey hey hey, don’t bring me into this!" Cena protested from the side. "But I kinda think this Acacia isn’t too bad. Love should be direct and intense! What’s the point of turning around in circles and hiding everything! If you like someone, you should say it out loudly, and show your heart to the other person without any hiding!"

She said nonchalantly.

Cena had dark brown shoulder-length hair. Her air was completely that of a pure and kind girl next door, and she was very beautiful too. She should be the youngest among the three, looking no older than nineteen years old.

Her skin was fair with a flush, but her figure was slightly less impressive that the other two. Her chest was just enough to touch, and so didn’t match up to everyone’s sense of beauty when it came to body figures.

"He’s much better than the guy my dad arranged for me." Cena pouted and took out a small mirror, quickly combing through her hair ands pushing her fringe into a right-side slope.

"If you like him, just take him." Aquarius was exasperated. "But I really can’t… Cena… Give me your father, could you?"

"If you want me, take him yourself," Cena replied carelessly. She pursed her lips and reflected it on both sides in the mirror, as though not too happy with her image.

But neither of the girls noticed the flash in Aquarius’ eyes when mentioning Acacia earlier.

She had suddenly remembered that scene from earlier, the reaction when her finger touched Acacia’s forehead.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. He referred to her with the formal version of ‘you’ (您), also used for customers.

2. This time, he literally said ‘constipated’ (便秘), so yeah.

Chapter 241: Upgrade 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Aquarius snapped her fingers lightly, her eyes narrowing.

"Big Sister, what are you thinking about?" Cena asked from beside her.

"It’s nothing. I’ll go out for a walk, you guys go ahead and sleep." Aquarius stood, opened the entrance to the tent, and walked out.

There was a smattering of guards standing around outside, and she could hear the voices of Prynne and the others talking beside a distant stream. The day was getting darker, only the campside fireplace was getting brighter.

Aquarius greeted a few guards, and took a female guard with her to the bushes, acting as though she was going to answer the call of nature.

That way, she avoided any other curious gazes.

She walked into the bushes, and looked at the shrubs surrounding her, all about as tall as half a person.

"You go look out around here," she said to the female guard softly.

"Yes."

Once she was alone, Aquarius flicked her finger. Two dots of blue light instantly flew out of her fingertips, falling into the bushes, flickering in and out of view. Like two small fireflies.

"Go and test that Acacia," she mouthed the orders.

The blue firefly lights immediately and lightly darted into the bushes, and utterly disappeared.

Standing on the same spot, Aquarius looked thoughtful.

　*****************

The excuse was they went out to gather firewood again, and decided to take a stroll at the same time. With Ulun in tow, Garen once more sauntered to the position from earlier.

Carefully he walked to the border of where the amejade grass was, and started patrolling while acting nonchalant.

Soon enough, he found a pinweed near the amejade grass. It had large leaves and a thick stem, which meant it was quite matured in years as well.

The pinweed was another more commonly used medicinal ingredient. Garen silently recorded this piece of information.

Then he started patrolling again. Ulun followed closely behind him, but didn’t know what he was doing.

In this whole area of the forest, Garen continuously found about a dozen more amejade grasses. There were comparatively fewer pinweeds, only three in all. He was feeling increasingly more satisfied.

After taking a few more rounds in the surrounding forest, the sky had gradually darkened until he couldn’t even see properly. Only then did Garen decide to head back.

They were standing on a slope, surrounded by thickets of trees and bushes. Without realizing it, they had wandered far away from the campsite.

As the light dimmed, the forest became a sea of darkness. Even the green trees and plants looked inky in the shadows.

"Young master, what on earth are you looking for?" Ulun asked out of boredom from behind Garen.

"My cousin likes herbs and flowers, so I thought I’d look for some that she might like, and bring them back to her." Garen answered casually, "It’s just that we’ll be out for a few days, so even though I already singled out some targets, it’s pointless if we dug them out too early."

Ulun nodded in understanding. Suddenly, he reached out his hand to grab a little green snake that was pouncing at Garen.

His palm deftly and accurately pinched the snake seven inches from its head.1 With a light press, the little snake immediately hissed, and the seventh inch was immediately flattened. He then casually flung the snake onto the floor.

Only then did Garen act like he was belatedly scared.

"It’s another leaf snake! Why are there so many snakes in this forest! If you hadn’t discovered it so early, this one would have bitten me!"

"It’s nothing, this place is obviously a suitable habitat for leaf snakes, it’s nothing much if there are a few more than usual. No matter how poisonous a snake is, it doesn’t matter if it can’t bite anyone," Ulun said calmly.

Suddenly a dot of blue floated towards the two of them. It was a small blue snake, looking lazy as it slithered, its movements slow and smooth.

Garen and Ulun both saw that snake.

"What snake is that?" Garen asked, frowning.

"I’m not sure either, if it’s blue it should be a blue-scaled snake, but these sort of surroundings shouldn’t be very conducive for this type of snake." Ulun frowned slightly too. "Be careful, this type of snake moves very quickly, and it has a lot of explosive power as well. You back down first."

"Okay." Hearing that, Garen immediately hid behind Ulun’s back.

Ulun put on black leather gloves, his expression somewhat solemn. The blue-scaled snake’s skin was hard and it moved fast, so it wasn’t an easy adversary. He had also been a wandering warrior before, living off bounty money, so he was used to living in forests like these. But even then, he found this slightly challenging.

It’d be fine if he was alone, but there was a young master behind him that he had to protect, so that made things a bit harder.

"There shouldn’t be blue-scaled snakes here, right?" he asked inwardly, as he stared at the lazy blue snake.

It was a little fella not half a meter long. It seemed to have noticed the two in front of it too, so it looked up and hissed softly, as though warning the two of them to get out of its way.

"We should leave her slowly," Ulun said softly. "Be slow, don’t rush."

"Okay."

The two of them slowly move to the left.

Suddenly a blue spark erupted out of nowhere, headed straight for Ulun’s face.

The blue spark shot out of the blue-scaled snake’s mouth, and carved a thin blue line through the air, beautiful and crystallite. At the same time, a foul odor wafted through the area, as though this whole place had suddenly become drainage.

Just as the blue spark was about to hit Ulun’s face, he abruptly raised his right hand and held it in front of his face.

Pff!

The blue spark landed on his glove, and immediately made an eroding hissing sound. It was evidently a spray of thick blue poison.

"Run!!" Ulun howled, quickly taking off his glove, and immediately tossing out a thin dagger. However, the blue-scaled snake instantly dodged it.

One man and one snake faced off with each other, neither willing to be distracted.

As soon as Garen heard the yell, he set off at a run towards the campsite. There were a lot of guards there, so there wouldn’t be any big problems as long as he reached there. There were old hands and experts at dealing with snakes among the guards.

The forest ahead of him was rapidly retreating, his legs rustling through the bushes. Garen did not pause for even a moment.

The reactions and speed that Ulun and the blue-scaled snake demonstrated earlier, as well as their accuracy, had achieved an extremely high level. There was no way Garen could avoid the blue-scaled snake’s poison without revealing his true abilities.

Behind him, Ulun yelled again, but the sound was coming from further away. Evidently the distance between them had gradually increased.

Garen quickly ran forward, but he relaxed slightly inside. He gradually slowed down, wanting to turn around and take a look.

Pff!

Suddenly, a blue shadow pounced from behind a tree branch, coming straight for his face. Before it even touched him, he could already smell an intense stench like from before.

"It’s not a coincidence!!" Garen instantly understood inside, that someone was purposely trying to test him. He didn’t think much about it, but purposely tripped underfoot.

"Oh, no!" he yelled out, and fell towards the right, just in time to avoid the attack of the blue shadow.

With a smack, the blue shadow rammed into a white stone on the ground, and the stone immediately split apart.

Garen half-sat on the ground, and only then did he clearly see what it was.

It was the same type of blue-scaled snake as before!

The blue-scaled snake’s head had been bruised, but there wasn’t any blood leaking out. It stared at Garen, its long sleek body slowly and gracefully slithering towards him.

Garen acted as though he was extremely terrified. He didn’t even dare to move, just half sitting on the ground, staring at the blue-scaled snake slithering towards him in horror.

Strangely, he could actually see something familiar in this snake’s eyes.

"That is…" Suspicion rose in Garen’s heart.

Just then, the blue-scaled snake suddenly stopped, as though attracted by something, and the it turned around to head towards another direction. Totally ignoring Garen.

Garen slowly got up, putting on a pale face, but the confusion in his heart grew.

In the forest far away, Aquarius was also suspicious as she looked at the returning blue-scaled snake.

"That’s a very normal reaction, but that fall was too coincidental…" she frowned slightly, looking down at the black paper scroll in her hand. "Forget it, let’s get the important things done first."

*************

Trejon Estate, Vanderman Tower.

In the red and brown study room.

Vanderman was sitting opposite a person in black robes. The oil lamp on the table beside them emitted a dim but quiet yellow light, forming a yellow halo that was just big enough to cover both of them. Outside the yellow circle, everything was dark.

"What are you guys here for this time? Just tell it to me straight." Vanderman crossed his fingers, his expression calm.

"Old friend, I really don’t want to see you stray off the path like this." The person in black had a deep voice, a man’s voice. "You and I have worked together all these years, but at a pivotal time like now, you end up messing up like this. Even I will find it hard to smoothen this out for you."

His voice was calm and slow, but his attitude was dead serious.

Vanderman frowned and shook his head.

"This isn’t my problem. Yes, the cargo was intercepted on my territory, but my control at the borders is too weak. You can’t put all the responsibility on me." He paused. "There were three covers for this round of cargos’ shipment routes. After taking so many twists and turns, there was still someone who could accurately comprehend the border shipment routes…"

"Indeed there is a traitor, but that is not the point here." The man in black shook his head, "The point is, someone who wants to make a move on your territory, can make a move on your territory. And even more importantly, someone kept silent and allowed this behavior. Everyone kept silent, that’s the main point."

Vanderman fell quiet, his hand falling onto the chair’s armrest and gripping it tightly.

The man in black’s voice had a hint of pity.

"We’re considered old friends now. Because of this matter, the branches are very unhappy with you. If you still do not decide…"

"I am a royal Luminarist!" Vanderman interrupted him, his voice deep.

"Royal…" The man in black was slightly disappointed. "Is that your decision? And here I thought you had understood the situation, to think…" He stood up. "Forget it, just pretend I was never here."

He turned around and walked towards the darkness outside the yellow circle.

"Tonci, I haven’t forgotten about everything in the past. I hope you haven’t either," Vanderman said suddenly.

"I have long since stopped being the Tonci from before." The man in black stopped, and replied calmly.

"The royal family will not lose!" Vanderman said determinedly.

"But the royal family does not represent everything." The man in black strode into the darkness, and instantly disappeared into the shadows. There wasn’t the sound of an opening door, or footsteps. He integrated into the darkness like a breeze, disappearing without a trace.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

There is a Chinese belief that snakes have their hearts seven inches from their heads, so that would be their fatal spot.

Chapter 242: Upgrade 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Although the halo of light from the oil lamp was snuffed out, the bedroom remained strangely illuminated.

Moonlight crept in from the window and bathed the carpet.

Vanderman was sitting on a chair, quietly, with a rather perplexed expression on his face.

"The royal family still has us and the three major departments! It’s impossible for us to lose!" He murmured.

At some corner of in a forest far away from the manor lied a person dressed in black. He was none other than Tonci.

He turned his head around and looked at the Trejons’ manor.

"You and I have done our duties, Vanderman."

"Have we failed?" Another black figure slowly crept up alongside him from the dark. "I knew it, that old man had placed his hopes in the royal alliance. His household was in a predicament in the past, but he was blessed by the Kovitan’s eldest prince. He had sworn loyalty to the royal family, to never betray them. To suddenly have that happen would be a miracle."

"Nothing can be done. We’ve failed. Have some consideration and stop harping on it." Tonci said coldly.

"Whatever. The split doesn’t favor Vanderman from the get go anyway. Now that you, his only old friend, has given up on him, his life will not be that easy."

"That is his decision. Let’s go." Tonci replied coldly.

Both of them went into a corner away from the moonlight, and disappeared into the darkness without a sound.

*************

Cia seemed to be shocked by the blue-scaled snake during his two days in the campsite, and lived his days in the tent with a very pale face. He didn’t even dare to go near Aquarius and flatter her.

Occasionally, Prynne and Marin would come and accompany him. Garen didn’t even participate in the group hunt, his excuse being that he was feeling unwell.

However, everyone knew that he was actually traumatized by the blue-scaled snake. He was almost bitten by the venomous blue-scaled snake, which had the lethal potential to kill a man. No one could blame him, anyone would have required some time to recover if they had a brush with death.

On top of that, it was a natural reaction from the spoiled Acacia.

Garen took this opportunity to bring Ulun out to search for different kinds of known herbal medicines in this wide area. He didn’t have much knowledge in this field as he hadn’t specialised it in this practice. However, he knew enough knowledge in herbal medicine to get by.

He explored at least a thousand-square-meter wide area, and hence, two days had passed in the blink of an eye, and it was already time to head back. Garen had finally dug up all the herbal medicine that he was searching for.

Amejade grass, pinweed and giant roc flowers were the ingredients he had been looking for in this journey. These were essentially ancient herbs, but it was obvious that these people treated them as a common weeds. Some of the ingredients even let slip that they had been stepped on.

Garen estimated that he would be able to successfully conjure up to three kinds of herbal soups with these ingredients. It was unfortunate that there were a lot more ingredients that he wasn’t able to find, so he wasn’t sure how effective the overall medicine might be.

He filled the exquisite wooden box that was used to pack meals with soil and planted the herbs into these small boxes. They became makeshift planters.

**********

Early in the morning, at the entrance of the road just beside the forest.

A few carriages were parked on both sides of the road, and a few bodyguards, in either white or black shirts, were engaged in conversation.

Prynne was ordering the guards to move the beasts they had hunted onto the car beside the carriage, while the remaining ladies were chatting and giggling over to the side.

Aquarius was standing in the shade under a tree, as she gazed at the rest of the people moving camping equipment into the carriage. She then had her sight on the Trejons Household’s black carriage, and she looked at the bodyguards, carrying stacks of exquisite wooden boxes onto the carriage.

As she looked at the emblem of the Trejons Household, it reminded her of the results of her probes from earlier.

She hesitated for a moment as she looked at a guard in white, who was standing by a carriage not far away from her.

She flicked her fingers, and a blue colored flash appeared at the tip of her finger.

The curtains on the carriages were pulled down and a female guard in white came down from the carriage. Two of them whispered to each other for a moment before approaching the Trejons carriage together.

Garen was inside the carriage, carefully securing the small boxes to one corner with ropes. When he opened the carriage’s curtain, he saw Aquarius and two of her personal guards whispering among themselves.

His heart threatened to jump.

"Could it be that those two blue-scaled snakes from earlier on…" He could faintly feel that the smell of those two snakes and Aquarius’s smell were rather similar. Perhaps fragrance would be a better choice of word. "If the incident was man made… It’s most likely Aquarius’s doing."

He squinted his eyes as he gently touched his wooden boxes with his hands.

"The blue-scaled snakes are extremely fast and venomous. I can only handle two of them at best, since I am a martial artist who doesn’t focus on speed. With more than two, I can only avoid them. I’ll see how it goes when I regain some of my strength after drinking the herbal soup."

Based on his estimations, a typical Luminarist with an average threat level was at least level C and above. They might be able to reach level B if they really had a go at it. The Luminarist who were fighting against teacher Emin was definitely at least level B during his final struggle. This were just typical Luminarists, imagine the stronger ones.

"The only way to hasten my learning process to become a Luminarist, is to increase my physical attributes and recover as soon as possible!" As Garen recalled the details of the ambush; he was sure that it was a setup. The only person here who was capable of such a feat was Aquarius.

"I will remember this…" Garen closed the curtain.

***********

Back in the Trejons manor.

Garen noticed that Vanderman’s mood was getting worse lately.

According to the female housekeeper, Vanderman’s mood was affected by a letter he had received.

He had his suspicions, the only thing that could affect Vanderman’s mood was the situation involving the Luminarists.

Garen didn’t think much of it as it would be a better option for him to increase his own strength than to conjure a plan at this point in time.

He could only rely on himself during this chaotic period.

It took him three days to treat and cultivate all the medicinal herbs that he brought back, which were considered fairly simple tasks. Due to his inexperience, he had broken some of the roots of the herbs during the cultivation process and he felt quite saddened by it.

After that, he followed the ancient method in mixing the herbs together and stored them nicely into packets.

The final step was to soak them in the medicinal bath.

It wasn’t easy to collect the herbs. He managed to follow an ancient recipe to create something called Endurance Liquid.

The source was unknown, its main effect was of a simple enhancement and supplement to the body. It only required one whole day of brewing in fire.

Garen hid in his building for that whole day as he carefully set the fire up. He kept adding in water every once in awhile to prevent it from drying up. He stopped the whole process when there was a faint, sticky green mud appearing in the herbs.

The whole building was completely filled with the slightly pungent smell of the herbal soup.

Every female servant was told to leave by him, hence he was operating this process all on his own. The reason for this was of course to keep it as a secret. As for Vanderman, a father that always went out early in the morning and only came back late at night, he would only be in the manor during the unearthly hours of the day. The building was filled with a strange aroma, The servants had no idea what he had been up to, let alone Vanderman.

Garen took five full days to brew the herbs into ointments. He placed them into three small jade green bottle since the day he came back from the camp.

*******

Garen told the servants to carry the bath tub into his own room, pour in some hot water, light up the fireplace and close the curtain.

Then, they delivered and the towel and body wash in a wooden basin.

"Alright that’s more than enough. Get out, the lot of you!" Garen hushed them.

"Do you want us to add in the hot water for you?" An old lady servant asked.

"That’ll be fine. I will do it by myself."

"Alright then. Please be careful not to fall asleep inside the bathtub young master Acacia." The lady servant warned him with care.

"I got it, Anna." Garen nodded his head. "Please don’t disturb me. I need to realize some inspirations during my bath!"

Whenever Acacia reminded the servants about his poetry, the old servant, Anna, who had been watching Acacia since young, could even feel a chill in her nerves whenever he talked about his poetry.

"Then I shall take my leave. Please take your time to realize your inspirations." She forced out a smile and then gestured the rest of the female servants to leave the room before she closed the door gently.

Garen walked towards the door and locked the door with a chain.

As the sound of the footsteps gradually disappeared, only the crackling sound of the burning wood inside the room could be heard.

Garen walked towards the study desk gently and took out a palm sized emerald green glass bottle from the drawer. As he swung the bottle, the green liquid which was as viscous as the royal jelly was flowing gently in the bottle.

He walked towards the bathtub, opened the bottle cap and gently tilted the bottle.

Bloop!

A drop of viscount liquid went into the crystal clear hot water and swiftly dyed the hot water into faint green like an ink mixing in clear water.

He then poured the remaining viscous liquid into the bathtub. He even rinsed the bottle in the hot water to ensure there were no remnants left behind. It was only then that Garen took off his clothes, stepped onto the stool and entered the bathtub.

As he soaked his whole body inside the hot bath, it was no different than soaking in a normal hot bath, other than the pungent medicinal odor.

Garen took a deep breath, shut his eyes and immediately immersed himself completely into the water.

As the water splashed about, the sounds he heard were similar to being covered with a thick cloth. Everything sounded so far away, and was very quiet.

Garen recalled the ancient preparation method, using his index fingers and placing them on the other side of the shoulders to form a gesture which resembled him hugging himself. He started to expand and contract his chest periodically as he completely soaked himself in the water.

This was the most basic breathing technique from the Divine Statue Technique, which was used to build the foundation and train his skin, blood and qi. However, the original method did not require one to use any medicine for assistance. Garen was merely using the endurance liquid as the catalyst.

As he immersed himself inside the water, he occasionally got out of the water to catch a breath. This process continued for quite a while. He did not feel anything untoward happening to his body.

What he felt when he was immersing himself was that the water was getting hotter over time. It was as if there was someone who kept adding more wood under the bathtub to increase the temperature. The water’s temperature was getting higher, and getting hotter over time.

The green pigment in the water became fainter as the water started to clear up over time.

Garen’s skin started to become green at this point.

Splash.

As Garen came out of the water for the fifth time, he wiped off the water that was on his face and opened his eyes.

"It’s getting hotter… This endurance liquid had proven itself. According to the ancient documents, the endurance liquid was one of the basic medicines for the Emerald Jade Panacea. It was unfortunate that it was a lost art and this medicine was now primarily used for body enhancement." Garen sighed repentantly. The Emerald Jade Panacea was similar in theory, compared to the Divine Statue Technique’s White Gold Divine Statue. However, its specialty was not focused on defense and recovery, but full immunity to toxins and increasing of one’s lifespan.

He was unsure of the effect when he used the breathing technique from the Divine Statue Technique to absorb the medicine into his body. He had to give all of his attention to the breathing technique and thus he did not see the changes in the attributes pane.

He was slightly stunned as he looked at the attribute pane just below his sight.

The attribution pane had an overall increase without his knowledge.

Chapter 243: Approach 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

‘Strength 1.1, Agility 1.0, Vitality 1.2, Intelligence 0.6, Potential 1872%. Possess the qualities of a Luminarist.’

What made him even happier was the skill pane right below.

‘Precision Blueprint: Not Learnt. (Max Level: 3)’ There was a faint red symbol at the end of the sentence. It was the basic requirement for an increment via attribute points.

Garen had not noticed the symbol at the beginning as the skill Precision Blueprint was grey, which indicated that it could not be increased.

He quickly set his sights onto the faint red symbol for three seconds.

The symbol’s meaning appeared in his mind.

‘Requirement to learn Precision Blueprint: Intelligence 0.6, Vitality 1.1, Agility 1.0, Strength 1.0’

Garen finally understood that it was his weak physical body that forbid him to enter the beginner-level of the skill. If he were to purely follow the traditional learning path, he could only fulfill this requirement after understanding the theories, go through lots of practice and ensure that the body was used to it. What’s shocking was that this was the requirement to enter the beginner level, and it would required at least half a year.

"Luminarists really do hold up to their name… This needs four different kinds of attributions." Without any hesitation, Garen set his sights onto the Precision Blueprint.

The skill’s word moved slightly and went out of focus. When it crept back into clarity, it had already changed its form.

‘Precision Blueprint: Beginner-level (Total of three levels: Beginner Level, Intermediate- Level, Master-level.’

Cool air flowed out of Garen’s brain and entered both of his arms.

He suddenly felt that his agility and speed had went up a notch as he reached out and moved his hands.

"According to the manual, it would need half a year to reach this level. On top of that, continuous training and learning in between." He nodded satisfactorily.

Every Luminarist was a master of Precision Blueprint. Only when one became a master of the former skill could he unlock the beginner-level studies of the Luminarist, which was also the basis of tactics.

Even now, countless Luminarists-to-be ceaselessly practise this basic technique; they were mastering the Precision Blueprint via repetition.

Garen used the towel to clean his body and put on a bathrobe as he slowly got out of the bathtub. He stood still and closed his eyes, slowly moving his lower body. He was performing the most basic technique from the White Cloud Gate.

What was supposed to be the White Mammoth from the White Cloud Gate technique looked totally different than it should be. It became some sort of technique that used palm techniques as a base, after it had merged together with the Divine Statue Technique.

"East King Hand!!"

Garen pushed both of his palms forward with all his might, and two high pitched noise were generated from the air. The transparent air condensed for a bit before disappearing right after.

He shook his head in disappointment as he withdrew his hands.

"Looks like I still can’t use the actual secret technique."

He had come up with four of his strongest secret techniques from merging multiple battle skills from his past life. They were the East King Hand, West Phoenix Fist, Southern Double Fist and Northern Capturing Hand. These four strongest techniques were derived from his understanding and experience in martial arts. It was his martial arts life’s work.

When combined, these secret techniques produced massively different results.

His martial arts overall structure went something like this.

The first tier were his four strongest techniques.

The second tier was the combinations of techniques such as: Red Jade Thousand Mammoth Spring. This type of technique had the momentum of the Thousand Mammoth Traction, coupled with the effects of the Red Jade Palm.

The third tier were different types of battle skills that he freely used. The strongest among this tier was his integrated Mammoth technique of the White Cloud Gate, Thousand Mammoth Traction, third form.

The last one was the typical sleight of hand such as Capturing Hand, Combination Fist, Palm Knife, etc.

Garen sat by the study desk and penned a few lines onto white paper.

‘Four major tiers. First: Ultimate Technique, second: Secret Technique, third: Normal Technique, forth: Sleight of Hand.’

"Since the day I practice martial arts in the White Cloud Gate, I have not lost to anyone other than Sylphalan." Garen’s gaze became dim as he recalled his two battles against Palosa. He started to feel emotional all of a sudden. "The Secret Techniques cannot possibly have this little strength…"

He was unwilling to accept the fact that there was a huge difference in strength between Secret Technique and the Luminarists. One relied on the user’s own strength whereas the other used the strength from an external source. It was similar to comparing martial artists and sages in the legends of China. The difference between them was too huge!

On a whim, Garen started writing all the secret techniques that he had learnt on the piece of paper.

The Four Major Secret Techniques were written at the front, as these four techniques were the result of combining secret techniques and battle skills. Each of these skills required complicated techniques and aura to execute. These techniques suited Garen best, as no one could possible have learnt such a technique, even if he taught them step by step.

Garen, who had practiced martial arts for such a long time, had accumulated boundless experience. He would obviously feel dissatisfied when secret techniques became insignificant all of a sudden. Releasing the emotions that were welling up inside him, he had listed down all the possible routes that he could take on the piece of paper.

Half an hour later…

Garen finally exhaled and placed down his pencil helplessly. He felt a sense of disappointment as he looked at the white paper, densely packed with handwriting.

"Is there no other path?" He muttered. He stood up, opened the window and allowed the cold night air to blow onto him and freshen up his spirit.

"No… There must be a way." This thought flashed through his mind as he looked up at the full moon in the sky, the disappointment within his gaze slowly turning to calm.

"My strength has recovered to the third tier, which is a little stronger than before. If I compare it to the handbook…" He took out the handbook, which was given by teacher Emin, from the drawer.

Black words littered the plain yellow pieces of paper, all of which were handwritten notes by teacher Emin.

Garen flipped it to the last few pages, which was where the remarks were located. There, it was clearly written:

-- Luminarist levels are very strict. However, understanding this is meaningless for you now. I have written down how we Luminarists categorise you commoners.

We Luminarists grade ourselves as Silver Level. Anyone below us would be categorised under Commoner Level. The following was the categorisation for the commoners.

Comoner Levels can be broken down into four levels: Master-level, General-level, Guardian-level and soldier-level.

A Soldier-level can fight against ten people, a Guardian-level can fight against a hundred people and a General-level can fight against five hundred people. However, they can be of different types and each has their pros and cons. A Master-level can fight against a thousand people and can completely overwhelm a General-level. They are, under any circumstances, at the peak of the Commoner Level. This is the limit of a commoner.

As for Luminarists, in theory they should not be affected by the Common Level, and they should not be a threat to a Luminarist. The attacks of a non-Luminarist to a Luminarist is very minor, and can even be considered negligible. You can ask your father to prove this point to you.

Only a Luminarist who has managed to completely forge his own totem and light his White Luminescence is officially a Silver Level Luminarist. At this point in time, do not reveal. --

There was another remark at the very back.

-- Do not tell your father that you are learning from me. Do not forget your promise. The moment you graduate is the moment I have fully cleared my life debt towards you. --

Garen closed the handbook, and he also knew why his teacher was reminding him so.

Emin didn’t know why he had approached him to learn the ways of the Luminarist, and he didn’t care for the reason he wanted to pursue this path. He merely treated this teaching experience as a trade. Perhaps he might have reasons to want to protect himself. He had considered some aspects in detail, but ultimately, this was just a trade.

He stowed away his thoughts, followed the instructions recorded in the handbook, and started to estimate his strength.

"Based on the categorisation here, when I was at my peak with my Divine Statue Technique, I should be in the Master-level, which was the peak of the Commoner Level. The current me who had just slightly recovered should be at Soldier-level."

He knew that the person that the writing was referring to was the standardised elite soldier who had undergone training. The elite soldiers in this world were slightly stronger than the previous world.

He was no more than a soldier-level at his current strength and his secret technique.

He could only handle three blue-scaled snakes from that day. Forget about going against Guardian-levels or above; the General-levels and Master-levels respectively.

Even his father Vanderman’s strongest underlings were at the peak of the Guardian-level. The distance to becoming a Master-level was still far away.

"A mere Soldier-level, the lowest rank of all?" Garen looked at his hands as he felt his strength was constantly recovering. That was the soul’s ability changing the structure of this body, which was a slow and irreversible process. Since it was a change from nought to one, the process required was slow and lengthy. "So weak… but only for now. If I were to use all three medicines, I will soon recover my physical attributes. I am currently constrained by my physical attributes, and I can’t use most of my strength. My strength will recover tremendously if I can reach the threshold."

He turned his head around and looked at the crystal clear water in the bathtub.

"I should be able to recover to a decent level, and no longer remain at Soldier-level when I fully absorb these three medicines. The next step will be to do repetitive practising."

***************

Northen region of the Lush Forest District, somewhere inside the forest in the mountains.

Night time.

A woman in a green shirted walked slowly from a forest slope in Aquarius’s manor.

With her attire being all green, she was like a forest ranger who had become one and blended completely with her surroundings.

The woman was around twenty, and had a long and slim body. She looked like a sexy female aristocrat who was about to go on a hunt.

She had a noble themed green colored lantern sleeve shirt and was wearing a small green circular hat which even had a white feather inserted into it.

On her lower torso, she was wearing a light green mini skirt and green floral patterned stockings. Revealed in between the stockings and the miniskirt was a swathe of her fair thigh.

The woman was wearing a green mask, and a green longbow slung across on her back. The quiver was hanging from her waist in a way that was hidden yet convenient at the same time.

She looked at the manor from far away, as the manor was lit by dots of yellow under the night sky.

The woman raised up her right hand and wound up her pinky finger as she placed her blue colored metal ring, which she wore, to the side of her lips.

"I have arrived." She whispered to the ring. Her accent was not of the Lush Forest region, and her tone was slightly high pitched at the end of the sentence. She sounded like she was singing.

Chapter 245: Attacked 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There was a dark green figure by the slanted forest just outside the Trenjons Manor. It was a young woman in a tight green shirt and dress. Although she had an average face and was slightly filled in her chest and backside, she was incredible sexy in the tight shirt.

She was carrying five black arrows on her back and holding a black longbow with her hand. She was looking into the Trenjons Manor coldly from afar.

The ray of light during noon landed on the right of her body, reflecting off a faint green light.

She squat down slowly and used a dagger to leave a shallow mark onto the grass beside her feet.

She then stood up, turned around, and disappeared into the trees.

**************

Two days later, in the morning hours.

A black horse carriage slowly came out of the Trejons’s manor, headed towards the Black Flower Mountain.

The carriage was pulled by two strong black horses. They were going through the sea of trees at incredible speed, with no sign of stopping down anytime soon.

With the carriage’s window wound down halfway, a handsome young man with golden hair and pale skin could be seen inside. He looked tired, as he supported himself with one hand on the chin by the window, as if he was taking a nap.

A set of blue eyes were staring at the moving carriage in the forest. As the carriage moved further away, the eyes followed suit.

Diaz was following the carriage closely, jumping around the branches swiftly. Everytime she landed onto a tree, she was perfectly hidden behind the branches and well hidden within the carriage’s blindspot. She was as swift and stealthy as a civet, so stealthy even the grass wasn’t disturbed.

She had one hand on her thigh the entire time. She was wearing a black long stockings, which had a line of thin black needles placed on them. The black needles connected the short green dress and stockings together, and no wind seemed to be able to coax the skirts upwards.

The carriage and her were moving without rest. Occasionally other carriages would pass by, and they would take a short break during the journey. After an hour or so, the carriages took a turn and went down a small, remote lane.

The carriages that were on the road could not be seen from here. Only the farmer natives, who were there to collect firewood, would occasionally seen on this road.

The carriage stopped as it reached the very end of the road.

The young man opened the car door and jumped out of the carriage, exchanging a few words with the driver. A tall person in black armour came down from the carriage, and the two of them formed a line and slowly went into the forest in front of them.

Diaz was confused, and slowly removed a black needle from her skirt.

"This place should be nearly outside of Vanderman’s range of awareness…" She muttered as she slowly followed the duo.

*********

Garen was looking carefully looking for the medicinal herbs at the place where he had previously found the Amejade grass. This time, he went deeper into the forest. Ulun, who was fully equipped with his battle gear, was following him from behind. This calm middle aged man who always looked puzzled and suspicious was following him silently from the rear without asking what Garen was doing, owing to his good manners.

Eventually, they arrived at the location where they had their camping trip. Ulun walked in front of Garen on his own accord, pulled out a short sword and went into a state of alertness. Although the dangerous animals should not have recovered yet when he killed them off, it’s better to be safe than sorry.

"Don’t be so tight up about it. Hadn’t we just left not long ago?" Garen laughed.

"It’s always better to be more careful." Ulun was unswayed by it.

Garen shrugged his shoulders and let him do what he wanted. He was searching high and low for the things he was looking for with a container in hand, ready to place anything inside as he went on his search.

Two of them went straight into the deep forest without any detour. They could faintly see the mountain ranges that pierced through the clouds, the peak of the green mountains covered with white snow.

The grass on the ground had grown longer over the years. Occasionally, fierce venomous snakes and spiders would jumped out of the grass to attack them, but they were all disposed off by Ulun.

Garen didn’t recognize most of the plants, as there were only a little of them that looked similar to what was in his previous world. He was searching for those that he was familiar with, such as the amejade grass, pinweed, etc.

They eventually found two in the dense forest. However, they were only less than a hundred years old. It was as if they were extremely lucky to be able to find the thousand year old amejade grass last time.

Unsatisfied, he continued looking for it. He knew that the types of grasses similar to the amejade grass would be grouped in the same area. So when he found a few bunches of amejade grass, he kept on searching near the surrounding area.

"I’ve found it!" His eyes brightened up as he walked a few steps forward towards the thousand year old amejade grass, which was located just behind a green colored stone. The leaves were filled with tiny white spots, which gave off a sense of uncleanliness.

"It’s a thousand-year-old one! It’s even older than the ones I’ve previously collected!" Garen was filled with joy. It took him great difficulty to find a thousand year old amejade grass among the bunch. This particular one that he found had the medicinal effect of two packets of herbs. He estimated that it could recover half of his peak strength with this.

At this point, he believed that he could not find any more in this area any longer, as these herbs had high requirements towards the environment in order to live. He could only depend on to encounter more of them, as the soil quality further ahead was not suitable for the amejade grass to grow.

Garen went straight for the herbs, preparing to dig it up before doing anything else.

Flap.

Suddenly a rattling sound came from behind him.

Afterwards, the sound of shirt flapping could be heard, and a greenish human figure jumped over his head and landed gently in front of Garen.

"Reveal your identity!!"

Ulun quickly pulled out a sword and place it in front of Garen with one hand and held a dagger with the other hand.

"Who are you?!" Ulun was staring at the girl in green skirt. The opponent had a green short hair and was holding a longbow in her hand. She was looking at the duo with a rather disturbing gaze.

"A forest ranger? No, there shouldn’t be any forest rangers in this area. Who are you?" Ulun asked with a solemn look, as he knew that the move performed by the opponent was something he, a Soldier-level could only hope to do.

The woman laughed and didn’t answer his question. She had her eyes on Garen the whole time.

"A rich playboy who doesn’t go and enjoy his life, and instead decides to dig up some weeds in this deserted area? Acacia, what are you up to?"

"Who are you!" Garen retreated and hid behind Ulun. "How do you know my name?" He was trying his best to act frightened while paying attention to the woman in front of him.

The opponent was filled with energy spirit, which made him slightly anxious. It was an opponent that was currently stronger than him.

"My name is Diaz. Consider yourself unlucky because I am currently in a very bad mood!" Diaz started smiling coldly as she raised her right hand.

Suddenly, a soft sonic boom rang out.

Pew!!

Ulun forcefully pushed Garen away and shielded him. He grunted and swung both of his swords towards the woman only to be easily evaded by her.

"Run!!" Ulun shouted as he swung his swords at incredible speed at Diaz without any concern for his injury.

Garen stumbled about as he ran away. As he ran for a few steps, he saw a blue figure at the corner of his sight.

"It’s the blue scaled snake! Of course!" He felt a chill in his body. The opponent was definitely related to Aquarius.

Shortly after, he heard Ulun shouted from behind him, and was completely silent after that.

"Can you even escape?" A woman’s voice came from behind and a soft sonic boom was heard as well.

Garen pretended to sprain his ankle and tumbled on the ground as he avoided the black needle. He tumbled down the slope and landed onto a grass field.

He heard the sound of the footsteps approaching as he saw Diaz’s figure in front of him. She pulled out her long sword and pointed it at Garen.

"You’re so weak." She looked at him arrogantly.

She looked at him as if he was a joke when she saw the herbs that was in Garen’s hand.

Slam!

She stomped onto the basket of herbs with all her might and as a result, the herbs were completely ruined, leaving no useful ingredients behind.

"Is this the garbage you’ve been looking for all over the place? It’s very unfortunate that they’re completely useless now~~"

"What the f*ck!"

Garen’s eyes were filled with rage. These herbs were collected with his sweat and time, and now they were completely ruined by her stomp.

As he looked out from the corner of his vision again, and still the blue-scaled snake was there. He was very sure that a Luminarist was controlling the situation in the dark.

"You dare to kill me!!? I am the only successor to the Trejons Household! You may want to consider the consequence before killing me! My whole household will never let you go!!!" Garen acted as if he was omnipotent. However, he was only strong on the appearance in the eyes of the blue-scaled snake and Diaz.

"Never let me go? Hehe, I’m so scared…" Diaz started to laugh loudly, so much so that she started to tearing up. "I didn’t know garbage like you even knew how to threaten others."

Whoosh.

At this moment, Garen showcased a little of his battle skills. He got up, ran and jumped to the other side of the steep slope without giving Diaz a chance to react.

"You’re dead!" Diaz quickly followed up and chased Garen down at full speed as she jumped to the other side of the steep slope as well.

The human-like eyes on the blue-scaled snake looked slightly disappointed.

"Is that what he is only capable of? This is the little strength that he was hiding?" It hesitated for a moment and eventually turned around and left the area. "I’ve wasted my effort to arrange a General-level to be here."

Splash!

A sound of a heavy object falling into the water came from the steep slope.

*********

The end of the slope was actually a deep green colored pond.

Diaz flew down, tracking Garen’s rolling. She ended up at the cliff edge of the slope and looked down at the pond down below.

"There’s no one here!? Where did he run off to? Did he fall down?" She was mortified as she looked down at the water ripple in the pond.

"If I die, someone will avenge me. What about you?" Suddenly a gentle male voice came from behind her.

Diaz felt a shiver from her head to toe and out of reflex, she struck back with her sword and shot out three black needles at the same time.

Pew pew pew!!

Chapter 246: Attacked 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

With a swift motion, he caught the three black needles with his bare hand.

Boom!!

She saw that Acacia’s golden eyes were fused with a faint red color, as she felt two big hands silently placed onto her chest.

There was no sound of impact, only that her mind was sent to a chaotic state. It was as if her body was hit by a big vibration and lost her balance as a result of losing almost all her strength.

Diaz could do nothing but to watch herself falling into the pond, back towards the ground.

Splash!

Garen stood at the edge of the cliff and threw the three black needles with his left hand. At the same time, he jumped and went after Diaz who was falling into the pond.

"You bastard!!" Diaz wanted to scream but she was interrupted by the three black needles that were fast approaching, followed closely by a black figure from above.

As she looked up, she saw Garen fast approaching with a cold expression. The frail and fragile look that he had earlier had completely disintegrated. The gaze sent a shiver down her spine. This fellow had hidden too much of his strength! No! She had to report this intel immediately!

"Three Leap!!" She stomped with all of her strength and went after Garen, leaving behind a hemispherical wave behind her. She was like an arrow flying up from the pond. She stomped on the water three times, increasing her speed with each stomp and reached the edge of the pond in no time.

She was not an expert in fighting on the water or fighting in close range. In addition, she had been hit by his palm and her body was still numb from it, resulting her being unable to exert any force. She could only muster half of Three Leap’s strength and speed, which was one of her proudest skills. This made her feel fear and aggrieved.

"When I recover…!!"

As she was about to utter a vengeful statement, an intense strength came from behind her silently.

"Myriad Water Jasper Technique!!"

Garen attacked Diaz’s back with his glowing blue hands, and the ear splitting sound of waves followed suit.

All his might merged as one and released a sound that resembled a tsunami. The horrifying strength had formed countless of small vortices and landed onto Diaz.

Boom!

Fresh blood came out from Diaz’s mouth. Blood could be seen everywhere, as if water was leaking from a water bottle. She limped a few steps and turned her head around.

"You…!!"

Garen walked up to her and kicked her. She was sent flying and landed hard on a green stone before falling to the ground. The total count of broken bones that accompanied the sound of snapping and breaking from her body was unclear.

"Any last words?"

"I… I…" Diaz tried to open her mouth with all of her might, but her mouth was completely filled with blood, and anything that came out from her mouth was completely unintelligible.

Garen squat down, picked up one of the black needles that was scattered on the ground, and gently took aim at the center of her head.

"Good bye."

Pew!

Diaz shivered as despair could be seen in her eyes. Her body started to tremble greatly. After a few moments, her trembling subsided and became weaker, eventually coming to a complete stop after a minute.

Garen stood up and brushed off the dirts and dust that was on his body. His casual clothes, which was originally white, had turned green.

"This is embarrassing." He sighed as he started to examine the traces he had left behind.

His footprints, special effects that was caused by the fist technique and the remaining clues that could possibly reveal his strength were completely cleaned up.

"This person that was sent to probe us by Aquarius… Diaz… I’ve seen this person in the images…" He looked at Diaz’s corpse as he vaguely found this person in his memories.

He sorted out the major keys and main events related to Vanderman that occurred in this time frame, which was about the overall events within the next 2 years.

"This person should have appeared two months later. Why is she here?" His started to frown slightly. "If I hadn’ ambushed her, I would have been in grave danger if she were to pull some distance between us and attack from afar with her longbow." Afterall, he had yet to reach General-level.

After ensuring that there were no strange noises from the surroundings, he squatted down and took off the longbow and arrows from the corpse. He then started fumbling around the corpse, and found a small brown pouch and some spare change.

He poured out whatever was inside the pouch onto the ground, and what came out were some pink pills and a stack of white long cotton cloth.

"What is this?" Garen picked up the cotton cloth and examine it carefully. He could faintly see a line of word saying: ‘It’s a relief to have Masona.’

There was another short sentence below: ‘With the Masona pad, you can move about freely.’

Garen immediately knew what it was and threw away the pad.

The pink circular pills were very tiny. On the surface were the words printed ‘AD’

"This is…" Garen seemed to have thought of something. "This might be useful."

He kept the the pills and picked up a tree branch filled with leaves. He started to wipe of his foot prints as he walked, and swiftly left the pond area.

He went back to where Ulun was. Initially, he hid himself carefully. Upon realizing that there were no blue-scaled snakes, he quickly rushed towards Ulun’s side. Surprisingly, his loyal subject was alive. He had a hole in his head and was bleeding profusely.

Garen took out the pink pills and crushed it into a powder. He then rubbed it onto the wound and applied pressure onto it.

After a while the wound stopped bleeding.

Ulun started to wake up from being unconscious.

"Mas...ter, are you still alive?"

"Someone saved me. Let’s not talk about this and leave this area first!" Garen acted as if he had yet to calm down.

"Al..alright."

Ulun’s injury wasn’t dire as he only lost too much blood from the bleeding. The bloodstain that was on his body would have shocked anyone. Although faltered as he walked, it didn’t really affect him much at all.

As the two of them went back to the horse carriage, they saw the driver laying down on a pool of his own blood with an arrow stuck in his neck. The two horses ran off with the carriages about ten meters away and were stuck in between two trees.

Garen and Ulun got up the carriage and swiftly went back to the manor.

**************

There was an uproar in the whole manor when the news of Acacia being ambushed spread.

Angered, Vanderman sent out all of his forces to the Black Flower Mountain to search for any clues for two days, but to no avail. The corpse of the female assassin was dragged off by the wolves to an unknown place, and what could only be found was the trace of the battle near the pond.

Due to this incident, Acacia was grounded and could not leave the manor.

Vanderman had gone out for some reason unknown to Acacia. However, judging from the look of his face when he went out, he obviously was not out for vacation.

Garen took this opportunity to stay in the manor and study the handbook on a daily basis. He also trained his physical body in the hope that he would recover as soon as possible and raise his Precision Blueprint to the Intermediate-level.

As his physical body kept recovering, his learning pace had started to become faster as well. The requirement needed for the Intermediate-level was a matter of time.

He was able to attack the without any pause. The surprise attack to stun the enemy, and Myriad Water Jasper Technique as the finishing blow.

He obtained Myriad Water Jasper Technique from Celine, and it was very suitable to use it during an ambush. Furthermore, it didn’t put a lot of strain onto the user’s body. The only downside of this technique was that it wasn’t lethal, and would be ineffective against a master. However, it seemed to be rather effective towards the General-levels of this world.

*************

In the certain part of the manor, there was a sea of bright red roses.

A girl in a tight short skirt and a green mask was standing in the center of the rose field, cutting off the branches with care. There was a girl in a green shirt reporting the situation to her, softly, with her head bowed.

"We have a few captains that are on the move to kill the bandits. Such is the situation regarding the bandits for these past few days. Furthermore…" The reporter looked at the masked woman in front of her cautiously.

"Furthermore, Diaz who had gone to Vanderman’s manor had disappeared and has yet to return."

"Oh?"

The masked woman stopped cutting the branches and sighed softly.

"Have we received any secret signal?"

"None."

"Have the remaining people receive anything as well?"

"None."

The masked woman placed down the scissor as she frowned.

"Diaz is a woman who knows the severity of the situation. She would not have disappear for no reason. Looks like she has gotten into some trouble."

"I’m afraid so." The reported lowered her head.

"Vanderman… Even a General-level couldn’t escape from you? You’re a mysterious man…" The masked woman’s green eyes were filled with murderous intent. "What about Tracy?"

"Isn’t she on vacation?" The reporter was stunned.

"Call her back immediately. I cannot withdraw from this incident; I will leave the rest to her. We, the Green Shades, must not lose our value over this incident."

"Yes."

*************

A few days later….

Hoooo!

Garen threw a punch in his room and short vortices were formed in the air.

Garen threw the punches with both of his hands, and this time his clothes that were near his shoulder was slightly torn off.

His face was filled with satisfaction as he relaxed his fighting posture.

"My strength and agility are now more than 1.5. I am finally able to use my battle skills combined with the secret techniques. Now, my last step is to fully recover, and use my four ultimate techniques without worry. " Garen picked up the towel and wiped the sweat off his body and sat beside the circular table in the middle of his room.

It was a table that he wanted placed there so that he could conveniently pick up the items on the table.

He looked at the attribute pane as he poured himself a glass of water.

Although the the medicine was no longer in his body, the effect had yet to be completely absorbed. Hence his body would still be recovering for a while before it completely stopped.

His strength had recovered by half compared to the last time.

‘Strength 1.6, Agility 1.5, Vitality 1.9, Intelligence 1.1, Potential 1772%. Possess the qualification to be a Luminarist.

Secret technique -- Divine Statue technique, Ten Thousand Mammoth Battle Skills.

287 days left until full recovery (a year).

Precision Blueprint: Intermediate-level. (Total of three level: Beginner-level, Intermediate-level, Master-level)’

As he had reached the Intermediate-level for his Precision Blueprint, his recovery time had naturally decreased. Furthermore, his intelligence level had finally reached 1 point, which was the average intelligence of a human. This was the point that Garen was most excited about.

His current logical thinking was different than before. In the past, he was slow, unresponsive and couldn’t connect the major points most of the time. Memorisation was essential to the Precision Blueprint. In addition, it could be handy and he felt much more smoother as well.

This was indeed the advantage of having a high intelligence. He drank another hot cup of water with satisfaction.

Chapter 247: Recovery 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Intelligence is a funny thing. It represents the ability to memorize, imagine, analyze, so on and so forth. If it’s too low, it’d be severely impact the ability to learn and comprehend.

Garen rested on his chair, considering his next moves.

"The timeline is changing, that Diaz shouldn’t be here yet, why is she sent here early?" He set down his cup, his fingers tapping the table.

"If I recall correctly, there were a few major events before Beckstone arrived. The RAL (Royal Alliance of Luminarists)* had a fall out with the Obscuro preceding some riots. Within a year the power that RAL holds weakened significantly, until they were overturned by the Obscuro. The key turning point of that was the War of the Luminarists led by Rosette."

Reviewing the information from the memory, Garen started to finalize his plans.

"If that’s the case, in this Totem World, there were three major factions, The RAL, Obscuro Society, and Terraflor Society. All three have their own top Luminarists. At first, the RAL and Obscuro had a clash, leading to their loss of power, Beckstone from Terraflor took the opportunity to rise up."

He meticulously picked at specific details in the memory. Soon, he found the strongest Luminarists under all three factions.

The Royal Alliance of Luminarists had three Luminarists leading the three departments, they represented the benefits of the Royal family and the nobles.

Obscuro’s were Hellgate and his two disciples.

Terraflor’s were Beckstone and his teammates, along with the Silver Knight’s leader. They have a lot of people, but they were the weakest out of the three.

These are the strongest Luminarists from the three factions.

Viscount Vanderman was only one of the supporters outside the three departments, and was at the same time an outer member of the Obscuro, he was one of the initial opponents Beckstone faced.

"The leaders of the three departments of RAL, that’s too far away. Any one of them would be stronger than Beckstone in his most powerful period. Vanderman couldn’t even reach them." Garen analyzed. "If these three people were still alive, Obscuro wouldn’t be so daring to attack the manor. In that case, the attack I faced was probably as a warning to Vanderman."

Frowning, he figured out the situation.

"The following event would probably be small-scale collisions between Obscuro and the RAL before it turned into large-scale ones. Right now, Terraflor is still a small fry. With upcoming battles, Obscuro wouldn’t be able to pay attention to us, so they will only destroy the manor when Beckstone arrives."

Garen’s brows were tightly knit, he stood up.

"But I was just attacked, that means both sides were not planning to do it secretly anymore. Time is running short, maybe the timeline would be shifted forward even more."

He paced in his room.

"I need to keep up…" He had made his mind.

His gaze fell onto the ability pane.

His Precision Blueprint skill was shown as Intermediate-level.

"I’ll raise this to Master-level first, then I’ll go look for Teacher Emin to learn the Tactics to get a head start with creating my own Totem. But before that, I need to recover my strength completely!"

He showed a sense of determination.

"No more keeping secrets, I guess."

　　***********

After Garen made up his mind, he started hiring the townsfolk in the town to pick amejade grass, pinweed and the other herb. With every individual plant, he bought it off of them with ten rumbs*.

The Rumb is the official unit of currency issued by the Kovitan Empire, its buying power is slightly higher than the American Dollar on Earth. That was not a bad value.

After asking his servants to man the booths for purchasing the herbs, they spread the news, many townsfolk started collecting them for Garen.

His father Viscount Vanderman found out, but he didn’t ask. About his son’s behavior, he reasoned as one of his passing fads.

Acacia used to like planting roses too, switching it for another isn’t that big of a deal.

After the initial confusion, Viscount Vanderman found out that his son switched every single one of the roses to herbs. He guessed his son learned some alchemical formula from somewhere and that he kept wanting to have a mysterious potion for his own use.

With regards to this he scoffed, alchemical potions were debunked about a hundred years ago. It was just a scam, but one of the biggest scam in the century. It wasn’t spending much of his money, so he ignored it.

Viscount Vanderman was busier than usual.

He went to the capital of the empire and visited scores of famous Luminarists and aristocrats, getting information about the Obscuro Society. As an academic Luminarist, he always had means to contact people. After all the trouble he went through, he even gotten himself two other Luminarist friends to stay over at his manor for a few days to show the Royal family’s attitude toward them.

　　*************

"Good evening Sirs." Garen stood in front of the white-bearded old men, greeting them with the utmost respect.

These two were his father’s Royal Luminarist friends from the capital city, Rob and Eric. They both wore white robes with silver lining, and had an aura of wisdom.

Both nodded.

"He’s not bad, even though he’s not intelligent, he’s still a polite kid."

"I can see the respect for intelligence in his eyes." Eric boomed. His voice is loud, echoing throughout the study.

Vanderman sit at the side, his face slightly fark.

"This attack on Cia, I strongly suspect it’s by the people over there. Several of the other lords were also attacked, reducing their powers. This is obviously a planned operation."

He eyed Garen.

"Cia, you can go now. Do go out unnecessarily, the situation now is a little unstable."

"Yes, father."

Even though Garen wanted to listen to the conversation, but all three Luminarists were much stronger than his current self. Even if he recovered all his strength, it’s impossible to fight them. Eavesdropping is out of the question too.

He used his Turtle Breathing Technique and slowly backed away from the study. The hushed conversation carried on behind him. He left Vanderman’s building briskly.

When he passed by the yard in front of the building, he looked up and stared at the candlelit room on the second floor.

"Looks like the RAL is going to fight back soon. They even got two Luminarists to support…"

He strode toward his own building.

Closing the door, he rushed to the second floor into his own study, closing all the curtains and windows.

He retrieved a redwood briefcase and unlocked it.

There were scores of bottles with a cornflower blue potions.

"I managed to concoct so much potion, it wasn’t the millennium ones, but they can still work." He took out a bottle and chugged it.

If it was the potion made from the millennium old amejade grass, he wouldn’t dare to drink it. It was too strong. But these amejade grass were only less than a century old, their medicinal properties were much milder. If he doesn’t drink it, the effects would be even worse. Right now, it’s just strong enough that his body could endure.

After one bottle, Garen kept the briefcase away.

His body started to heat up.

During the past few weeks, through collecting the herbs with his servants and brewing the potions himself, he had already consumed a large quantity of the potion, his body was almost back at his peak.

He glanced at the attribute pane, having a sense of expectation.

Just a little more to his peak.

‘Strength 2.0, Agility 1.9, Vitality 2.2, Intelligence 1.7. Luminarist Talent detected.’

"This is a physical attribute built purely with the potion, I have developed resistance to the potion, but I’m also almost recovered." Garen was happy at the result feeling his strength.

At his peak, all the attributes were about 2.6.

As of now, his attributes were twice an average person’s. When put together, his power would be exponentially more powerful than that. He can already use his strongest Four Secret Techniques.

All in all, he had already recovered 90% of his strength.

"However, this is no longer the original world. My strength here is not enough…" Garen sighed.

After resting for a bit, when the effects of the potion had subsided, his gaze fell upon the ability pane once again.

"Now that my body is almost back to normal, I need to work on my skills… Need to raise the level of Precision Blueprint."

Garen stared at the skill Precision Blueprint for three seconds.

Immediately, the name of the skill vibrated and blurred out and finally turned into Master-level!

The Potential Point decreased by 500% with just a second!

The skill pane has changed.

‘Precision Blueprint: Master-level. (Levels: Beginner, Intermediate, Master)’

"It really is an advanced ability… I have advanced to Intermediate-level myself, so I didn’t use up the Potential Points, but now to turn it into Master-level, I used up 5 whole points…" Garen thought begrudgingly.

The Potential Points looked like it was a lot when it was 18 points, but because of the Precision Blueprint skill, there are only 12 points left.

"I wonder if there are Antique of Disaster in this world…" He thought.

In this manor, he had already touched all the antiques Vanderman collected, but none of them were Antiques of Disaster. His Potential Points had not changed.

This made him wonder if Antiques of Disaster actually exist in this world.

Following the mastery of the skill Precision Blueprint, Garen felt another breeze as thick as ink flowing to his hands from his brain.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. May shorten to RAL in future chapters depending on context.

Chapter 248: Recovery 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Both his hands were warm, as if they were submerged in lukewarm water.

A never before experienced sense of dexterousness surged from Garen’s hands. Raising his hands, he made a few poses.

Following the sound of his hands cutting through the air, his fingers created apparitions where they moved.

Garen squinted.

"What speed! This level of dexterity is only a foundation in being a Luminarist?!" He observed his own hands. With his current proficiency, he could form three complex gestures in a second.

Basically he could finish any gestures in an instant.

"I guess, it’s Tactics next." Garen retrieved the handbook and pressed against the tiny wrinkles on the cover. "Teacher Emin said if I want to continue the study, I’ll need to go to his place. I can’t leave the manor yet, need ideas…"

His Intelligence had already returned to his normal level, so his thinking speed is really fast.

"Right now the manor has three Luminarists, the Obscuro wouldn’t provoke us for the moment. But Vanderman would know that already. They’re in a sticky situation at the moment, if the RAL could request for reinforcement, so could the Obscuro. If they clashed then, I’d be in even more danger."

He estimated that if he requested to go out, Vanderman wouldn’t oppose to it after giving it a little thought. The Luminarists wouldn’t pay much attention to a nobody like him anyway, there shouldn’t be much problem if he hid himself appropriately.

　　************************

In a town a few thousand kilometers away from the Lush Forest district.

The setting sun sent its rays onto the streets, bringing out a sense of warmth and peace.

Children chased after each other in front of the fruit stall. Among the townsfolk coming home, some mercenaries walked with their weapons. Occasionally there were a few people from the upper class too.

In a yellowish private building made of some sort of wooden material.

The door opened with a creak before letting in a young man with a slightly pale face. His youthful, beardless face was accentuated with his calm, bright eyes. He wore a black set of suit with an equally black bowler hat, a black feather in his breast pocket, and a black walking cane in his hand.

He entered the hall and looked at an enchanting young lady sitting by the bar.

"Berlina, is teacher back?" He said, gazing at the staircase toward the second floor.

"Upstairs. He’s waiting for you, go quickly." The lady was combing her long red hair with a small comb and answered him nonchalantly.

"I know."

The man hung his hat on the rack beside the entrance and rushed to the second floor.

Knock knock.

"Beckstone? Come in." An old raspy voice came from inside.

The door opened by itself, leaving space for the passage of one person.

The man in black entered.

It was an average-sized study. Bookshelves took up most of the wallspace. Everywhere, the floor, the desk, were books and opened notebooks.

Sketch papers were filled with random notes, complicated formulas, symbols and shapes.

An old man sat in front of the desk by the window. His silver beard was so long, it drags from the desk to the door, spooling in front of it. It measured about twenty meters.

"Your beard has grown out again." Closing the door, the younger man avoided stepping on the silver beard and approached the older man.

"This is a curse, one that I can’t ever undo…" The old man put aside his notebook, leaned back against the chair and sighed. "Compared to killing that person, I am willing to pay this price."

"Do you have any orders for me?" The younger man asked politely.

"Beckstone, when you were still a baby, I saved you from the stream. Even then you were able to understand my words. You promised me, don’t hate the world, don’t antagonize your parents who left you. Were you able to do that?" The old man stared into the young man’s eyes, his own sparkling with evaluation.

Beckstone stayed quiet for a while before he answered with hesitation.

"I am working on it...:"

"You couldn’t, I know…" The old man sighed, once more. "Life is constantly changing. You’ve lived in this town for the past nineteen years. Hatred can only create more hatred. At this point, I can no longer restrict you from doing anything. Your talent frightens me, I’m afraid that you will bring damage to mankind if you lost your way. Unfortunately, this is not something you can control."

"Teacher…"

"No words. Maybe you will become the strongest Luminarist in the world, but never forget this. Your hatred, your desire, your choices, everything you do will bring about huge impacts to the world. You may bring light and hope, but you may also bring suffering and pain."

The old man looked at the young man whom he taught for twenty years, his eyes kind.

"Go, it’s time for you to leave here."

"Leave?" Beskstone was lost for words, "Where should I go?"

"Wherever you want to go."

Beckstone wanted to protest, but his vision blurred, and the next thing he knew, he was standing outside the building, his hand posed on the door, preparing to enter.

"Teacher… is this what you wanted to say to me?" He murmured, let his hand fall to his side, and left.

Creaking, the door swung open, an enchanting red-haired lady stared at his leaving with a weird look.

"Hey! Don’t you wanna keep teacher company?" She hollered.

Beckstone waved with his backhand, and soon he disappeared into the crowd.

A beautiful face emerged from the depth of his mind.

"I will find you, and the person who took you…" Beckstone’s grip tightened on itself.

　　******************

Lush Forest district

Manor of Aquarius

Clink! Clank! Crash!

Aquarius swept the vases off the table in her fury. Some of them crashed on the wall, some landed on the floor, but they all broke into pieces.

The room was a galore of her wrath. Crystal statues, life-size models, furnitures, flowers, everything was strewn around in the room.

"Dammit dammit dammit dammit!!"

Aquarius’ face was in a state of contortion, her anger bursting out of her facade of divine beauty.

"Barr! Baphje!" She clenched her jaw as she tugged at the tablecloth, throwing it on the floor and stepped on it in frustration.

"Royal Alliance, you’re pushing your luck! This is Lush Forest district! Obscuro’s territory, MY territory!" Her rage was seething so much, it made her tremble. Her eyes were filled with killing intent as dense as mud.

However, being furios is one thing, sticking to the plan her higher up gave is another. The overall arrangements in different countries have yet to be finalized, and she’s just a very small part of it. Even Barr and Baphje, the two district-level people in charge from Royal Alliance of Luminarists, were only considered as a small price to pay in exchange for their operation’s success.

"Shouldn’t jeopardize the whole situation. Or else I won’t have my revenge, the higher ups will also…"

"You won’t be seeing the last of me… just you wait!" Aquarius felt as if her chest was drowning in the air, her displease nowhere to be displaced. "I will remember this, but next time! I will throw you all in the sow barn, naked!"

Outside the opened door, one of her subordinates shivered as she heard the words.

"Re- reporting for duty!"

"What!" Aquarius yelled back in her fury.

"Two news…" The subordinate replied with hesitation, "A missing General-level in Lush Forest district had been found. Only bones were left behind by the wolves…"

"Oh? Those useless imbeciles! Not bad, Vanderman-" Aquarius’ face was wild, as if she’s going to break out. "What’s the other news?"

"Master… Lonave is here."

"Lonave…" Aquarius was going to respond when she recalled her assassin Diaz’s pursuit of that idiot Master Acacia through her blue-scaled snake.

"Interesting… What kind of elites does Vanderman have protecting his son? I wanna know!" She licked her lips and barked her order at her subordinate.

"Tell Lonave, compared to his boorish self, I’d rather have a handsome fellow like Vanderman’s son Acacia. Tell him to never bother me again!"

"Yes… Yes…" Her subordinate didn’t wait any longer as she backed out immediately.

　　*****************

Three days later.

Every few days, there will be a team escorting exchange materials from the territory of the Trejons to the district of Hanna on the other side of the Red River.

The procession marched past a small bridge under the afternoon sun. The river itself is the border between districts, the carriages cast their reflections on the stream, seemingly calm and peaceful.

In one of the white carriages, Garen wore a white hood to hide his face, but he was by himself among all the cargo.

The captain of the team is Banq, a shrewd businessman. His official job is the leader of interdistrict exchange, but in secret, he’s also a spy of the Trejons family.

This team looked like they’re sending goods to another district, but their real motive is to escort Garen away from his manor. It was getting more and more dangerous, that’s one of the main reasons Vanderman agreed to let Garen go.

His destination will be at the other side of the Red River, his aunt’s house in Hanna district.

Staring at his own reflection under the bridge, it was like looking into a mirror.

A red maple leaf drifted slowly onto the water surface, creating ripples that spread out and disturbing that reflection.

Garen rubbed his hands lightly as the weather cooled.

At every period of peacefulness, he would think about the life he had on earth.

He kept going forward with his special ability, there was no pauses or stagnation. As he reached his goals, he kept thinking, what are all those for, but he had no answer.

"Maybe as I moved forward, I will return to earth one day." Garen fantasized, breathing out a cloud of white mist.

Only with enough power, he can feel safe. Sometimes he also doubted his motive of learning Martial Arts in the first place. Was it because he had fantasized it for the longest of time, or was it because he wanted to not be afraid anymore?

Afraid of disappearing.

Countless planets in the universe, countless civilizations, he wondered how many were stronger than the Luminarists. Even the powerful Warlocks had completely died out.

"What exactly, is forever…?" Garen lifted his jaw, looking at the orange sky.

A skein of geese flew past them, forming a V-shape.

A platinum-gold silhouette slowly appeared beside Garen, mirroring his action of staring at the sky.

Chapter 249: Dream 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A sudden uncertainty arose from the depth of his heart.

As if he had lived several decades with no specific goal of his own, and one day, he starts asking questions about the meaning of his life.

This is the first time Garen thought about it. He was used to the passivity of his journey, being led on by the enemies in front of him until he climbed up the peak.

But now that he’s in a different world, everyone was much stronger than he is that he can’t catch up right there and then, but there’s also nothing he could do to speed up the process.

In the gap between all the fighting he had done and he will do, he started questioning his own existence.

This uncertainty had only lasted a short moment before he shirked it off.

Garen shook his head, laughing at his sudden yearning.

"I haven’t even resolved my current danger, who am I to think about existential questions?"

Laughing at himself, he continued his study of the handbook. Combined with the memories he’d watched previously, he started collating the details and information of Luminarists.

The whole planet is dominated by the East Continent and the West Continent, the rest are mostly just oceans and glaciers. All the countries of the two continents were controlled by Luminarists, and as of now, the Obscuro Society and the Royal Alliance of Luminarists are having a feud.

Riding on that opportunity, Terraflor Society which lacks a huge power will rise and turn into a syndicate as powerful as the Obscuro Society.

This was the overall situation. Aside from the three parties trying to get the biggest piece of pie, the rest were just normal Luminarists.

The support of the world comes from this large group of Luminarists, the only thing separating them were their ideals. This is not just a normal battle, but a war of ideals.

Garen compiled all the memory he had watched and started to collect events that may be happening in the near future, arranging them into a timeline for future reference.

The cargo stopped every once in a while to unload and refill their wares before continuing their journey.

Following the Red River, they passed by several villages. Garen kept searching for an opportunity to leave.

Teacher Emin stays in at the Red River Valley, but that wasn’t where the team was heading to. The elites who are protecting him, Ulun and the two other quieter knights would not let him leave by himself. He needs to find an opportunity to sneak away.

A dozen days later, there was a raid from some mounted robbers, forcing the elites to make a move. In the chaos, Garen left the team with a note, and went on his way solo, following the map his teacher left him.

　　*************

At the other end of the Red River, in the small town of Vinker.

The town was built on the side of a hill-laden plain, an ocean of red flowers bloomed across the plain, surrounding the town, steeping it in its fragrance.

In the afternoon, a dust-covered Garen stood on top of a hill, staring at the town from afar. The town is shaped like two side-by-side crosses. It's small and could only fit shit several hundred people.

It was much smaller than the other towns along the river.

The houses were built with old wood boards, most had some clay bricks mixed into their infrastructure.

A stone wall marked the border of the town. Notches were left decorating the wall, clearly left behind through something charging at it.

Garen was looking at the town silently before he suddenly stomped his right leg.

Thud!

A red centipede crawled out of the dirt before rolling over and curled up, dead.

"It actually is quite dangerous, it seems…" Garen muttered. On his was here, he took the carriage path along the Red River, which fortunately didn’t have bandits. However, creatures like this swarmed the road, and that’s excluding the wolves and wild dogs. Those come in packs.

Especially the wild dogs, every time they appear, they’ll bring hundreds of them along. Garen only scared them off using his intimidating aura. If it were any other people, it’ll take a while even if they’re not scared of them.

With such a terrible state, if normal people have not gone through special training, it’s impossible for them to go for a trip. Before long, they’d be bitten by a plethora of bugs or injured by hordes of animals, and were forced to find some place to stay. Otherwise, once their food stock was exhausted, they’ll have nowhere to go in the wilderness.

"Finally found this place after two days!" Garen took out his map and checked, confirming the accuracy of the location.

He kept the map and took out a whistle, preparing to blow it as a signal.

An unfamiliar shuffle came from the left.

By reflex, Garen lowered his body and took a few steps back, hiding behind the downhill slope.

On the only road leading into the town, two black horses raced toward him with two men with black capes on them. The two men had hulking statures and wore exquisite clothes, silver axes hung behind their backs.

Even from that distance, Garen could feel the strong but hidden aura they were emitting. From his Aura Detection, the two lit up like a torch in a moonless night.

"Guardian-level…" Garen squinted, noticing the symbols on their capes. It was red long-necked flying dragon, the symbol of the Royal Kovitan family.

"Them again…" Garen’s brows furrowed, "The RAL had been everywhere on my way here. Pretty much every nooks and crannies had been covered by them. What are they planning?"

It’s not the first time he saw these people. He had occasionally seen them in several places, in forts, towns, and even villages.

They seemed to be investigating something.

It’s only a while that Garen had to hide behind the slope. They had left the town not long after, disappearing on their horses.

One of them seemed to have seen Garen, but he didn’t think too much about it, he only urged his partner on to leave.

Garen stood up and witnessed as the two black horses disappeared into the horizon. He took his silver whistle and blew into it with force.

There was no sound except for the air rushing out of the whistle’s other end. It feel just like a broken whistle.

Garen didn’t stop, he just kept blowing the whistle.

Soon, another ‘knight’ came out of the town. It was a pretty girl in white clothing on a beardless white goat.

Meh-eh-eh!

The white goat ran toward Garen.

The girl in white yelled in excitement.

"Yah! Yah!"

Garen let down his whistle, and waited for the girl to arrive in front of him and got off the goat.

"Is that your whistle?" She asked without thought, pointing at the whistle by his side.

"Yes."

"Grandpa Emin asked me to bring you there. Come on." She hollered.

"Okay."

Garen answered without hesitation, the little girl in front of him didn’t look weird. Her physical properties were estimated to be average. Garen glanced at her hands. They were rough with calluses.

"Not a Luminarist disciple as well. Should be a normal person."

He followed the little girl into town. Most of the population was made up of women and children, save for a few men who looked like they’d just woken up. Chimney smoke were coming out of a few houses.

Dogs were barking, and roosters were crowing.

The little girl led Garen to a wooden house at the edge of the town.

"Here it is. Are you Grandpa Emin’s student? You’re so young!"

"I am," Garen nodded. "My name is Garen, what’s yours?"

"My name is Nicol, I’m a neighbor. Sometimes I come here to sweep the floor and learn some words." The girl answered. "Quick, go in, Grandpa Emin is waiting."

"Okay," Garen took out a small copper rumb, "This is your reward." He handed over the rumb copper to Nicol.

"You’re so generous!" Nicol’s eyes were shining and almost grabbed the copper out of Garen’s hand. She sniffed the copper. "It really is money!"

"Have fun, I’ll be on my way." Garen smiled and left the little girl to her own. He pushed open the fence and walked into the area of the house.

After a few paces, the door to the house slowly opened from the inside. An old man with snowy white hair stood in front of the entrance. He wore a white robe, his face lined with wrinkles that cross each other. The only familiar thing to him was the analytical look he gives.

"Teacher… Emin?" Garen asked hesitantly after laying his eyes on the gray-haired man. "How do you, how are you…?" From the aura that he give out, Garen was sure he was Emin, the Luminarist who had the appearance of a middle-aged man.

Emin smiled calmly.

"Come in, I’ll tell you in a bit." He turned around and walked into the dimly lit corridor.

Garen strode into the house and closed the door.

Humidity filled the air of the dimly lit house, there was also a scent of burnt leather.

A beam of light shone onto the floor from the dormer, providing the only source of light in the entire building.

Emin sat at a sofa just outside the range of the lightbeam. He had a cup filled with warm water, which he sips occasionally. Observing Garen’s entrance, he pointed at the sofa in front of him.

Garen went over and sat, proper and poised. His gaze fell upon Emin’s hair and his beard.

"Get the water yourself if you need it." Emin gestured toward a dusty jug of water.

"Yes sir," Garen nodded, "Teacher, I’m here for…"

"If there’s anything, just say it. Is it about the Blackguards? If it is and you want me to interfere, I will no longer owe you anything. Think about it." Emin said calmly.

"Blackguards?" Garen did a double take, "What Blackguard?"

"Huh?" Emin did a double take as well, "Aren’t you here because of the Blackguards?"

"Of course not." Garen was completely confused until he remembered the two people in black capes.

"If you’re not here for the Blackguards, what do you want from me at this point of time?" Emin frowned.

"I’m here to get my next part of the lesson." Garen stated flatly.

Chapter 250: Dream 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Next lesson?" Emin set down his cup and stared at Garen with burning eyes. "Kid, only such a short time had passed, and you want to learn Tactics already? It’s not that I look down on you, but if Luminarists can be made so easily, there’d be tons of Luminarists in the world right now!"

He stood up with his hands behind his back.

"Don’t be too ambitious, stick to your foundation first, that’s the most important part. Consider this an advice from your elders."

He sighed.

"I was like you once upon a time. I have yet to master my foundations before I wanted to learn Tactics and create my own totem. My teacher gave me a rude awakening by making two gestures in a second. I was stunned silent." He looked up to the dormer, reminiscing his own past.

He only let Garen become his disciple then because he saw his younger self in Garen. Adding that to him saving his life, it made sense to do so.

Looking at Emin who was clearly in his own world, Garen doesn’t know how to interrupt him.

"Teacher, actually I…"

"You shouldn’t be too disheartened. You don’t need to be at Master-level to start learning Precision Blueprint, that was only because I wanted to give you a high threshold. You actually only need to be at Intermediate-level." Emin interjected. "Usually with enough talent, reaching Intermediate-level in half a year is not that rare, as long as you’re hardworking."

He raised his head and went into reminisce again.

"I used half a year to reach Intermediate-level, and even my teacher said I’m one of the geniuses that only come about once in a hundred years." His face was proud now. "So that’s what I am holding you up to. Get to Intermediate-level in half a year, and I can teach you the basic Tactics."

"I…" Garen was close to speechless at this point.

"No talking back!" Emin said seriously, "You only need to answer me, can you or can’t you! I don’t need other excuses! None! I only look at the result! You’ll know how strict I can be soon enough!"

Completely dumbfounded, Garen looked at Emin, unsure of how to convince him.

"I…"

"Can you! Or! Can’t you!" Emin cut him off again.

"..." Garen went completely silent. From the beginning, he hadn’t had the chance to form a complete sentence. "I can…" He answered dejectedly.

"Good! This is how my students should behave like." Emin patted Garen on his shoulder. "Intermediate-level is not that easy, you’ll need to have an unbreakable will to succeed, an unrivalled tenacity, and a persistence beyond compare. Every day, tens of thousands of people faltered on this path. With your talent, you should be able to reach this stage in half a year, don’t give up just because you don’t see a progress."

"Teacher… I have progressed…"

"Don’t be so full of yourself, when you reached the final stage, you’ll meet one of the biggest hurdle in the Intermediate-level, the breakthrough of finger speed! But I have heard people with greater talent, they don’t even have a hurdle when transitioning into Intermediate-level, even going into Master-level is only a matter of time. Geniuses like that, it’s so inspiring…"

"..."

"The breakthrough of your speed will be your biggest hurdle in becoming a Master-level user. I’d spent countless days just working hard in my craft and exchanging experience with other Luminarists to achieve Master-level and learn Precision Blueprint. The difficulty in achieving this is harder than you can imagine… Even a genius like me need to work so hard…" He shook his head again, spacing out, yet again, into his memories.

Garen’s head begin to ache. Teacher was just recovering when he was at his house, so he didn’t show this level of bullheadedness, unlike now. Seeing Emin lost in his memories again, Garen clarified softly.

"Teacher… Actually, I’m already at Master-level…"

Emin snapped back into reality.

"This is your shortcoming, you keep boasting about your abilities, when will you actually be more grounded? You won’t win other people’s respects with just boasting, it’s with real skill, your results…"

Fwop! Fwop fwop!

In one second, Garen made three gestures with exceptional accuracy and stableness.

Silence.

"..."

"..."

It felt as if the temperature had just dropped a whole notch. The two stared at each other, each not knowing what to say to the other…

Emin’s raised arm hung in the air, his jaw dropped, his unfinished sentence gone.

Garen gulped, he looked at his teacher’s eyes as it shifted from emotion to emotion, each one so complex that the most complicated mathematical equation cannot compete with.

Slap!

Emin’s slapped his own head.

"Oh… This can’t be, must have slept too late last night, I’m definitely not awake, go back to bed, Emin." Emin turned around, his palm still holding his head. "It’s too early for a hallucination like this, weird…"

He paced upstairs, completely ignoring Garen.

Garen watched as Emin turned around and left, treating him like an illusion.

"Teacher!"

He yelled.

Emin froze in his tracks.

The situation turned sour with awkwardness.

It took a while before Emin turned around stiffly.

His face was a red as an apple.

"You… you’re really at… Master-level?" His voice trembled as he spoke, reluctant to believe.

Garen nodded slowly.

Emin took a deep breath.

"It’s so unfair!" He lowered his head, recalling the hardships he faced before he became a Master-level user.

He looked up at the extraordinarily young face, finally accepting the Garen he saw is real.

"I… need to go upstairs… I’ll be down in a while." He waved his arm in dismissal, looking much, much older than when he started.

Garen watched as Emin moved upstairs dejectedly.

He didn’t think it would be such a huge impact to his teacher. People who could go into Master-level in a short time were not rare, but actually relatively common. That was why he decided to show it in the first place, so that he could start learning Tactics as soon as possible.

However, he didn’t know this was such a huge impact to his teacher who thought he’s a genius.

Sitting on the couch, Garen wasn’t sure what to do. So he waited.

After a long while, the sky outside started to dim. As the sun sets, its rays started to become golden-red.

Footsteps appeared at the staircase as Emin slowly took his steps.

His face was calm again, and he sat opposite of Garen, taking his time.

"I got it now… Some people were able to have extraordinary talent in a specific domain, however, this only indicate their slightly higher affinity to their crafts. Those who can reach the highest, not only do they need the talent, but also the persistence and their unyielding will." He said seriously. "Thank you, Cia."

"Call me Garen, Teacher. I ran away…" Garen answered.

"Fine, Garen it is." Emin nodded. "Your talent, at least your affinity in Precision Blueprint, is my first experience as a Luminarist. Can you show me… the gestures you did before?"

Garen nodded.

He raised his arms and made one gesture after another without much difficulty.

Only a few second had passed when he was finished, averaging three in a second.

Emin watched silently without much expression, but marvel was written all over his eyes.

"Such talent… Garen, your talent in Precision Blueprint is too terrifying… From the beginning of your lesson, you’ve only needed about two months…"

Garen nodded again.

"Then, can I learn some Tactics under you, Teacher?"

"Of course." Emin nodded with intent. "You must be tired on your way here. Rest up for tonight, we will start our lesson tomorrow, the essence of us Luminarists, the Tactics!"

"Yes, Teacher." Garen nodded.

"Your room is the master bedroom on this floor. You can clean up at the bathroom over there, and meals will be at the dining kitchen. Got it?"

"Got it, Teacher. I’m not as spoiled as I look." Garen said smiling.

"Good. I’ll rest upstairs." Emin nodded and turned toward the staircase.

He stood hidden at the corner of the staircase and listened as Garen entered his room before continued walking up the flight of stairs.

Entering his study, he locked the door and approached a redwood shelf, pulling out a white notebook on the right edge.

He sat down in front of his desk and lit the oil lamp with a match.

He inked his quill and gently wrote on the opened notebook.

‘This may be fate finally giving me my favor. In my nineties, I didn’t expect a disciple with such immensely terrifying talent. It may be my luck, or yours, Resha. I will pass down the knowledge, every bit of it. Maybe I will finally be able to compile my clan before I pass on…’

Emin paused to think, and continued writing.

‘Do you still remember when we were young? When we practiced the gestures together under the grapevines, you said you had a dream. Now, among the five of us, only I’m left. Life is such a beautiful thing, but time will always steal that away.’ Emin’s eyes flashed a sense of sentimentality at this point.

‘Resha… What will you do if you’re still here?’

He ended the two paragraphs with a final stroke at the top.

‘To: The one who gave me happiness’

He closed his notebook and glanced at the darkening pastures, staring into the distance without movements.

Chapter 251: Tactics 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen hurriedly looked for some white bread in the kitchen and cleaned up the dust on him. Returning to the master bedroom, he changed into a lime-colored robe he took from the wardrobe, throwing the soot-covered shirt to wash before resting comfortably for the first time in a long while.

The next day, Garen was up before the sun was even up. In the living room, the little girl had already started work. Obviously she had the keys to this house.

He sat on the couch, watching as the little girl served him a plate of slice apples and some bread along with some warm goat milk.

"Enjoy your meal." The little girl Nicol performed a rough imitation of a greeting and turned back to the kitchen with haste.

Garen sipped the goat milk slightly. It’s thick and tasted fishy. Garen suspected something’s been added to it.

He raised the glass and scrutinized the milk. It’s got bits of yellowish substance floating around which he suspected was raw egg yolk.

Footsteps clopped on the stairs as Emin descended from the first floor. He wore an off-white robe and looked joyous.

Taking a seat in front of Garen, Emin took a slice of Garen’s bread and bit into it.

"Did you have a good rest?"

"It was great, Teacher." Garen nodded.

"Very well." Emin nodded back, "Today onward, we’ll converse using the Lush Forest dialect. This town was pretty cut off from the rest of the country. Aside from the common language of the empire, they only use their own dialect. They wouldn’t be able to understand any other dialects or languages. Furthermore, your Lush Forest dialect is somewhat different from the common language, this should be good enough for secrecy."

"I have no comment on that." Garen answered.

"Good, then we can start." Emin’s second half of the sentence was spoken entirely in the Lush Forest dialect. It sounded accurate too, something Garen wasn’t expecting.

"Teacher, how do I start learning tactics?" Garen asked formally.

"Tactics…" Emin muttered, as if to organize his thoughts.

The little girl Nicol appeared with Emin’s breakfast and set it down in front of him carefully. After silently curtsying at Emin, she turned and left.

She cleaned her hands on her black apron and exited the building, gently closing the door as she did.

When the little girl was out of earshot, Emin took his own glass of goat milk and said as he sipped on it.

"Tactics are the basics of any Luminarists and the foundation of all Luminarists’ abilities. This you need to remember."

He dipped his finger into his glass without manners and started drawing on the table.

A circular-shape appeared on the table with several sections.

"You should know that the Science Pictorial have found out a long time ago, that organisms were made up of microscopic cells." Emin retracted his index finger, "Cells make up tissues, which make up organs, which make up systems, and those make up a whole organism. You should know this, right?"

"Of course. This is the basics of Biology, we have learned about it." Garen nodded.

"Our tactics is basically the same as that. It’s just like a cell of an organism. They form the tissues, the organs, the systems, and become our own totem at the end. This is what you’ll go through in the future." Emin answered simply. "Tactics are also units. Professionally, we call them unit tactics. They are what we base our totem creatures on. Every Luminarist would create their own totem this way, no exceptions."

"Teacher, there are countless cells in an organism, if we have to create the same structures in a totem, don’t we have to build an insane amount of tactics?" Garen frowned.

"This is the core of what we learn. First, you will learn about the structure of a single tactic, an active unit. It is what forms everything else." Emin said seriously. "You will use active units in the future to build your own tissues, organs, systems, and finally a real living totem. This is what you have to do."

"That’s… a huge project…" Even if he reached the top of Martial Arts in his past life, this was still shocking to him. There are trillions of cells in an organism’s body, if he construct it one by one, it’s impossible to construct a totem even until the end of his life.

"What’s wrong? Disheartened?" Emin smiled. "Aren’t you a genius? You aren’t beaten with this little setback, are you?"

"So many Luminarists have successfully constructed their own totem, that means there’ll be some sort of pattern to it!" Garen answered with confidence.

"Not bad." Emin nodded with approval. "Let’s finish up our breakfast. I only told you what direction to take, you’ll need to learn to use the tools of the trade."

"Okay."

Both of them sped through their breakfast and went up the stairs to a white room that is reminiscent of a laboratory.

There was a huge rectangular table that took up half the room. A piece of black cloth was used to cover up something on the table.

Emin closed the door and locked it.

He walked in front of the black cloth and yanked at it.

Flutter!

The black cloth landed on the ground, unveiling the object.

Garen took it in with a breath, his face in disbelief.

The whole table had one very delicate-looking apparatus made with a transparent metal with silver sheen. Within the area of a palm, there were hundreds on faint silver components turning with gears.

The details on the instrument was so precise, it exuded a sense of purity and cold steel.

The whole apparatus was like a detailed toy, it kept dropping a small aqueous silver ball, from left to right, top to bottom, until it dropped into a silvery container.

On the apparatus that’s at least five meters long, there were thousands of components as big as a fingernail functioning as they’re meant to.

Emin walked in front of the apparatus, sporting a businesslike expression.

"I will be teaching you about one of the two most important tools of a Luminarist, unit factory."

"Unit factory?" Garen repeated the noun, his gaze still fixed on the instrument.

"Yes, just like what it’s called, it’s a factory that produces units." Emin nodded and answered. "This particular one is mine, it produces my totem White Bear." He paused.

"As I have said before, totem creatures were created from unit tactics. Your father is also a Luminarist, you would have seen totems before, so I won’t talk about that. Active units were the bedrock of everything. When a Luminarist studied and learned a creature’s active unit, he will be able to use unit factories to clone them, slowly building it up to a higher level of structure and ultimately, become a totem. Basically, it’s a tool to duplicate unit tactics to be formed into tissues, organs, systems and totems."

He covered the instrument with the black cloth.

"You’ll get one in the future as you’ll need one. Next, we’ll look at the second tool."

He walked to the other corner of the room, in front of a small table.

"This is a whole series of tools. Before unit factories can reproduce active units, where do they come from? That’s where the Luminarists have to search for themselves."

"Search?" Garen was confused. "Isn’t it a standard blueprint that everyone can use? Like your White Bear, won’t I be able to build it if I want to?"

"There’s also that. Learning a standard model and produce based on that, that’s the easiest way." Emin nodded, "Pretty observant, not bad. This is also why different Luminarists have different paths. The stronger and richer their inheritance, the stronger their totem will be. Hence, all Luminarists will be extra cautious about their own knowledge, because it literally represents their power."

Emin paused again, "Since you are my student, you’ll have to walk the same path as I did, but I’m not only proficient with White Bear, I know about other totems too. But let’s put that aside for now."

He pointed at a white instrument that looks mildly similar to a microscope on Earth.

"This is a microscope, it can show you enlarged images of objects. It can enlarge images up to 800 times their original size. It’s one of the medium-range ones on the market. Beside that are petri dish, forceps, magnifying glass, microdissection needle, tripod, asbestos net, bunsen burner, tube holder, blade tweezers, slides, coverslips…" Emin introduced the whole set to Garen.

Garen looked at the familiar equipments.

"These are definitely the same as the ones on Earth…" He thought.

At the end of his introduction, Emin sighed,

"Alas, I only have so much money. The RAL just came out with a new tool, but I don’t have the money to buy it."

He stood beside his table.

"These are the two things Luminarists must have, one to research, another to reproduce."

"I get it, active units are what forms everything, but how do active units come from?" Garen asked.

"This question is very crucial." Emin nodded with approval. "Their origins can be from anywhere. There are countless types of creatures in the world, Luminarists seek to research strong creatures and use silver to mimic their powers. The active units we talk about, are actually from the creatures in the nature."

"Creatures in the nature… If that’s the case, theoretically, any beings can be used as a totem?" Garen asked curiously.

"Of course. As long as you dig deep enough to understand the cells of a creature, you can use them as your totem," Emin nodded, smiling. "Of course, there’s a limit to everyone’s vigor, if you want to study everything but lack specificity, then nothing would come to fruition. Your totem may not even win against the most average Luminarist."

Chapter 252: Tactics 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I understand now. Many Luminarists specialize in one type of totem generation after generation, and expand that type to a really high level, so it grows stronger and stronger. So unless you’re an ultimate genius researcher, there’s no Luminarist who could catch up to the results of their cumulative studies over generations while being distracted." Garen nodded in understanding.

"As long as you understand. So what you need to do now is first learn how to use these two sets of items. Especially the unit factory, you must make your own unit factory from now on as well. Otherwise, you won’t even have to think about constructing your own totem," Emin advised him solemnly.

"Yes." In that instant it was as though Garen returned to his time on Earth, carefully listening to the teacher speaking.

Emin began to teach Garen how to use the two sets of tools. And the latter listened with unusual raptness as well, concentrating hard.

But after they began practical practise, Emin noticed with some regret that although Garen was terrifyingly talented at making blueprints, he was still slightly slow in understanding how to use the two types of tools.

For that reason he sighed a lot in succession, venting the unhappiness within.

However, he didn’t get to sigh for long.

When it came to using these two tools, the microscope used for research was fine, but the unit factory on the other hand did indeed use up a lot of concentration and energy. Garen crouched clumsily in front of the intricate factory, following the construction process step-by-step. This thing took at least one hour for every cycle. If you followed the mercury ball while even slightly distracted, it would be extremely hard to observe the whole process of creating the factory carefully. At the same time, you needed to understand the actual timings and methods of using it.

"Teacher, I didn’t see this part properly, let’s go again."

"Okay."

An hour later…

"Teacher, please repeat this part again."

"Fine."

Two hours passed."

"Teacher, I used a little too much force there. Please start again."

"No problem."

Three hours passed…

"Teacher, I was slightly nervous just now, so my hand moved too quickly. Once more please!"

"..."

Six hours later…

"Teacher, I was too agitated, I didn’t pay attention at the fourth part. Again please!"

Emin looked at Garen’s excited, energetic face.

The student and teacher stared at each other wordlessly.

Coo-coo… coo-coo…

There was the sound of an owl from outside.

"Teacher, what’s the matter?" Garen blinked, and asked in a low voice.

Coo…

Emin’s stomach made a dull sound.

"Is it this late already…?" Only then did Garen notice that the sky outside was already pitch black.

"Are you… always this energetic?" Emin’s feelings were complicated, as he looked at Garen’s expression of excitement.

"It’s okay, I’m young, and I have stamina."

Garen smiled.

"Forget it, I’ll bring you something to eat, you go ahead on your own. You should have clearly seen how I use it. Is that okay?"

"No problem." Garen nodded. "Sorry, Teacher, I made you stay hungry with me."

"It’s okay, this is your first time in contact with all this. It’s very normal for you to be so curious about it." Emin waved his head, but deep inside he knew. When it came to learning how to use the unit factory, most normal people would start feeling dizzy after two hours of consecutive use, ending up mentally exhausted. This was because the Luminescence caused the human body a certain amount of damage. If one came into close contact with it for too long, their body wouldn’t be able to withstand it.

But Garen had been working on it for more than ten hours, and still didn’t feel any discomfort. This meant that the time Garen could spend on this was several times that of other Luminarists!

When Emin walked out of the lab, he once more harbored deep suspicions towards everything he thought he knew about this world before.

"Looks like I knew too few Luminarists before this." He shook his head and sighed as he went down the stairs, looking as though he aged a lot suddenly.

After having dinner, Emin finally gave in and returned to his room to rest. He left Garen alone in the lab, learning enthusiastically, using the unit factory over and over again. He seemed to have returned to those biology or chemistry classes back on Earth when he listened intently.

Of the three strongest specialties of the terrifying Divine Statue Technique, two of them were recovery power and endurance. This was when they shone the most.

Before Emin went to sleep, he saw the light in the lab shining.

In the middle of the night when he got up to use the toilet, he raised his head to look at the lab, and the light was still on.

Early the next morning, he yawned as he walked out of the bedroom, and the light in the lab was still shining.

"It’s the first time, so no wonder…" He sighed feelingly, listening to the sounds of Garen moving about in the lab, and went downstairs to eat breakfast himself.

Noon.

Emin sat in the courtyard, lazily tanning in the sun.

"The weather sure is great…"

He narrowed his eyes, looking at the cornflower sky. The golden sunlight shone on his body, warming his entire body up.

The little girl Nicol was hanging out the freshly-washed sheets and clothes next to him.

"Is Garen still upstairs?"

"Yes, mister," Nicol replied hastily.

"It sure is good to be young…" Emin sighed deeply. He had always taken good care of himself. If he hadn’t been grievously injured in that intense battle before, there was no way he would end up as old as he was now.

The sky gradually darkened.

After dinner, Emin looked at Nicol, who was washing up the dishes.

"Is Garen still upstairs?"

"Yes, mister," Nicol replied hastily.

Emin touched his beard, and said nothing.

At night.

Emin put down the novel in his hand, and glanced at the second floor.

"Garen still hasn’t come down?"

"It seems so… mister." Nicol was crouching by the fireplace and adding more firewood, and replied hesitantly.

The third day…

The fourth day…

Ker-chak.

The door to the second floor lab finally opened.

Nicol picked up the empty tray on the floor outside the door and was about to leave when she suddenly heard the door open. She quickly turned around.

"Mr Garen?"

"Teacher! Teacher!" A black shadow dashed past her, and raced down the stairs.

Emin walked out of his room, yawning.

"It’s so early in the morning, what are you yelling about."

The black shadow instantly trampled upstairs, ran in front of Emin and stood still.

It was Garen, who had lived in the lab for four days.

He frowned deeply, and held up something in his hand.

"Teacher, the lamp oil ran out."

Emin released a long breath.

"If there’s no more oil, go rest. After messing around for so long, what results do you have? Don’t tell me you fell asleep in there?"

"I got it!" Garen grinned, revealing his pearly whites.

"Okay… Four days, that’s still considered normal." Emin nodded.

Garen also released a deep breath.

He already knew that his talent when it came to instruments of high delicacy like the unit factory was only so-so. This thing needed a high degree of concentration and an accurate hand of corresponding calculations at the same time, and he was really not used to it. His body had already regained his reflexes from the peak-level Body Hardening Technique, so if he lost his focus for even a moment, he would emit some miniscule vibrations.

This was the result of his body and spirit not merging fully yet. Although he could already use the Four Major Secret Techniques, he still needed some time to feel it out.

It was just that this didn’t affect how much he could actually use his martial arts. After all, his martial arts didn’t have any delicate moves, they were opened spectacularly and closed large.

For those four days, he basically didn’t sleep or rest, only occasionally eating something. That was how he managed to learn how to control the unit factory in one go.

After eating breakfast, he took a little break.

It was only after Emin confirmed that Garen was still feeling quite good, and didn’t show any signs of insufficient rest, that the teacher agreed to demonstrate the manipulation process.

In front of the lab door, there was a light silver horizontal line, glowing with a faint silver light.

Emin and Garen stepped across the line, and walked into the lab.

"This line at the door is a little device to prevent normal people from seeing the objects inside this room. It’s another application of tactics, one of the practical ones to use in daily life. I’ll teach it to you next time." Emin walked up to the unit factory.

"Now, let me see what method of control you’ve picked up."

Garen nodded.

He stood the furthest-left end of the unit factory, and picked up a small silver ball using the pliers in his right hand. He then lightly placed it on a slanted slope on the factory machine.

Brr…

The small ball rolled down the slope slowly, and dropped into a silver cylindrical container. Soon enough, in the midst of clacking sounds, the three silver pipes connected to the container began to flow with a translucent liquid.

The three paths of liquid split up and flowed towards three directions. When they passed through a small round archways, Garen instantly reached out his hand to press the archways, as though adjusting something.

The three liquid paths instantly became a lot clearer. Passing through the archway, they gathered into one silver pipe, and flowed into a metal device like a merry-go-round. Once the liquid stopped flowing completely, the merry-go-round began to turn slowly, making a melodic sound like wind chimes.

Garen quickly reached out to adjust some small switches and buttons around the merry-go-round, turning the many dials to the optimum numerical degree.

After the wooden horses took two rounds, he counted silently to himself, and reached out again to adjust these dials, his accuracy and speed absolutely on point.

Pak!

The spinning stopped.

A drop of viscous silver-colored water dripped down from the exact center, falling precisely into the neck of a purple curve-necked flask.

Pff!

A flash of purple smoke instantly rose from the curve-necked flask, following the curved neck as it flowed down, darting into a large silver ball the size of a human head.

Garen quickly walked up to the round ball, his fingers pressing rapidly on a panel there, as though he was keying in some data.

In a mere ten seconds, he keyed in twenty numbers, forming several combinations of different lengths. And this was just the beginning.

After a whole half an hour, drops of silver liquid dripped out of the round ball with a smacking sound, falling into the last large beaker.

These silver liquids looked like silver grains of said, flowing slowly. At the same time, they looked like some microorganism, squirming ever so slightly.

"You did it." Emin looked at the silver-colored liquid in the beaker closely, and with satisfaction. "Not bad, there was not a single mistake there."

Garen heaved a sigh of relief, and pulled his hand back from the panel.

"Teacher, I learned how to use the tools. Now what?"

"You learned how to use the microscope as well?"

"That’s a lot simpler." Garen walked up to the microscope with an air of familiarity, and easily set it up. He sucked up a drop of silver liquid, did the preparations, and began to observe.

Emin nodded, satisfied.

"Not bad, not bad. You’ve done all the preparatory work, so let’s begin with the first step."

"The first step?"

"Go out into the wild on your own, and find the totem creature you want. Bugs, beasts, birds, anything works. Go ahead, we’ll start constructing from the basic levels. But you should still choose carefully, this is the direction your potential totem will take, the totem you will rely on for everything. So it’s best to be more careful when choosing the rough direction." Emin smiled. "Although I’m not specialized enough because I study everything and ended up still being a very average, normal Luminarist, the benefit is that my student will have more directions to expand. First, you choose something, anything, and as a demonstration, I’ll show you how to construct a totem, as well as what steps are required in between. In general, which tactics are needed to create organizations, organs, systems. I’ll show you each of them, one by one. Of course, other than the White Bear, which is inherited, I haven’t gotten too deeply into the others. It’s just enough to finish constructing a simple totem. If you want to upgrade it, you’ll have to do the deeper research yourself."

"I understand." Garen nodded.

"There are two types of totems, one is core and the other basic. Now go, find a creature you want to make into a totem in the wild around here. This will be the first basic totem I’ll give you. Basic totems have very weak abilities, but they’ll have a certain benefit for your daily life. Such as reconnaissance, such as cleaning up, such as collecting items, or using it as a tool etc."

Chapter 253: Totem 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"So I have to find a target by myself?" Garen nodded thoughtfully. "Are there any basic conditions or requirements?"

"It’s good as long as it’s not too complicated. Since you just began, you just have to learn the basic frame, the rest you can explore at your own pace in the future," Emin advised him. "Alright, go. You still have all morning, find me the totem you want to make. Remember, it has to be something you need, and something you can use. Every creature has their own unique power, don’t choose carelessly."

"Yes."

Garen nodded respectfully.

"Then I’ll go wash up now. Once you return after catching what you want, we’ll officially begin the construction demonstration." Emin yawned, turned around, and walked out of the room.

Garen found a large glass bottle and a pair of boarskin gloves. Then he went downstairs and immediately left the house.

There were a lot more young men in town in the morning. They were mostly carrying bows and arrows, hunting knives, and wore clothes made of fur and leather, as they came and left in small groups. Some were even carrying their freshly acquired prey on their backs.

Garen followed the main road until he left the town. The long grey robes he wore slightly piqued the curiosity of the townsfolk. Several children who were chasing each other about instantly hid behind a wall when they saw him approaching, and watched him guardedly.

Upon exiting the town, he saw a large, wide field of hills and grass spread out in front of him. Small clumps of forests dotted the landscape, mostly shorter shrubs that didn’t grow too well. The lush green forests and dark green grassy plains practically merged into one. Some small white butterflies danced circles around the little flowers on the grass, and groups of unnamed birds occasionally flew across the sky, making soft shrill cries.

Not far away from the town, there was a little stream about three or four meters wide. This was the source of the famous Red River, and was exceptionally clean because it consisted of melted snow water from the snowy peaks of the mountains towering into the clouds in the distance.

Garen walked up to the side of the Red River, crouched down, and began scouring through the grasses and moist mud.

"What kind of a totem do I need?"

That was how he asked himself.

"What kind of a totem would be of use to me?"

He uprooted the grass, and saw a troop of black ants slowly crawling across the black soil. He looked at them but didn’t move. Then he turned his gaze away, to another clump of dark green grass.

There was a big fat green caterpillar resting quietly on the thin and narrow grass leaves. It was covered in spikes, its four lazy eyes looking completely listless.

On a little yellow flower next to it, there was a wild bee with a thin black thorax. It was crawling back on forth on the fingernail-sized flower stamen, its legs covered with yellow pollen. It was obviously out collecting pollen.

"Ants, caterpillar, wild bee…"

Garen shook his head slightly.

"They’re too weak. Although they have simple make-ups, it wouldn’t be much help to me even if I succeeded."

He stood up, and continued walking towards the hills and plains in the distance.

"If it has to be useful to me, then it better have some strength so it can support me in daily life. If it can fly, it can be used to obtain information, for reconnaissance, and as a lookout. If it has a certain offensive ability, it can also be used to defend. In that case… the best option is a type of bird."

He glanced at a few patches of forest not far away. There was the light trilling of birds there.

After crossing a few hills, he quickly chose the largest patch of forest and walked right in.

The forest was lush and green, with clean air. A few children were wandering about inside, gathering something. These children were dressed in rags, looked sickly and pale, and their bodies were also pitifully thin. They each carried a large basket on their backs. Some were filled with plants and wild fruits, while others barely had anything.

These children only took one look at Garen when he came in, but they soon started ignoring him, looking back at the ground instead as they dug.

There were many types of birds resting here, raising a continuous chatter.

Garen looked up and identified them carefully. There were many types of birds on those trees, almost five or six in all. They came in different sizes, and most were black. Only a few were blue or green.

"It has to be slightly bigger, with offensive power, and decent flying speed…" Garen realized he didn’t recognize any of the birds. Looking around, his gaze fell on a dirty boy in the distance.

Like the others, this boy wore grey sackcloth clothes and carried a large basket on his back. His hair was matted and messy, but there was a green parrot perched on his shoulder, which let him stand out from the rest.

Garen walked over to him, and stood beside the boy. "Are these birds yours?" He tried to soften his tone as much as possible.

"Yes, sir. Do you require anything?" The boy straightened his bent back, looking at Garen in confusion. This strange lord came into the forest and starting looking left and right, but no one knew what he was doing.

"I want to ask about what species of birds you have here, do you know?" Garen pulled out a small copper piece and flicked it towards the boy.

The little boy quickly caught it in a flurry. A copper piece may not be able to buy much elsewhere, but it could still buy some snacks here. He instantly broke into a grin.

"Birds? I know about them."

"Know your bird! Know your bird!"1 The green parrot on his shoulder started squawking.

"Shut up, Hans!" The boy grew flustered and angry. "If you go on like this I won’t give you dinner!"

"Just explain it to me properly, if you do it well I’ll give you another." Garen looked at the green parrot smilingly.

"No problem. My little sister loved keeping birds. After she left, I started liking it too, so I’m really good at this!" The boy thumped his chest.

"Know your sis! Know your sis!"2

"Shut up!!" The boy’s face flushed bright red, and he flicked the green parrot’s head angrily.

Garen couldn’t help but laugh as he watched the boy and bird combo. They seemed to get along very well.

"I want to find a type of bird that can fly fast, has some strength, and some attack power. Do you know any types?" he listed out his conditions.

"Then you’ve found the right man, sir!" The little boy wiped the snot that was about to leak out of his nose. "According to your requirements, the most suitable candidate is definitely a hawk."3

"A hawk, is it? What’s the fastest hawk here?" Garen nodded and asked.

"All our hawks here are pretty fast… and most of them are the cunning blue hawks. It’s not too big, and it’s really fast. It can scratch open someone’s skin in the blink of an eye! Its claws are the sharpest, and it really likes to steal everyone’s chicks," the little boy replied in details.

"Are there any other types of birds? Or maybe it doesn’t have to be a bird," Garen asked, frowning. Although the blue hawk fit his requirements, he still doesn’t like this sort of eagle that only knows how to steal chickens.

"If it doesn’t have to be a bird…" The little boy scratched his hair. "Oh! There is a type, but it’s not a bird, it’s a bug."

"Oh? What is it?" Garen looked interested.

"Neon butterflies!"4 The boy looked uncomfortable. "The bigger ones are as big a a washbasin. They’re strong, very beautiful, and really strange too. Most butterflies aren’t fast, but these are super fast, even faster than normal birds. Only eagles can compare to them. And even more annoyingly, they’re extremely poisonous. If a person accidentally breathes in their powder, their whole body will get poisoned and grow numb. If it’s just a little more serious, it could kill you! It’s terrifying!"

"Oh? There are butterflies like that? Where, show me?" Garen was instantly sold.

"I’m not going. You just have to walk in that direction, just walk all the way straight, and you’ll see those annoying butterflies in no time. Their whole body is poisonous, and they took over the whole patch of forest. If you see any huge butterflies, without any speck of impurity in their blue, that’s them." The boy pointed in a direction as he explained.

"Thanks." Garen flicked his second copper piece, and took large strides in the direction the boy pointed.

Leaving the little forest, Garen followed the direction the boy led him to. His steps were quick, and more condensed little forests soon appeared around him. Signs of human activity gradually decreased, while the tire tracks and footsteps on the ground rapidly vanished as well.

In the distance, he could begin to see the white snowy peaks reaching into the clouds.

Very soon, he saw the neon butterflies the boy was talking about.

Under some dark shady trees, a group of blue butterflies glowed with fluorescence, dancing in the shadows. It was as though they had fluorescent powder scattered all over them.

These butterflies danced about soundlessly. The smallest were palm-sized, the largest had nearly a meter in wingspan. The long furry bodies were fully exposed, and creeped out anyone who looked at them.

Garen picked up a stone from the ground, narrowed his eyes, and tossed it at them.

Psst!

Like a sharp arrow, the stone tore through the air and accurately hit the largest neon butterfly.

In that instant, it was like poking a beehive. A large swarm of neon butterflies rushed out of the forest, flooding the air as they came for Garen, as though the blue lights had instantly merged into an ocean.

Garen kicked the ground, and a big piece of black soil scattered through the air, carrying specks of grass with it. They rained down everywhere, beating on the large swathe of neon butterflies around him.

In the midst of many dull plopping sounds, the blue lights began to fall and dim, while the piercing smell of poisonous powder spread through the air.

Garen held his breath. With a flash of his steps, he appeared in front of the largest neon butterfly. Picking it up with a gloved hand, he stuffed it into the glass bottle and turned heel immediately.

He hadn’t gone far when suddenly a huge swarm of neon butterflies surged out behind. They were extremely fast, and could almost catch up to a running Garen even without flying in a straight line.

Garen took one look back, and applied more force under his feet. This gave him a boost of speed, and he left the neon butterflies in the dust.

He gave his body a jolt, instantly and quietly throwing off countless fine particles of blue powder from his body. They were blown away by the wind, and he only started breathing again after all the poison powder had vanished.

Holding up the bottle to see, he noticed that the neon butterfly wasn’t completely dead yet, moving ever so slightly in the bottle.

He was considered satisfied with this sort of butterfly. It wasn’t slow, it was highly poisonous, and rather strong as well. Compared to normal bugs that died with a stomp, there was a layer of thick keratin on the surface of these butterflies, so it seemed to be as strong as a mouse. That would mean it had no problem delivering messages.

"The only weakness is that it’s not very good at camouflage, but even so, it will do." Garen thought back to the blue-scaled snake encountered before. Compared to those totem creatures, the neon butterfly was a flying animal, and it wasn’t part of the hawk’s menu. Even if it was rather flashy, the other advantages were enough to mask those little flaws.

　************

In the experiment lab

Emin carefully wiped his mouth with a white napkin, holding up the neon butterfly’s bottle to observe it.

"It’s my first time making this type of neon butterfly, but I have researched butterflies before. Even though I didn’t go into detail, I do know some." He put down the bottle. "So you’re sure you want the neon butterfly?"

"Of course." Garen was standing beside him, and nodded when he was asked.

"Alright then. A Luminarist will have a core totem and a normal totem for support purposes. As your teacher, I can make you your first totem for free. Consider it my present to you. But if you want to change to another a totem next time, you’ll have to study and create it yourself. Do you understand?"

"I understand." Garen nodded."

"Alright then, let us begin."

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. Sounds like a swear, hence his embarrassment.

2. Same as above.

3. 鹰, can be translated as hawk, falcon or eagle.

4. 荧光蝴蝶, lit. fluorescent butterfly. Neon sounds more like a name, though.

Chapter 254: Totem 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Emin nodded, and put the butterfly bottle on the microscope.

"Creating a totem is basically using silver to imitate a living creature. How to imitate? First, you need to know the creature’s biological make-up, only then can you successfully imitate it."

He pointed out his index finger, and slowly started sketching mid air.

His fingertip drew lines of silver-white light in the air, forming silver-white threads.

As the threads slowly faded and disappeared, but before the vanished completely, all the silver-white threads Emin drew each formed a tiny figure 6. All the 6’s quickly and randomly matched up, forming many inconsistent figures that looked like badges. Just like a oval insect’s egg being wrapped up in many large circles.

"This figure represents analysis. It’s used especially for analyzing any creature’s internal make-up. It can trigger the analyzing ability in your brain, in order to quickly analyze any creature. We call it the analysis tactic. It’s one of the three basic Luminarist tactics. I’ll teach it to you later."

Emin pointed at the the floating figures, and a wave of ripples spread from that spot. With a whoosh, the figures dart into the bottle, landing on the neon butterfly.

Soon, silver tattoo lines appeared on the neon butterfly’s body.

Emin explained, "Normally, analyzing a creature requires sufficient knowledge, experience, and accumulation. If you haven’t accumulated enough, your analysis tactic wouldn’t get many results. After all, this is just a quick analysis. It’s only suitable for Luminarists who are familiar with this type of creature."

Beside him, Garen nodded, looking at the butterfly in the bottle with his undivided attention.

"Now, I’m analyzing this neon butterfly’s body systems. Its life would always be dependent on some certain systems. This neon butterfly… mm… the survival system, that’s the most basic instinct. A flying system, and defense system. There are three parts. It’s made of three parts in total, that won’t be too hard."

Emin flicked his finger, and the silver tattoos on the neon butterfly instantly began to dim.

"After that, I’ll imitate the basic units of the three part systems in order. At these times, I need to have completely researched and understood creature cells. I can only proceed after knowing the root principles. I researched butterflies before, so I’ll skip this part."

Emin walked up to the long table with the unit factory, bent down and pulled out a large black box. He opened the cover, revealing blocks after blocks of pure silver bricks. All square and proper, they looked unexpectedly clean and brand new.

Emin picked up a silver brick, and drew in the air again with his other hand. Soon enough, he had carved out another figure.

This time, it was an extremely complex figure, lined up like rows of mathematical formulae, or like a passage of unknown words.

As Emin wrote his figures, the silver block in his other hand also began to slowly melt, turning to liquid like mercury and floating over his palm. It merged into a silver ball.

"This is the second basic tactic: forging. Right now, I’m forging different units for the three systems at the same time, so it’s a little more complicated. Actually, all these figures are used to move the silver, and use them to replicate the principles and scenes in my head. That’s why we also call this tactic: replicate. Anyway, it’s up to you what you want to call it."

Garen stared at his teacher’s movements closely and nodded without speaking, terrified that he would miss even the slightest movement.

The round silver ball in Emin’s hand dissolved quickly, revealing three small balls inside.

The three small balls formed a triangle and spun rapidly, as though forming a whole.

Emin pointed at the three silver balls and said, "These three things are the basic units for the three systems that I forged. Don’t be fooled by appearances, the structure inside is actually very complicated, and completely different. What I’m going to do now is put these units into the unit factory, and then perform large scale replicating. Then I’ll assemble them to make a model of the three large systems. The assembly also requires a third basic tactic: assimilation."

Garen nodded slowly.

"Three steps in total: analyse, forge, and assimilate. You use these three tactics to control and lead, is that right? Teacher."

"That is true, it looks simple on the surface. What you need to do is replicate a creature using silver. These three tactics are the most basic of the basic, and all totems come from them. No matter how complicated the totem, it must go through these three steps." Emin put down the silver balls in his hand. "Of course, after all that is done, there’s still the final step."

"There’s still a final step?"

"Of course." Emin smiled. "After completing the three steps, the silver totem formed is just a model made out of silver. But creatures themselves require food as an energy source to support their movements. What about totems? If they want to move, they naturally require energy. And this is the last step that needs our help."

"What is it?" Garen asked.

Emin threw a unit into the unit factory, and began to adjust and replicate it as he replied,

"The last step is to provide the energy. We also call it activation."

"Activation?"

"That’s right, this is the basis for all Luminarists. In the past, it was also called lighting. Lighting the lamps to illuminate, that is how the term Luminarists first originated," Emin explained.

"How do you light it, then?" Garen pressed on.

"That is our most pivotal talent." Emin pointed at his head. "Here. Anyone who can be a Luminarist, has a special appraisal quality. Our power is shapeless and immaterial, and it can’t influence anything other than silver. But it has the mystical effect of giving silver life."

"No wonder Luminarists use silver as their materials…" Garen instantly understood.

"It’s actually very easy to activate something, but according to the difference in our appraisal, the strength of the totems activated will also differ."

"And how is my appraisal power?" Garen asked with slight anticipation.

"Unfortunately, your appraisal is very normal… Back then, at your home, I checked for you on the sly." Emin shrugged and said bluntly. "In other words, the totems you light will not be given any special extra effect."

Garen thought as much. Vanderman’s appraisal was very average too, so it would be hard for his son to be Prodigy-level.

"Those Prodigy-level Luminarists, are there totems really strong?"

"I saw one peak Prodigy-level Luminarist’s totem, it was an owl used for support. This prodigy’s appraisal ability was to give totems three time the power the original had." Emin reminisced slightly, "That owl was half a person tall, and it had terrifying power. It could actually fight on even ground with a lion totem, and eventually defeated the lion totem. It tore the lion into shreds."

"An owl defeating a lion, huh…?" Garen could also imagine this strange scene, and felt a little melancholy inside.

"Alright, enough about that. You are far from Prodigy-level now. But your advantage is with precision blueprints. A strong precision blueprint ability is enough to give the totems you forge impressive stability. Master-level precision blueprints would also have a great impact on high-level precision blueprints and fixing totems. With your skill, if you expand it well, you can accept jobs from some Prodigy-level Luminarists, and help them to make unactivated totems and reap some rewards. Of course, the precondition is that you must be able to completely analyze the principles." Emin continued to console him.

"I can still do that?" Garen’s eyes lit up, and he nodded solemnly.

"First, I’ll explain the principles of analyzing tactics…" Emin didn’t waste a moment, and immediately started to explain the details to Garen.

The teacher and student gathered in the lab, and a whole day passed in a moment. Other than eating, drinking and answering Nature’s call, they basically did not leave the lab.

With Emin’s careful teaching, Garen also began to slowly understand some basic Luminarist knowledge and secrets.

Luminarists usually did not write any books. They tended to teach their own knowledge verbally just like this, in order to prevent their knowledge and inheritance from leaking out to others. Every Luminarist could be called a biochemist. Their appraisal talent was their research tool.

In four days, as the neon butterfly totem slowly took shape, Garen witnessed the whole process of forming a totem step by step. From analysis to assimilation, each step was further divided into many smaller steps, exceptionally intricate and detailed. The final assimilation was especially hard. With his teacher’s tutelage, he used a Master-level precision blueprint and, step by step, put the units into groups, and then put the groups into units, systems. In the end, they had utterly formed a complete butterfly totem.

At last, it was time for the final activation.

************

Garen stood quietly in front of a small table, looking at the silver neon butterfly totem on it.

The totem was silent and dull, without a trace of life. It looked just like an intricate silver model, gorgeous and graceful.

Garen looked at Emin on his right, and the latter nodded slightly at him.

"I’ll start now."

Garen pointed his index finger, and pressed the surface of the neon butterfly lightly.

"Kandas vieira (Ten Thousand Mammoths Traction)… Silversa (May the Silver be ever-luminescent, the end is rebirth) …"

As he chanted lightly, a pale silver halo of light rose slowly behind him.

"Hildaves (where I am)... Runsa (there is life)."

As soon as Garen’s voice stopped, the room descended into silence.

The two of them look at the silver totem quietly, and disappointment flashed in both their eyes.

Did they fail?

The same thought appeared in both their minds.

Garen also understood that if the first activation didn’t work, that meant his appraisal quality may not even be average-level. It could only be the lowest level.

"It’s okay, if you don’t succeed this time there’s always next time." Emin consoled him from the side. "With just the Master-level precision blueprint ability, your abilities from now on will be guaranteed."

"That’s all I can do." Garen nodded, feeling slightly helpless. The silver halo behind him slowly scattered.

"Let’s go in to eat."

One followed after the other, as the two men left the lab.

At the very end, Garen looked at the butterfly totem on the table once more, and sighed imperceptibly. He began closing the door behind him.

Smack!

Suddenly there was a small noise from behind him.

Garen’s whole body jolted.

In an instant, silver light erupted from behind him. Countless rays of blinding silver light shot out of the room, making his back shine like a sea of silver.

Just behind him, the silver butterfly on the table began to flap its wings slowly. It struggled a bit, and then leapt off the table, slowly taking flight.

Garen tilted his face to look at the butterfly, a hint of excitement and a hint of joy in his heart. He stretched out his index finger, and the butterfly landed on it.

"It worked…"

"Congratulations." Emin looked over from where he was standing by the stairs, with a similar expression of joy and relief.

Chapter 255: Achievement 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After dinner, the teacher and student duo left their little block and went out of the town, into a dark and deserted forest.

There wasn’t any sign of human habitation in these isolated woods. All they could hear were the strange noises of animals rustling past grass.

Emin wore all pitch black, holding a short staff in his hand. He tapped the ground once, lightly.

A silver ripple instantly spread from the tip of his staff, quickly rushing past underneath Garen’s feet as it spread far and wide in all direction. It soon vanished into the distant forest.

It was only when the ripple scattered that Emin raised up the staff in his hand and gave it a twirl. Silver engravings rose to the surface of the staff, looking especially evident in the dark night.

"We can start testing now," Emin said softly. "I cast an isolation tactic around us. Normal people can’t see us. Your neon butterfly is just a support totem, and you can change it any time you want later. But it’s still your first totem, so it has dome special meaning. It can demonstrate some totem-specific qualities for you. Are you ready?"

Garen was standing right opposite him, dressed all in grey, and nodded solemnly. He was holding a large bottle, and coiled up inside was his very first totem, the neon butterfly.

"I can feel it, the totem is like I got a new organ, an arm. It’s very lifelike and convenient. I can choose to control it, or give it a simple order for it to complete on its own. What a miraculous feeling," he said soft, as he opened the cap to the bottle.

Psst!

With a flash of blow, the neon butterfly immediately darted out of the bottle, and slowly landed on Garen’s shoulder. It was like a huge blue shawl, glowing with a pale blue fluorescent light in the night.

Emin’s palm paused, and a large white bobcat walked out slowly from behind him.

It was a meter and a half long, like a slightly smaller leopard. It walked soundlessly, its shoulders rising on both sides as it walked, and it licked its tongue greedily at times. In the night, its eyes glowed with an eerie green light.

Emin reached out his hand to pat the bobcat’s head.

"This is my support totem, Bobcat." He smiled, "As long as you can support them, you can create as many support totems as you want. After all, it’s your own talent keeping them afloat. Most Luminarists can only support one or two. The stronger ones can do four or five. Because support totems have simple structures, it’s easy to make them, so they’re usually treated as disposable items."

He glanced at the blue butterfly on Garen’s shoulder.

"If it’s like yours, you should be able to do more."

Garen nodded, and said bluntly,

"I can sense that my spirit can support a few more, probably about two."

"In other words, you can have two more support totems. If you add that to your core totem, that would be four totems. That is the extent of your talent." Emin nodded. "Alright, begin then. Let’s see, how does your neon butterfly fare in real battle?"

"Alright."

The two of them stopped talking, and retreated a few steps back at the same time, leaving the stage to the two totems.

Meoww!!

The white bobcat arched its back, and made a noise between that of a cat and a leopard. Its emerald eyes were fixed intently on the neon butterfly flying in front of it.

The white bobcat began to slowly walk circles around the neon butterfly.

The neon butterfly flapped its wings, rising higher and higher, as though trying to avoid direct conflict with the bobcat.

Suddenly, the neon butterfly pulled itself upwards. With a single meow, a white figure pounced into the sky, directly at where the butterfly was, and missed.

The neon butterfly immediately flew up in a curve, swaying uncertainly from left to right.

Pshh!

It dodged another pounce from the white shadow, and landed gracefully on a tree branch.

Having missed twice, the white bobcat seemed to get instinctively frustrated. It paced, making circles around the tree where the neon butterfly had stopped, and occasionally made deep howling sounds.

Suddenly its gaze turned sharp, and it dug its limbs onto the tree trunk, borrowing the momentum to leap up the tree.

The green tree trunk was ripped to shreds. Four white scars appeared on the whole and smooth tree trunk underneath its claws. The bobcat pounced at the neon butterfly with lightning speed.

Ka-chak!

The tree branch broke, and the butterfly took flight again. It flew higher up, but a white shadow quickly followed it, pressing it down with its claw as it landed nimbly on the ground.

But the bobcat had barely taken a few steps with the butterfly in its mouth when it started swaying, and eventually fell sideways onto the ground with a thud.

"It’s over." Emin clapped his hands as he walked over. "It counts as a draw. The bobcat just needed to bite down to break the neon butterfly. But at the same time, it was struck by the poison powder during those few failed pounces. Its internal systems were damaged, so it can’t move anymore.

"So you’re saying I chose well?" Garen also walked over as he asked.

"To be more precise, you controlled it well. A real neon butterfly wouldn’t be able to avoid a bobcat’s pounces so easily. I would have won with the first pounce." Emin shook his head with a smile. "But the neon butterfly’s main ability is its poison powder, that’s used to protect itself. It can fly rather fast, and it can fly in the rain as well. When faced with complicated geography, it can also be a good scout. Only problem is it can’t hide very well."

"That’s true." Garen nodded in agreement. "It glows blue in the night, it indeed can’t really camouflage."

"This is just your first totem, you can choose to change it later. There’s no rush." Emin waved his hand, "Regarding totems, there’s still one more crucial item."

He raised his staff, and dipped it lightly in front of Garen.

With a smacking sound the tip of the staff was pressing on Garen’s calf.

"Eh?" On the other hand, Garen looked curious. "This is…"

He noticed that the tip of the staff hadn’t actually touched the skin on his calf, as though it was being repelled by something.

He looked closely at where the tip of the staff was. There was a thin, transparent, pale blue membrane between the staff and his trousers.

"That is Totem Light." Emin pulled back his staff. "After a totem forms, this is the protective force field it reflects on its master. It covers the master’s whole body, and has no weak spot."

"So this is Totem Light?" Garen reached out his hand, looking at that extremely thin pale blue membrane expand as he stretched his hand. It was like a malleable layer of water, and extremely fascinating. "How is its protective power?"

"It’s usually twice as strong as that of the totem itself, or more." Emin smiled. "Do you know where it came from?"

Garen shook his head, waiting for his teacher to reply with careful concentration.

"A Luminarist has many totems, and each totem would bestow a protective force field on its master. The forces stack up, and are definitely stronger than the power of an individual totem. Besides, the defensive power of Totem Light usually stronger than the totem itself." Emin paused, "This is why, battles between Luminarists are usually fought by the totems, and you usually don’t attack the master first."

Garen understood.

"True, in that case, Luminarists would actually have a lot more defensive power than the totems themselves. It’s most important to deal with the totems first."

"That’s exactly it." Emin waved his hand, and the white bobcat on the floor instantly became a flash of white light that retreated behind him.

The neon butterfly also took to the air again, landing inside the large bottle in Garen’s hand. He stuffed it in mercilessly and stoppered the bottle.

Emin watched him keep it, and then raised his head to look at the night sky.

"It’s still early. Let’s walk back, and chat as we go."

"Yes, teacher." Garen nodded.

The two of them walked slowly down the path they had came, heading back towards the small town.

Emin held his staff, watching Garen as the latter walked ahead of his teacher carefully, testing the road for puddles and potholes to prevent Emin from stepping in one. The teacher smiled, comforted.

"Garen, the power of the totem itself will not harm its master. You must remember that. Aside from that, almost the large majority of Luminarists have support totems that aren’t that different from real living creatures. There is no increase in their power, they’re just like the creatures you see outside."

"Bobcats are bobcats, and neon butterflies are neon butterflies? They’re just like the original creature, so support totems are rarely strengthened, is that it?" Garen said in understanding.

"That’s it. But core totems are different." Emin sighed. "Take my core totem, White Bear, for example. Other than the superior strength that white bears are supposed to have, it also has thicker fur than regular white bears, so it can prevent damage from stronger lethal weapons."

Teacher, your White Bear didn’t come from a regular bear, did it?" Garen asked softly.

"Naturally." Emin nodded. "My line focuses on three animals, the Great White Bear, Black Panther, and Sabertooth Tiger. The Great White Bear is indeed no ordinary bear, it is a large white bear from northern tundra, and is the apex predator there."

Garen nodded in understanding.

Emin continued, "This extremely durable fur and skin was the result of many generations of strengthening. It’s a lot sturdier in defense than usual great white bears. When faced with regular bears, there won’t be any unforeseen accidents, the other side will lose utterly. That’s why if you want to choose a core totem in the future, you had also better choose a core totem that has some accumulation. Stand on the shoulders of giants, and you will go further, without having to start from scratch."

He sighed, "You must understand that, in the world of Luminarists, you can barely even protect yourself without real power."

Garen nodded silently. He suddenly remembered the large number of Luminarists who would die in the future war.

There would be the two consecutive crises. The first would be the war between the Royal Alliance of Luminarists and the Obscuro Society, in which Luminarists die by the hundreds.

The second would be the war between the Obscuro Society and the Terraflor Society, in which Luminarists die by the thousands.

At the end, the remaining Luminarists would not number up to a third of a thousand. A vast amount of knowledge will disappear because it was never recorded down. The age of the Luminarists, aside from partial knowledge from the very peak, will be reduced to a few schools of knowledge.

And Emin, would also die in the crossfires of the first war.

"Alright, let’s forget that for now. When we get back, you can start learning the three major basic tactics from me." Emin smiled. "These three basic tactics are actually very easy. The difificulty lies in here." He pointed at his head.

"In the accumulation of knowledge."

"That’s right. Luminarists without enough knowledge wouldn’t be able to analyze even the smallest, weakest insect. And Luminarists with enough knowledge, will be able to analyze practically anything." Emin smiled as he replied, "I’ll hand the three major basic tactics over to you. And then you can enter my underground book cellar and study for yourself. In the meantime, if you’re willing, I can also give you the knowledge that I have in hand, that of the Great White Bear, for you to learn."

Emin looked at Garen. At first he just wanted to bring this kid into his school. But after seeing Garen’s Master-level precision blueprints, the scales in his heart instantly fell heavily down on Garen’s side.

Chapter 256: Achievement 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Ever since his teacher left the school, the large Tasura Academy school of thought also began to crumble and fall apart, splitting into the three main divisions. The Great White Bear, the Black Panther, and The Sabertooth Tiger.

Emin actually still had a senior brother and a junior brother, both of whom lived further away. Unlike him, the two of them had long since started spreading their teachings, and now had students as well as grand-students, holding quite an influence over the local community.

They had also invited him over many times, but he rejected them each time.

As his thoughts wandered over there, Emin couldn’t help but sigh, and looked at Garen beside him.

"Your control is great, that’s the little convenience brought by Master-level precision blueprints. If you’re willing, join my school of thought, and I can help you create a White Bear core totem. Of course, once you decide on a core totem, it’ll be very troublesome later if you want to change. And this way, you’ll have to take responsibility for our school."

Garen did remember hearing about the situation of Emin’s school.

Hearing his teacher’s words, he remained silent, and did not reply immediately.

"When we get back, I’ll start teaching you the three major basic tactics. It’ll probably take a few months’ time, you can consider it carefully in that period of time." Emin knew that this was a troublesome problem as well, and didn’t force it.

************

Upon returning to Emin’s house, Garen first achieved a basic understanding of the information and principles regarding the first tactic, analysis.

After washing up hastily, he returned to his room on the first floor to rest.

The kerosene lamp by the head of his bed burned slowly, emitting a bright yellow light.

Garen sat by his bedside, rather casually flipping through the large book in his hand. The cover of the book said: Illustrated Encyclopedia of Creatures.

"Once you’ve settled on a core totem, you need to wait for more than five years if you want to change it. At the same time, you need a special ritual and ingredients to disassemble it. It’s very troublesome… but, with a decent core totem, you can have an automatically-reacting Totem Light that can follow you everywhere in life."

He understood the benefits of that. Totem Light that activated of its own accord was enough to match any dangers a Luminarist might face.

Without having to release their totem, they could automatically activate Totem Light to protect themselves at any time and place. This was also the reason Lumimarists could stand high above the rest, and disregard even the strongest normal person.

Because no matter how strong a regular person could get, they wouldn’t be able to break that Totem Light that looked so thin. That’s because attacks without silver would not be able to break the core Totem Light. This was a difference in quality, one that couldn’t be overcome by quantity.

"Only Luminarists with core totems can truly manifest this unbeatable nature of Luminarists, and stand at the peak of mortals." Garen murmured, hesitation in his heart.

Logically speaking, choosing the White Bear would make a good shortcut, but deep inside he also knew too well that compared to those unbelievably strong Luminarists in the future, the White Bear was pathetically weak.

"Whatever, now I’ll have to learn the three major tactics, and then accumulate the relevant knowledge. I’m not like other Luminarists, after regaining my power, I’m already standing at the peak of mortals. It’s the same as being a Master-level fighter in this world. I don’t have to rush in to decide a core totem to protect myself." Garen decided, and rolled into his bed, pulling his covers over himself to rest peacefully.

**********

In the time that followed. Garen learned the principles and structures of basic tactics from Emin every day, as well as how to activate his own appraisal ability.

Just as Emin said, the three major tactics weren’t hard, much less with Garen’s special physical qualities. Even regular Luminarists taking it step by step could learn them.

In that period of time, Garen’s attributes also returned to an average of 2.0 and above. Even his intelligence, his weakest point, rose to 2.0, evidently as a result of constantly using his brain.

With Garen’s undivided concentration and effort, he completely learned the three major tactics -- which were expected to take a few months to learn -- in half a month’s time, and he could use them with unnatural familiarity too. This was a great surprise to Emin, who also realized that as time went on, Garen’s ability to learn seemed to be increasing and speeding up.

Soon, he suggested letting Garen go into the underground book cellar on his own to accumulate knowledge. Those were all non-core books he had collected, mostly about basic totem construction that had become public knowledge.

The way he saw it, the thing Garen lacked now was the accumulation of knowledge, as well as a unit factory that was suitable for him and completely his own. He could create a totem for Garen, but a unit factory was different. If Garen wasn’t willing to inherit his school, then as a teacher in the future, Garen would need to create a unit factory all of his own. That involved a nearly astronomical cost…

　**********

"Now, you’ve gotten the three major tactics down. So all that’s left is to gather your own theoretical knowledge. Only with enough theories can your analysis tactic have enough information to be based on. Now, let’s go into the underground book cellar."

Emin brought Garen to the dark corner behind the stairs.

On the wall behind the stairs, there was a heavy metal door, fastened with a huge lock.

Emi handed the keys over to Garen, and then turned to walk away. He left, as though to discuss something with the little girl Nicole.

Garen held the large palm-sized key, and inserted it lightly into the keyhole. A turn.

With a clack, the large lock bounced open.

Garen pushed the metal door with all his strength. It was pitch black inside.

He walked in, and used a match to light the oil lamp on the wall.

Hiss!

It was strange. In an instant, a row of oil lamps lit up all along the walls of the underground room, forming a bright yellow row of lights.

The first oil lamp seemed to be a trigger, lighting all the oil lamps in the underground cellar at once.

The whole cellar lit up at once.

Garen closed the door behind him, observing the whole cellar quietly.

It was about as big as a futsal court, lined with bookshelves made of black stone. There were a few books scattered here and there.

There was a reading desk and chair next to the shelves, and there were sheafs of loose white paper meant for writing on the desk.

Garen followed the slope downwards, and felt a draft flowing in the book cellar. He walked to the first bookshelf on the furthest left, and glanced at the corner of the shelf. There was a black label stuck there, white words on a black base: Tactic research’.

He looked at the shelf. There were only two thin handbooks. They didn’t even have covers, and were all white.

Shaking his head, Garen walked to the second shelf.

The label said: ‘Creature composition encyclopedias’.

There were quite a few books on this shelf, of various sizes and thicknesses, filling up most half of the shelf. The largest book had pages half a meter wide, and was wrapped in very thick leather. It was like a black shield, leaning by the bottom of the bookshelf.

Garen glanced at the cover of this book: Tasura’s Creatures Illustrated.

He continued on to the third shelf.

The label said: Basic school theories.

There was only one book on this shelf. It was extremely thick, and had a leather-bound cover. It said on top: History of Totem Development.

And then, the fourth and fifth shelves had the same name: ‘Theories and Practical’.

The books there were also all about the Lumminarists’ journeys, experiences, journals and so on.

Garen casually pulled down a book and flipped through it. Each of these books were actually written in unique symbols and words. They were all encoded, and each of them differently. There were thirty-two books in total and in twenty-eight separate coded languages. Unless you knew the key to these, there was no way to read it at all. Only a few journals from recent years weren’t encoded, and these seemed to be talking about other Luminarists.

Garen had no choice but to replace all the books he couldn’t read to their shelves.

Most of the remaining shelves were about the same, including that black leather book that looked like a shield, Tasura’s Creatures Illustrated. This was encoded too, so he could only more or less see the pictures inside, and didn’t understand any of the rest.

He could only read one bookshelf.

It was the second one: ‘Creature composition encyclopedias’.

In this period of time, Emin had taught him his unique keyword, which was just enough to decode most of the books on this shelf.

Garen pulled a book off the shelf. ‘Entomology’, by Emin Kreso… and followed by a long line of names.

He flipped open this book, his brain translating its contents through rapid decoding.

This manner of decoding and translating took a long time, equivalent to the time taken to read two books. And it wasn’t easy either.

Garen slowly translated the words one by one, and the read them together.

The time ticked by. A few hours had passed, but he had only gone through half of the book.

Garen closed his eyes. They were feeling rather sore, so he rested them a bit. And then he continued reading.

His attributes had all reached extremely high levels. Faced with an intelligence of more than 2.0, almost anything he saw could be instantly understood and stored in his brain.

In the meanwhile, Emin did come down to check on him. Upon finding Garen wholly focused on his reading and studies, he went out again, feeling comforted.

That first day, Garen didn’t even finish reading that book on Entology. The book started out simple, but got more complicated as it went, and the more creatures it introduced the more complicated and intricate their systems got. There were also more things for him to remember.

On the second day, Garen continued to read and learn in the cellar. And then the third day, during which he finally finished reading the whole Entomology.

Sitting on the chair, Garen watched the light red skills attribute on his attribute pane shift a little. Light red symbols appeared, and he immediately understood what the symbols meant.

"Requirement to fully comprehend Entomology: Intelligence 1.4 (fulfilled)."

As soon as the symbols appeared, Garen felt the parts where he had been a bit blur about when reading instantly become extremely clear. Any secret parts he hadn’t understood fully before, he also comprehended in an instant.

"The first book…" He let out a long breath, glancing at the few remaining books on the shelf. This included zoology, ornithology, marine biology, microbiology and many other types. There were even more specialized books with details among them, such as ‘Composition of Butterfly-type Insects’.

Garen began to go through the books one by one, day after day, staying in the cellar.

Slowly, the books on the shelf about creature compositions began to lessen, and he piled all the books he had read on the desk.

Chapter 257: Turmoil 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Emin had originally thought of letting him gain some knowledge on the different types, categorization and its structural differences of biology. He never expected that Garen would remember all that he had seen, instantly understanding them. With the combination of high intelligence and abilities, he could vividly remember each book he read.

However, there was no complete skill formed in his Skills Pane.

After staying in the underground chamber for more than a month, Garen walked out, face wrought with fatigue. Having continuously researched all the boring academic books for more than a month, even Garen, who had strong mental capacity, felt fatigued and sleepy.

"How was it?’"

Emin stood waiting at the doorstep, quietly looking at him.

"I’ve gained a lot." Garen answered with a serious nod. "It’s just that, so many books were encrypted, I couldn’t read them."

"Naturally; neither could I, most of the books were snatched by my Teacher. There was no way of decrypting them, hence they are only fit for collection." Emin’s face had a slight hint of helplessness. "Now that you have essentially mastered the three main tactics and have already read all the books within my collection, you can be a master too. I will ask you one last time; do you want to join my school? If you do join my school, I will craft a White Bear core totem for you, otherwise, you would have to choose other core totems. Once you are ready, come to me and I will craft a core totem for you once. But I trust you would know what the result would be."

Garen nodded.

It was time to make a choice.

"For now, I will still choose not to join." He calmly professed his decision.

Emin’s mouth opened, as though he had wanted to say something; but no sound was projected.

Both parties went silent.

Garen solemnly bowed at Emin with respect.

"Regardless if I join or not, you will always be my Teacher."

Emin wave his hand with much regret.

"The Great White Bear is not as weak as you think, actually, each core totem has different evolutionary modes."

"I understand. only by inheritance from the schools can it show its strong evolutionary mode, making the core totem stronger, having headroom for evolution." Garen answered clearly.

"But…""

He did not continue speaking.

Instead, Emin nodded clearly. "I know, you would want to inherit your father’s core totem.

That’s alright, when do you plan to go back?"

"I’l rest for a bit, so tomorrow. Tomorrow, I will leave." Garen replied surely.

Emin did not say too much, instead retrieving a thick, folded piece of paper from the pocket of his long robe, which he gave to Garen.

"This is the Luminarists' Night Market, some of the popular night markets are marked on it. With your Master level detailed blueprint, you could go there to do a few jobs and earn yourself some resources. In the future, you best build your own unit factory, otherwise your unit secrets may be leaked out if you borrow it from others. Of course, you could use your father’s one, but…. You’ll know in time."

"Thank you, Teacher." Garen thanked him sincerely. In this period of time, no matter what cause or intention, Emin had been very serious and responsible in his tutelage towards him, and really brought him into the world of Luminarists.

This was had been a huge favor.

Garen understood clearly the information that he had read in the book collection chamber; a majority of them were written by Emin himself, as the encryptions that was used was his specific encryption password. All this information had contained his experience and knowledge.

From the initial deal, to the attention he gave later, up till now where he taught Garen without reserve, Emin’s change in attitude was observable to Garen

"Work hard." Emin patted Garen’s shoulder with force.

"I will." Garen nodded sincerely.

"Since you have some time on hand, let me tell you some rules while interacting with fellow Luminarists. Don’t offend or touch onto others’ taboos and create trouble." Emin solemnly said.

Ding…... Ding…...

The silver wind chimes hanging by the side of the carriage rung incessantly.

The wide, yellowish-green plain held a winding river stream. The evening sun was oddly cold, and a cold breeze blew in waves.

The pale green carriage moved forwards along the stream, slowly, just like a little green bug on a yellowish-green carpet.

The wheeler had a gray leather shirt on him, with a wine bag on his hands, which he sipped from from time to time. His mind was concentrated on the tracks on the ground in front of him.

The grass still showed telltale signs from the carriages and hoove prints from the users of the track before him.

"How long more to Natta Town?" A male voice came from inside the carriage.

"About half a day’s journey before we reach." The wheeler answered with some estimation. "We will definitely reach before dusk, be rest assured. Otherwise I would feel guilty taking those rumbs of yours." The wheeler snickered, and raised the whip and caused a loud thump with it.

In the carriage.

A handsome-looking young man with blonde hair was sitting inside, calmly sporting a long gray robe with a thick black leather book rested on his knees, with just the first page flipped.

This man was the one whohad left the small town, Garen, who left Master Emin.

Before he left, Emin gave him yet another two items.

One, the book that was resting on Garen’s knees. The second one was a short, silver-white cane, which is a storage device used to keep Garen’s butterfly totem.

Garen, while listening to the horse’s clip-clop along with the wind chimes, set his gaze on the black leather book on his knees.

The pages of the book were of the width and length of a forearm, the first page showed a line of familiar handwriting. That was Master Emin’s encryption symbols, the ink still seemed fresh.

"Master, looks like I owe you another favor…" He muttered, shaking his head lightly as he started to decrypt the line of words.

--- "I have replicated a part of my academy’s illustrations, some of these non-core items would probably be of use to you. When you are in a pinch, try browsing this book…." ---

Garen sighed, and flipped a page over.

--- "Any normal creature can evolve into strong, legendary creatures. It all depends on how you nurture its evolution."

That’s all that was written in the second and third pages.

Garen continued flipping the pages.

In the fourth page, a menacing looking black wolf appeared on the top. To its right was a colored picture, on the left was some textual explanation.

‘Black Wolf, foundation level, one of the most commonly found forest wolves in East Continent, are very large in number, vicious in nature, cunning and cruel.’

‘Special ability: sense of smell. Its strong sense of smell is much stronger than regular canines, they are quite effective in tracking and pursuit.’

‘Area of activity: Forests, hills.’

‘Totem crafting difficulty: Simple’

Garen frowned, and flipped over to the next two pages.

On the fifth and sixth pages, to the right was a black wolf with its paws stepping on crimson flames, on the left were more textual explanations.

Garen observed closely; this black wolf’s form is almost identical with the one in front, just slightly bigger in size and the bottom of its four paws are burning with a crimson colored flame.

‘Fire Wolf, Evolution Level, second form. A vicious evolution from the black wolf totem. Possess stronger and sharper fangs and claws, able to attack by supplementing biting high temperature attacks.

‘Special Ability: Sense of smell, damage fortification, high temperature fortification, self-destruct. The final special ability is the main reason why Luminarists chose the black wolf as pets, fire wolves will detonate a horrifying explosion upon death, completely melting everything within a certain radius.’

‘Totem upgrade difficulty: ten thousand grams of A-grade ruby, ten thousand grams of A-grade garnet. Success chance depends on (base material) and (totem strength before evolution). Normal success rate: 11.5%. Will self-destruct upon failure, carries a certain risk.’

Tch…..

Garen inhaled a breeze of cold air.

"Ten kilograms of grade A rubies and garnets… such high success chance!" He understood the self-destruct part, after all, the power of the Luminarists was not easily obtainable, and you can be in danger at any time.

While reading through the information, the top part advised multiple times to do all the necessary preparation before evolution, otherwise your life will be in danger easily.

"This kind of financial expenditure… if you are not noblemen, evolution should not be something you can afford at all." Garen internally simulated the situation below, finally having a clear position towards a Luminarist as a profession.

"This is as good as burning money! But on retrospect, there should be a large production of gemstones in this world...."

Garen continued flipping through the pages.

‘Giant Magma Wolf, evolution level, third form. The Fire wolf totem evolves into a terrifying giant wolf. Its power is stronger, speed if faster, its body is filled with a fluid similar to lava, just by approaching it, one can feel the hundred degree heat. It is the strongest evolution form from a black wolf, is one of the three ultimate forms of my Tasura Academy.’

‘Special ability: inherits all of fire wolf’s abilities, and gets strengthened. Exploding Fireball: able to shoot powerful exploding fireballs, destroying enemies from afar, highly destructive.’

‘Totem evolution difficulty: One piece of red dragon fruit, magma tactics. Success rate depends on (base material) and (totem strength before evolution). Typical success rate is 2.6%. Will self-destruct if failed, carries high risk.’

Garen let out a long sigh, looking at the giant magma wolf on the page.

"This is no longer a normal creature, but a true strong legendary creature. No wonder totems are so powerful, no wonder Luminarists are so powerful…"

By continuing to flip the pages, two more creatures appeared: the white bear and leopard, as well as their evolution forms.

The entire book only had three creatures, the final totem of the Tasura Academy, the sabretooth,was not shown in this book.

According to the research done by the Tasura Academy, all their creatures had three evolutionary forms. The White Bear, Great White Bear and Ice Bear. The leopard, on the other hand consisted of the Leopard, Black Wind Leopard and Night Shadow Leopard.

The final forms were like creatures of legend; each extremely tough.

However, the evolution requirements and success rates were terrifyingly low. This lets Garen witness clearly the gap among Luminarists.

"To be able to gather such detail, this meant that the final forms were not only theorized, but had actually appeared before. If we took the black wolf for example, appearance wise it was not any different compared to a regular black wolf, At most it would have white luminescence, and be a little stronger than a living black wolf. However, if it evolves into a Fire wolf, it would essentially be a killing machine. The final form, the Giant Magma wolf is simply a legendary creature! This gap between the elite and normalcy is utterly huge!"

Garen originally was unclear about what form the Luminarists could achieve, after all, the scenarios that he saw as he transmigrated were blurry, due to the strong interferences when the scenario involved high level combats.

But now, through the illustrations, he can see that Tasura Academy’s hundreds of years of ultimate totems, have already reached such heights.

Chapter 258: Turmoil 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He slowly closed the book, gazing out of the window into the now distancing plain.

From afar were a group of dairy cows and sheep sporadically walking around on the plain. S Strong winds kept flattening on the grass, which rippled like sea waves.

"It is scary being a Luminarist…" He let out a long, emotional sigh, "If I were to face the giant magma wolf…"He no longer spoke, but just imagined it. No matter how he simulated it in his mind, it would always end with utter defeat; he would not even be able to get close, and was easily eliminated.

"Looks like I have to choose my core totem soon, and be a Luminarist as soon as possible, Only then will I officially step into this world. There are only one and a half years left."

Garen kept his illustrations into his ba. Holding the forearm-lengthed silver cane, he closed his eyes and started paying attention to the skill and attribute pane at the bottom of his field of vision.

Under the skill pane, there was a faint, red, translucent symbol, just like a growing fetus, and a faint red light shining with rhythm, like a heartbeat.

This is something that Garen had noticed last night, as he looked closer, he realized that in this fetus, there seemed to be a 3D image of a luminescent butterfly.

This made him happy, he always hoped that his abilities were able provide him some help on his journey of the Luminarist. Otherwise, it would be preposterous to think that he could catch up to the elite Luminarists in the span of over a year.

And now it finally seemed like there was a glimmer of hope.

Abilities seem to slowly merge into the luminescent butterfly totem.

"The image today is clearer." Garen retracted his vision, "I guess when I go back to the manor, I would be able to showcase its real function. But I can’t just count on this, I still need to prepare on multiple different aspects."

Now what he lacks is a core totem.

The scenarios that happened while he transmigrated were always blurry during combat scenes, it was always too complicated, always with strong vibrations. He could only see clumps of colors shaking around, and could only roughly make out the strength from just how shaky it was. Even the actual totem form was not very clearly visible.

Garen refused to use a totem by the Tasura Academy, mainly because he wanted to find a strong enough totem by himself, one that gives him some confidence in what lies ahead.

But this kind of totem would require detailed inherited knowledge; how to nurture and maintain the totem, the conditions needed, even the requirements in terms of time and environment.

At least, he had some sort of plan in mind already.

The carriage arrived in a small town. Garen kept changing carriages, or joining caravans, and soon he arrived at the border of the Lush Forest District.

The Lush Forest District was a garden district. Being covered by large sections of forests, tourists came and went endlessly.

Garen arrived at a small city between the Hanna District and Lush Green district called the Ferlondo. From here, he took a tourist bus and headed for the central part of the Lush Forest District: Trejon’s Territory

In the jade-green forest, two white bus-sized carriages moved within the sea of trees slowly.

The tour guide was the hunter’s daughter; she held a megaphone-shaped paper cone, loudly introducing the culture and habits of the Lush Green District to the tourists.

The carriage was full of tourists who came for a tour, mostly husbands and wives, couples, and a family of three. They were comprised of the working class, merchants, minor nobles and military officers. Males, females and the old and young made up about twenty-odd people in the bus.

Carting the carriage were black cows with strong physiques. There were 4 of them, each about one meter-odd in height, and were about the strengthened version of a typical black cow. Occasionally, they let out a deep roar.

The wheels would run through a pebble or a small pothole from time to time, making the carriage ride a shaky one.

Garen sat on the left side of the final row of the ride, near the window.

Still wearing his usual grey robe, with a black leather box next to his legs, he looked very tidy. Much like a young lecturer of a university, carrying an aura of gentleness.

He sat facing two people, one middle-aged male pastor with black shirt and white sides, and next to a quiet young lady.

The two of them seemed to be together, but they did not talk to each other in the carriage, the atmosphere seemed awkward.

The two of them have not spoken a word since they went onboard about half an hour ago. In contrast, the four people that were sitting diagonally on the right have been speaking merrily. They are two pairs of newlyweds, the gents are talking big, about the glorious old days, about something weird that happened. The two wives were showing off new items purchased for the house; what was it, where was it imported from, and on top of that what kind of cuisines that they have tasted from which chef.

The two pairs of materialistic mercantile couples that were grouped together influenced those around them; everyone around them had started using different methods to imply that they were not to be offended, that they were able to ask favors from whoever.

The poor tour guide could only boringly talk about Lush Forest district’s culture and customs alone, although it seemed like nobody was paying any attention to her.

Of course, there were those who are not interested in engaging such conversation, like Garen, and the pastor and lady opposite him. Also the ones in front of them: a white-haired old couple and a young male military officer.

Garen studied again the comprehension of basic tactics, but upon feeling that his brain was tired, he stopped for a moment to rest.

He looked outside the window. Just when the carriage passed a metal road sign, there were some sort of words written on top, but he wasn’t able to see clearly.

"May I know where are we now?" Garen politely asked the black-shirted pastor.

"Yishenhaire, that’s what the road sign wrote." The pastor replied with a warm smile.

The lady next to him burst into laughter.

"We turned left, so we are heading to White Garcia. Don’t just blurt something out if you don’t know!"

" Perhaps I was mistaken, apologies."The pastor told Garen, with composure. "If it is the White Garcia, we would reach in about an hour." He looked at the time on his pocket watch.

"That’s fast, after White Garcia would be Trejon’s Territory, right?" Garen asked again.

"yes, the Trejons family are the local noblemen. They have maintained the territory’s original look very well. Now, it is a great tourist spot." The pastor nodded."

"We’ll get to see a lot of black swans!" The lady interrupted . "God, the black swans there are as abundant as ducks, it’s a very popular place for scenery!"

"But the bandits there are rampant too. We won’t get robbed, right?" one of the men among the 4 newlyweds on the left interrupted the conversation worrisomely.

"We won’t. I’ve heard that some time ago, the bandit lairs were mostly cleared." The pastor replied warmly. "I have been there once, to officiate a newly built small church . I have met the territory’s city planners, I have a good idea of the situation on the ground."

"The city planner should be Sinke right? Sinke Minrose, an empire officer from Hanna?"The man asked.

"You know him too?" The pastor asked, slightly surprised.

"We met a few times, He is a well mannered big-shot, we met him once at the musical."the man replied in a slightly delighted tone.

"Planner Sinke was said to have transferred here from places where the turmolous Hanna District." The pastor frowned.

"Turmolous? You mean those damned Noir Rebels? I heard the southwestern areas are quite heavily impacted….. quite a few officers have fled their cities…" The man slowed down his speech.

"Do not speak lightly about the major issues of the Empire!" The wife next to the man tugged at him.

The man and pastor stopped talking, but their expressions were visibly tensed. They noticed that the military officer sitting at the front row glancing at their direction, his look seeming slightly hostile.

Garen however, got more curious.

"You said that there is unrest at the southwest?" He gazed attentively at the pastor and the man.

"Say no more, these kinds of national issues are best not discussed in this environment." The Pastor reminded in a slow voice.

"Can you tell me which cities are in trouble?" Garen lowered his volume too, but he had an expression that looked very curious.

The man on the side could not help but to answer. "I heard that it’s Cloudray City and White Rose city."

"White Rose!" Garen was slightly taken aback. his memory showed a squared flag with black and white on each side. The left, black side was a pure matte black, and the right, a white side which symbolized the pure, elegant petals of white Rose.

"So it’s began..." Garen’s heart felt heavy.

The wheels of history have begun spinning again.

Garen tidied the history scroll, everything started with the war between the Obscuro Society and RAL.

This unrest in White Rose marked the intervention of the Obscuro Society, as well as the beginning of the end of the Reign of RAL that lasted several thousands of years.

As the fires of the war of the Obscuro Society burns, the corrupt, puss-filled body of the RAL, will completely collapse within a year.

"RAL shouldn’t collapse that easily.." Garen internally calculated carefully. "According to written history, RAL is still much stronger than the Obscuro Society, just that the inner ring held back most of their combat prowess, worrying about the troubles outside. Plus, the alliances started fighting among themselves, trying to swallow other whole by not sending help for each other. This was what caused the second wave of unrest and the third Great War."

"All these stupid royals, they think the unrest would be the same as before, that the rebels would be exterminated before long, and they would use this to empty the nation’s resources amidst the war. Unfortunately… this time will different." Garen sat alone in his seat, his heart feeling uneasy.

The battle of White Rose was Obscuro Society’s one action to gauge the RAL’s integrity. They would assume that RAL’s power was strong and far-reaching, hence they would not launch a large-scale conflict. Unexpectedly, the results were far beyond their expectations.

A simple small-scale conflict could actually exterminate the small empire by itself. The ripples from this would affect the power balance of all the neighboring countries.

Garen’s heartbeat quickened.

"The assault this time was unstoppable, soon, within two months, an war will erupt. The Obscuro Society will launch a full frontal attack, and this war will reach and affect every corner of the world. There will be no place to hide. Luminarists would also completely expose themselves to the public. Enlisting into the army and fight for their lives. I must decide on my own core totem within these two months.Oherwise, when the war erupts, and father is enlisted for war, my safety will be the biggest issue.

This is the first world war for this realm. The Obscuro Society will wage war against 23 countries, launching their strongest retaliation against the traditional ruling coalition; RAL. And they will not do it righteously, but instead use the Luminarists’ style to ignite the fire of war throughout the world.

Garen remembers that in the first world war, the Obscuro Society used totems as a base, and created an army of countless inhuman creatures, destroying everything in its path like a natural disaster. RAL will face countless losses and large areas of their territory will be taken over.

Within a year, the empires from around the world will fall, the world will descend into chaos.

However, even in such apocalyptic and dystopic outlook of the world, there will be three extremely strong and young heroes emerging. Grand Duke Goth, Crown Prince Alyson and Queen Jean Earnest.

The city that the three of them are in, would become the forefront of the resistance against the Obscuro Society, at the same time saving the Three Formations that were about to collapse, becoming the flag and standard of the resistance.

What Garen wants to do now, is to find a strong enough totem for himself within this unrest.

Chapter 259: Ambush 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Money, knowledge, a sufficiently strong totem. These three requirements must all be fulfilled, otherwise he would face immense danger in the upcoming chaos.

As Garen sat in the tour bus, his thoughts churned and churned, but still no plans came out.

Logically speaking, The Three Great Heroes are extremely strong, so long as he can get any one to inherit their knowledge, his level would reach a very high level. However, there was doubt in Garen’s

Money, knowledge, a sufficiently strong totem. These three requirements must all be fulfilled, otherwise he would face immense danger in the upcoming chaos.

As Garen sat in the tour bus, his thoughts churned and churned, but still no plans came out.

Logically speaking, The Three Great Heroes are extremely strong, so long as he can get any one to inherit their knowledge, his level would reach a very high level. However, there was doubt in Garen’s heart.

"Even if the Heroes were that strong, it would still be an imitation, it would never exceed the levels of the generals. The abilities I own, might it be able to compete against their talent?" His heart still has a sliver of hope for his own abilities.

Observing the ever-nearing silhouette of the butterfly in the vision, Garen still couldn’t calm his heart. He decided to wait for his ability to mature, and then plan things out.

Regarding the terrifying effects of the ability, he once experienced it with the secret weapon. It was definitely not what you’d say to be within the ordinary realm of strong.

When he calmed down, Garen took out a small note book, flipped over the top and jotted down some questions and thoughts on it. This would be his preparation for his core totem in the future, so he tried his best to model a totem type that he would be suited for, as well as the requirements needed to achieve such a totem.

He would sometimes shoot the breeze with the two in front of him, or casually chat with the 2 pairs of couples.

The carriage slowly moved along, considerably stable. Miss tour guide seemed to be tired from all the talking, so she sat down with a bottle to moisten her throat.

"Look! It’s a black deer!" A child shouted while pointing outside the carriage excitedly.

"There actually still are black deer!" "So Pretty!" "Is that a fawn?"

The tourists started getting rowdy.

Garen tilted his face to the right to have a look. On the grassland next to the carriage was a fawn, about half a man’s height. No antlers, its body is slim and slender, it lowered its head to feed on the grass below, occasionally lifting its head to observe the tourist bus out of curiosity, Its ears twitching a little. Very cute.

Phew…

A zephyr blew past, rustling the leaves, carrying the sound through the forest.

The black fawn then suddenly dashed into the forest, quickly disappearing from sight.

"So cute." The girl opposite Garen praised, "If only we get to rear them…"She muttered slowly, her face etched with nostalgia.

She then pulled out a small bottle from her bag, drank some water and no longer spoke a word.

However, Garen squinted, as though he had realized something. He concentrated, suddenly turning his head to the far side canopy of the forest.

"Something’s wrong… "

In the forest.

Two girls wearing jade-green dresses squatted on a tree branch, quietly looking at the carriage path in the forest, observing the two tour busses moving along slowly.

The girl on the left was about 20 years old with a slender body frame, well-defined features, her skin almost translucent. There were two black shoulder pad on her shoulders. Two quivers decorated with white feathers hung by her waist, like a beautiful kingfisher resting upon a giant tree branch.

"Vera, are you sure that the person is in one of the carriages?" she looked at the other girl, who seemed ordinary.

The other lady is slightly smaller and looked average. She had a blood red slash scar on the bridge of her nose, making her her look ferocious.

"I’ve followed them for about half an hour now, there should be no error. Our target is the man sitting at the last row of the first tour bus." Vera spoke softly, "This time elder sister ordered that we complete the mission because this affects our valuation on Green Shade, mistakes will not be tolerated.

"I know" the first lady nodded. "I was supposed to be on holiday, but I got called back earlier. Alright, let’s move out."

"Okay."

The both of them squatted on the branch, simultaneously picked out an arrow from their quivers. They flipped their left forearms, and the forearm guards on them let out a few crisp snapping sounds. The guard had turned into a short bow.

"Jii…. Jii..."

The two sounds made were from the bow’s string. Two white feathered arrows from two different angles aimed straight at the end of the first tour bus.

The thin long arrow had a yellow wood color, with a distinct carving on it - Kingfisher

"Be careful, next to Cena should be a few General-level experts guarding her." Vera spoke softly "By then it will all depend on you, Tracy."

"Leave it to me." The first lady nodded, "We will go for a one-shot kill. This arrow has been imbued with something great, and it is invaluable…"

Only then did Vera notice that the tip of the arrow resting on her bow had a silver colored metal ball which had some sort of pattern inscribed on it. It looked very delicate.

"You actually used..."

"Shh….."Tracy’s face looked slightly reluctant, "Even if she is a Master-level, she’d definitely die."

Garen sat on the seat, having chills on his back but not knowing why.

He glanced his surroundings, not noticing anything out of the ordinary.

Between his tiny movements in the eyes, his right arm reached out to the box near his leg, slowly fishing for the cane rested diagonally on his box.

Just as he gripped onto his cane, the corner of his eye scanned a white silhouette that flew towards his direction, just like a white bird.

"Such a pretty white bird…"the girl opposite him also noticed the white silhouette, suddenly she looked slightly shocked, her sentence got cut off.

"Look out!"Garen’s iris shrunk, and he ducked quickly.

Ching!!

A white arrow instantly passed through the top of his head and lodged itself on a wooden plank in the carriage. The arrowhead which was lodged inside the wood let off a sound like something was being corroded, and within two seconds, the white piece of wood oozed a large patch of dark green, which had a sourish smell and green smoke.

The entire carriage first went into shock, then it erupted into chaos.

Ahh!!!

The entire carriage screamed in panic.

The girl sitting opposite Garen ducked down into a bundle quickly, her back facing the carriage wall.

The pastor also covered his head, fearing his head would be in the line of fire.

Garen avoided the arrow, and he stood up again, looking at the direction from where the arrow fired. Far within the forest, two human-shaped silhouettes in green retreated swiftly.

Ching!!

Suddenly, he felt an extraordinarily strong sense of danger diagonally from his rear.

Garen only felt creeps behind his back, and his entire body had goosebumps.

Without stopping to think, Garen rushed out. With a crack and the carriage shaking slightly, Garen knocked down the wooden plank on the side and he jumped out through the window, rolling on the ground a few times before stopping

Bang!!

The back of the carriage exploded.

Garen did not turn back. With his back facing the carriage, he saw the grass around him reflecting a sliver of red light, the burning sensation of fire surging towards him.

Ching Ching Ching!!

Yet another three piercing sounds came.

Garen pushed hard against the ground beneath him. Two small craters were left in the grass, and he evaded the three white feathered arrows in a flash.

Bang!

The final arrow suddenly exploded where he had been a moment ago and formed a crimson red fireball. The ground and grass instantly charred, and at the same time there was some sort of weird red smoke.

Tssss...

Garen’s back felt painful. Touching it, his hand was full of burnt fabric. He felt a stinging burning sensation on his back, which made it obvious that he’s injured.

He then rolled away from where he was and into the dense forest.

"What kind of arrow is this?! Such terrifying power!" He was surprised yet angry, "Even my Divine Statue Technique with such a strong defense could not defend against it."

He moved swiftly within the forest, at the same time staying alert to his surroundings, trying to capture any trace of the two people’s. The Divine Statue Technique was fully activated, a large aura of Qi spread from within, forming a white gold aura that was not normally observable to regular people which spread across different directions.

Very soon, the aura covered the radius of more than 200 meters of the forest.

Garen closed his eyes slightly, his body unnoticeably expanded, observing the surrounding like a leopard.

Suddenly, his body turned aside, a white arrow shot past him.

"Thinking of running?" The green silhouette within his sight retreated. He sprinted with a burst of energy, leaving more impressions as he sprinted towards the direction of which the arrow was shot from.

In the forest, far away, the two green silhouettes were moving within the forest with high speed. Like monkeys who leveraged the branches around to move.

"Tracy, he’s catching up!" Vera said loudly turning back and frowning.

"Such speed… interesting." Tracy laughed coldly, the silhouette was running at high speed, but his breathing was so calm, as if that person was standing on a platform. "I hadn’t expect that so many arrows would not kill him. Looks like this person is the expert who is protecting Acacia by impersonating him. He must be thinking of baiting the enemies and finishing them at one go. Their plan was great, but too bad they met me."

"I used two Red Smoke Arrows, but it could not hurt him at all, I estimate that he is a Master-Level, so I guess we should "treat" him appropriately."

"Tracy laughed cunningly. Her right left a slight afterimage as pulled out four arrows from the quiver and placed them all on the short bow and pulled.

Jii…. The string was tugged instantly, almost a full moon.

Ching ching ching ching!

4 minute piercing sounds rang, all four arrows pinned onto four different tree trunks. Forming a large arc.

Ching ching ching ching!

Another four Red Smoke Arrows were shot into 4 other trees, forming another large arc, the two arcs came together to form a circle, which was oddly symmetrical.

"The Ambush of Red Smoke, since you want to close the distance, I’ll let you." Tracy stood her ground and would rather not run anymore. "Vera, you go ahead, waiting for the results at the outer ring will do."

"Okay." Vera jumped into the forest.

Bam!

Vera suddenly fell back, as if she was pushed back by a force field, both her legs drew tracks in the ground,, and with a "bam" she smashed into the tree.

Garen walked slowly into this part of the forest, standing far away, with his sight fixed on Tracy, and took a look at their attire.

"Who are you guys?" His tone was very deep. Looking at Vera by the side of the tree, who withstood one of his Red Jade Palms. She merely puked some blood, and did not look like she suffered major injuries. She would be able to continue combat.

"As a mortal, You could withstand two red smoke arrows, impressive." Tracy’s expression became calm again, glanced over at Garen, and busted a laugh.

She suddenly took out a black iron plate, and waved it in front of Garen.

"Now talk, where is Acacia now? Bring him to me obediently, and then cripple your own two arms as a honest sign of apology, otherwise I wouldn’t mind killing you here." She thought for a moment, "Right, which school are you from? I am very interested in your martial arts, write me a copy of all your martial arts while you’re at it."

"?" Garen looked at her, confused, as if he was looking at an idiot. This woman had no idea what she’s talking about, with just one iron plate and she wants him to surrender, cripple his own hands and give his martial arts to her for free? Did she read too many novels?

Chapter 260: Ambush 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Why? Can’t do it?" Tracy laughed coldly, "Haha, it’s true that adventurers are the kind of idiots who do not know how to give up until the end. A bunch of idiots with muscles."

"You… You are from the Mercenary Guild!" Garen suddenly identified the plaque and its significance. When Cia was younger, Cousin Sofea mentioned it once.

The Mercenary Guild is the strongest among mortals, a terrifying dark organization. They committed countless misdeeds, and have wide connections in the dark world like spider webs. Its inner circle was very mysterious, even many kings of different empires had been successfully assassinated by them before. They were the sole rulers of the dark world.

"As an adventurer, you should know the rules. Perhaps you thought that a normal Luminarist would suffice to protect you?" Tracy continued laughing coldly.

Garen frowned, he didn’t know anything about adventurers, but the strength of the Mercenary Guild was well known. Obviously the opponent thought he was meddling with the dark world, like they were.

"Whatever, talking to idiots like you gives me headache." Tracy waved her hand away.

"Are you retarded? Or do you think everyone is as retarded as you?"Garen got lazy of thinking, so he spoke directly, and sarcastically. "Just a simple plaque and you expect me to stop resisting and surrender immediately?"

Tracy’s expression turned cold.

"There’s actually someone who doesn’t know my title of Kingfisher…."

Shikkk!

She flung her left forearm, and a green short bow formed, her right arm pulled the bowstring back and a "chikk" sound was heard.

"Forget it, personally killing you wouldn’t take much time anyway." Tracy smirked weirdly.

"Boastful!" Garen hmphed. With a big step forward, his body form turned into an afterimage that rushed forward.

At the same time, the bowstring loosened, Tracy did not move at all, while Garen rushed forward. A weird sonic boom spread across all directions.

The pair’s movements were set in stone from this moment.

Bam bam bam!

A barrage of crimson red fire exploded in all directions. A cloud of red smoke engulfed the forest like cirrus, leaving no space untouched.

"Heart of Awakening, Ares’ river!" Tracy raised her arms, suddenly her right arm was pulling the bow string with insane speed.

Ching ching ching ching!

Continuous rings from the bowstring formed a unique sound vibration.

The vibration and the red smoke got closer to Garen, forming a complete seal-in roundup, surrounding him from many directions.

Garen stood in the middle, and closed both eyes. He suddenly inhaled large amounts of air in one go, his cheat bulged like a balloon, and it looked terrifying.

Suddenly, his eyes opened, and his irises held traces of white and gold.

"North Capturing Hand!"

Fuu!!

The wind blew.

The wind caused the forest to rustle.

The sphere formed from the red smoke erupted with a large hole. Large amounts of red smoke started spinning and congregated on itself, forming beneath Garen’s left hand, forming a fast rotating, pressurized red air ball.

Garen rushed forward surrounding himself with the vortices, the air around him sounding like the terrifying roar of an elephant

The right palm swung forward! Pressurized air and aura violently rushed onto Tracy’s chest. The strong air flow carried with it the surrounding leaves and rustling, as though a tornado just blew past. It was horribly powerful.

The shockwaves activated by the bowstrings were completely collapsed. The red ball was violently pressed upon Tracy’s chest. A red hot light bathed her face in red.

"Heavenly Arc!!!!"

Tracy shouted, she did not retreat, but instead rushed forward split into two silhouettes; one rushing forward, and another is disappearing slowly, it was an illusion!

The green bow’s bowstring was tensed to point of breaking. The string had actually glowed briefly.

Zzang!

After releasing the bowstring, it became a silver arc, cutting towards Garen’s right palm.

In that instance, both persons attacked simultaneously, The North Capturing Hand and Heavenly Arc merged and formed a terrifying effect.. The red smoke ball and the silver arc collide.

Vera, who was nearby, shielded both her eyes.

Honggg!

A powerful gust of wind almost swept Vera off her feet, and she fumbled backwards a few steps. Both her ears were ringing incessantly, and she could barely hear anything.

After things had settled down, she took in her surroundings once more..

On the battleground was a grey silhouette colliding furiously with a green silhouette, each time they collided, the green silhouette would release a dim luminescence.

"Tracy actually used the Totem Light!" Vera took two steps back, her heart aghast. For Tracy to be using the Totem Light should be unrivalled by anyone that’s not a Luminarists! That is the trump card given by the organization.

But now she could only barely keep up with the opponent as equals?!

Agh A female voice let out a cry of pain.

In the intense combat, the green silhouette was knocked backwards and some fresh blood was spilled.

The silver silhouette caught on, both palms appeared to have a red jade texture, the sound of elephant roaring in the air have also became clearer.

Bam!

Both people engaged in combat once again. The ripples of the air blades struck the trees nearby, causing axe-like gashes on the trees, chipping off countless white tree barks shreds.

Garen showed himself, and with a hammer-like fist swinging downwards, clouds white and red smoke congealed his palm.

"Deity’s Possesion!" He roared ferociously. A platinum silhouette appeared behind him vaguely, then shrunk rapidly and rushed into his body.

His entire body started swelling to the height of about 2.5 meters, his body also had well defined muscles, much like a titan in the legends.

"How can a martial art reach this level??!"Tracy spat out fresh blood, she took a few steps back staggering, her eyes not believing what she saw.

"It’s over!" Garen’s eyes recalled a brand new martial arts skill tree, and he had a sudden epiphany.

He grabbed her with one hand.

"Kandas Vieira, Gods’ combined martial art!!"

His right hand suddenly became slow, the back of his hand glowed a line of light.

Instantly, countless blue lights illuminated from Garen, each ray became thinner, and smaller, covering the entire forest within the 100 meter- radius.

Tracy could only feel a large, terrifying formless pressure engulfing her.

"No!! No!! I will not die here… No!!" She struggled to pull the bowstring of her bow.

Lifting her arm, trying to take aim at Garen.

Jii…..

The bowstring was pulled halfway.

Blood oozed from Tracy’s eyes, nose and ears. Her body started trembling as she looked at the expressionless Garen.

"You…!!" it is as though she wanted to say something.

Her head exploded, it turned into a puddle of red-white goo-like mixture which was strewn all over.

Badum.

A headless corpse collapsed on the ground.

The forest became peaceful and quiet once again.

Garen stood back up with a handstand, but he stood in front of Tracy’s corpse, and he turned around to look at Vera.

The latter had knelt down on the round, tightly wrapping her hands around her throat, her face pale and without breath.

Garen lifted his right index finger. A blue butterfly appeared from behind him, resting upon his fingertips.

"This is all thanks to you, otherwise I’m afraid the other one would have ran away." Garen muttered.

With a light flick, the glowing butterfly turned into a blue light, and shot into the cane hanging on his waist.

Garen rushed to search Vera and Tracy’s bodies. He did not wait around for long, instead he left the place quickly.

He reminisced his final palm strike, the pinnacle form of the Deity’s Possession.

If say, in this world, his battle with Cayduran had approached the pinnacle of human limits, then the battle just now, he felt that he had found out how to use the power of a Luminarist, matching it with the secret techniques to show a perfect combat style.

Ever since he came to this world, Garen had been dissatisfied that the secret techniques were unable to advance. However, he had found a sliver of hope.

Running through the forest, he hastily rushed back to the area nearby the tour carriage.

Tourists of the carriage had mostly died, save for a couple of tourists supporting each other, and resting on a tree nearby, their face full of blood and boils that were caused by the fire.

From the attire and clothes, Gare could recognize that these are the pastor and the young military officer.

That were very lucky, to be able to withstand the burn from the Red Smoke and live to tell the tale.

Garen felt a twinge of guilt. After all, the pair were targeting him, but in the end it brought in two carriages full of people. Even if he had in fact killed countless people, but these were innocent lives caught in the crossfire, which made him very guilty.

"The damned Obscuro Society!" His face seemed forlorn.

The clip-clopping of horses came from afar. A platoon of black-clothed chivalry units were headed this way.

Garen quietly walked out of the forest, the black robe on his body having been torn and damaged during the intense fight with Tracy. There were a lot of blood stain on his clothes too.

At the same time, he silently activated the Turtle’s Breath to conceal his aura, and now his face looked terribly pale, without a trace of vitality and looked extremely weak.

As he approaches the pastor and military officer, the officer lifted his head to give him a glance.

"You have very good luck."

Garen opened his mouth to say something, but instead he coughed uncontrollably.

"Don’t talk, Look at you, I guess you fell out from the carriage right?" the pastor’s boil-filled face cracked open with a smile that somehow looked worse than crying. His eyes look swollen, perhaps he had just cried.

Garen nodded, and he sat next to the two of them, breathing loudly, coughing strongly from time to time.. He looked half-dead.

The speeding horses were approaching. The black knights quickly stopped next to the trio, each getting off their horses and frowned at the scene littered with corpses in the carriage.

"This is terrible…" One young female knight’s face turned pale, and she covered her mouth. She had just witnessed a three-year-old boy’s brain and body severed by an enraged black cow. The boy’s face still had traces of him crying.

The knight leading the platoon was a middle-aged man who got off the horse. With a heavy face he walked to the side of the carriages, and he pulled out an arrow that was lodged in the carriage.

"The Mercenary’s Guild again! Those damned bastards!" He couldn’t help but to shout, his chest bulged and released, and he looks very irritated. "Louis! Immediately inform the Secret Services! Keith, investigate the deceased’s identities! Give me a list of their immediate family contacts! If the Secret Services does not care, report it to the National Council! If they don’t respond this will be under my jurisdiction!"

He slapped the carriage once again out of anger. The back of his hand had traces of light glowing.

Garen, who was sitting on the side was feeling downcast. At the corner of his eye he saw the sliver of luminescence and his heart skipped a beat.

"This person is a Luminarist as well?! The National Council?! One of three departments! This person must have ties to people that work inside!"Garen had multiple thoughts crossing through his mind.